WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Leave it! You sister-fucker!
Leave it! Leave it!
I didn't know where I was.
Who brought me here? don't know.
Why they brought me here? I don't know.
Life was like hell to me, Sardar Ji.
Just like yours, will be.
Sister-fucker!
Jai Hind, Sir!
Bibinka623 has been activated.
They don't want...
The biggest billionaire. He's
finally decided to go to Montreal
to save 400 millions in tax, you see.
Sir, Bibinka623 has been activated.
Fuck!
When I got out from
that dark cellar after 40 days,
there was only one thing in my mind.
I just have to fuck them all!
Whoever had done this to me...
Isa, Parulkar, everyone!
Then I realized that this
game is much bigger than
these bastards...
bigger than you... bigger than me.
My information
is never wrong, Sardar Ji.
I told you that Trivedi would survive.
Swear, I told you the truth.
Try to solve this riddle...
you would get all the answers.
Sir, we got this
pamphlet from the bunker
it looks like a recruitment
poster of a terrorist outfit.
Generally they propagate such materials,
usually before any big attack.
And it says this is time of war, now.
ISIS has been trying to breach in India,
- this maybe any splinter group
- No.
We have been keeping a close
watch on ISIS, at the state level.
There's nothing alarming there.
Our agent... Anjali Mathur...
She was studying Hizbuddin.
We got a tip-off from Baluchistan...
Mario, - Sir.
... set up an SIT for this.
Lashkar, ISIS, and Hizbuddin...
- For the time being let's go after them.
- Sure, sir.
Sartaj... good work.
Will you join the SIT?
Yes, sir.
Sir...
... SPI Majid Khan
is specialist on terror cells.
Sure.
Majid, Sartaj will take
the lead on this case..
Yes, sir.
Now, you're the boss.
Give me a treat, man.
That big arms consignment
has a direct link to Bhonsle's NGO...
How does Hizbuddin fit into this?
Couldn't Bhonsle be
working for someone else?
You think so?
You don't get involved in big cases,
so, you won't know the
reality of Shahid Khan.
He has his hand in everything,
from the 93 blasts in Mumbai
to the Kandahar Hijacking.
We must check.
You find Shahid Khan.
I'll look for Gaitonde's third father.
It's alright!
Its over! Its over!
What's going to happen in 25 days?
My father will fuck you all,
but I'll save Trivedi.
Which father?
That priest in village?
No, Sir. I've three fathers.
Three reasons why I'm here.
The first one put fear in me,
the second gave me the
courage to face it.
And the third one who
I loved most, betrayed me.
It is possible to conquer time....
Because time is radioactive.
It decays and it stays... forever.
it is a circle.
And this circle of time is divided into
four Eras.
Four Yug.
Megha?
Megha!
Yes?
Can we try it again?
You speaking rubbish.
I'm damn serious.
Serious?
Alright.
Let's talk seriously.
Why now?
Because...
I can't do this anymore.
One by one...
I'm loosing everyone from my life.
I'm feeling lonely.
Now, I'm scared that...
You'll leave me as well.
I'm already gone, Sartaj.
No, Megha, please...
Please, don't say this.
We'll only fight.
No.
It's too late now.
You don't understand Sardar ji,
where the story is heading?
I didn't get it as well.
Life was weird in there.
I mangled one of the guards,
but even then he didn't tell
me a word about our location.
Well, what would
he say now that he's dead.
The raging fire of
revenge burned within me
while I tried swimming in
freezing waters, towards Mumbai.
Everyday I were swimming
gradually more than previous day.
Slowly approaching towards Mumbai.
There was nothing to do on the boat.
Swim daily,
eat shitty fish,
and jerk off thinking about Gopalmath.
That was the life.
Then one day, in the distance,
that answer was coming to me.
Hold this.
Wait sir.
This is your bag.
Let me speak first.
Anything else?
Ma'am you don't know him.
He's a crazy guy.
A man has died trying to control him
Where is he?
He was there, just sleeping.
Did anyone come in the room?
- I don't know.
- Ganesh! Ganesh!
Motherfucker, I'll shove
those keys up your asshole.
Come here, and take this key.
Shove'em up whoever's ass you want.
What's this Gaitonde?
- We were coming to talk to you.
- Shut up, you asshole!
I want to go back to Mumbai.
Gopalmath!
You can't go to Mumbai, yet, dear.
Who are you?
A friend.
What do you want? Just tell me.
You have just locked me
here like a fucking cattle.
There's a country
in Africa called Kenya.
There's a city called Mombasa.
It's not far from there.
I heard you tried
swimming back to Mumbai?
If you want to swim
then it'll only take you
188 years to reach there.
I've calculated it.
If you can read Marathi, then read it.
While I was stuck
jerking off in her memory.
DIPAK SHINDE ALIAS
BUNTY JAILED FOR 2 YEARS
Mumbai...
Mumbai was forgetting me.
Trivedi's men
demolished the Babri Mosque.
Isa planted bombs in the
city, with ISI's agent Shahid Khan.
Police did tit for tat.
They wanted every gang out.
Grab him.
Hey! Hey! Hey... you government
officers. Show some respect!
Come out!
Leave me! I'm coming with you.
Isa and me vanished;
Mumbai's balance was disturbed.
All the mafia business was wrecked up.
And Gopalmath became wasteland.
How can I run?
The country got divided in 1947
Mumbai was minced in 1993.
Some took over the city.
and some were forced into ghettos.
My Mumbai was dying.
Name?
Kusum Devi Yadav.
What do you want?
Work for us, here in Kenya.
I don't work for anyone.
We're offering partnership.
Start your business here
and later I'll get your
guys free from the jail
You want to revenge from Isa, right?
I can help in it.
Who are you actually?
I have friends in Mumbai.
And here?
Here as well.
Partnership?
Who was over the phone?
What phone?
That one whom I spoke with in jail.
In Jail?
Don't fuck with me asshole.
You brought me here. You
know who I'm referring.
Yes, yes. Guru Ji! Guru Ji.
His preachment.
And yes...
Push the button if you like.
That will be our signal.
The first incarnation of Lord Vishnu,
is "Matsya".
A fish.
is directly connected
to the very beginning of
the life on the earth.
We, humans, also evolved from the fish.
One day, the almighty God,
was so aroused after seeing
own creation, and got ejaculated.
His semen directly dropped into the sea.
In the sea,
a fish swallowed it.
The semen was so potent
that the fish
started suffocating after swallowing it.
Here, done.
Whether Aryans or fighters
or a shreded arrow.
I want chicken.
Whether scholars or keen
or the sages of the high mountains.
Brought me fish next time I'll
shove it in your ass, you fucker,
And it'll keep swimming in there
until we fucking reach Mumbai.
It only exists then.
That time I thought it was all bullshit.
Later, I realized that
Guruji was telling me my own story.
I was the fish of that story.
I was suffocating as well.
I made my efforts.
I had decided that
I have to get off this
boat, first of all.
Jai hind, Sir. First floor upstairs.
The first room is yours
I'll bring your stuff.
This is Katekar's package.
From L.T. Marg.
Kamble.
Yes, Sir?
Has Katekar's compensation
letter arrived.
No, Sir. I won't come that soon.
Sir, please make a call
to Shalini and tell her
if any letter is received at home,
she has to sign and send back here.
Get ready.
Hey, listen.
Wait a minute. I'll get the lunchbox.
- Don't worry.
- Hey.
Easy!
I'm trying.
Your father did this.
Where could this pamphlet be printed?
I don't know.
Majid, We have to do our duty.
So, you do yours.
First go to Sulphur
Road, then Neel Ghaati.
Hey!
Malcolm, come on, I'm also leaving here.
Take me with you.
I'm fucked up
with your tactics. Let's go.
You must stay underground
I won't say anything to
anyone. You motherfucker.
- Let me go!
- There's no way to say a word.
Hey, Malcolm! Don't try
to act smart with me.
Malcolm, give me my phone.
Motherfucker!
You're hitting me?
Malcolm! You motherfucker! Motherfucker!
Hey! Leave me!
Leave me!
Hey, Malcolm.
Hey, you sister-fucker.
Gaitonde left something with you.
Tell me, where have you hidden it?
What? I don't have anything.
I don't know what you want.
Please, I don't know.
I don't have what you want.
Please...
I don't know what you want.
I don't know...
I don't have anything.
- You've last chance...
- I don't have anything.
I...
- Tell me.
- I don't have...
What else did he say about Trivedi?
As much as I told you.
Did he ever mention about Malcolm?
- Inspector, I'm done here.
- Anything about an Egyptian man?
If you call me one more time,
I'll sue you for harassment.
Then the fish crawled
back from sea to land.
But, just like a crocodile does
it was still important to stay near sea.
- Hello, who's this?
- Whats up, ass-wipe?
Gaitonde boss?
Boss, where are you?
I'm 188 years far from you.
You are out?
Yes, boss.
They hit me very hard.
Then suddenly released me last week.
Kanta Bai is also out.
Don't know why they caught
us and why they released us.
I'm worried perhaps they can shoot us.
Boss, our business is dead.
I know it.
I'm just taking biscuits with black tea.
I'll take care of it.
Boss, you are 188 years away or 188 km?
I'm on the moon, you moron.
It'll take some time
to come back to Mumbai.
What are you doing there, boss?
Things are going to normalise
here, please try to come soon, boss.
- It'll take some time.
- How much time boss?
One month.
One month?
But moon is right here, over our heads.
It'll take whatever time
it takes, you dickhead.
If I piss here then it'll take
one month to fall on your head.
Look, this is "their" Juhu beach.
Go and drown in it.
Bunty, listen. They got me stuck here.
But I'll get out from
here whatever it costs.
You can run Gopalmath if you want.
I want the whole
gang reunited here. Okay?
Okay, boss.
- Okay, now hang up.
- Boss! Boss!
Yes?
Kanta Bai is right
here. Just talk to her once.
She really loves you.
Okay, I'll kiss her when I see her.
Boss!
Fuck!
We're playing carrom here
and Boss has reached the moon.
This is called fate.
Pick it up.
Haste is foolish, Ganesh.
Miss Yadav is very sharp.
It's not easy to go away from her.
Who's she?
She's a RAW operative.
You asshole, why you brought her to me?
Because, we're more sharp than her.
Fuck this sharpness.
Let her think that
your balls are in her court.
When the time is right make your shot.
Don't give me a lollipop.
No, Miss Yadav's friendship
is a protein shake
rather than a lollipop.
It will take you to Isa.
I don't like protein shake.
The control is in her hands.
You life, your freedom
is a collar she's tied around your neck,
That you can't remove from your neck.
Till when?
Until Guru Ji can
find a way out of this.
Look here, it's your new house.
Come in.
Trivedi insisted so I took the job.
I came to know,
that same fucking shit is
going on outside india.
When the USSR invaded Afghanistan,
then USA and Pakistan used an old trick.
They pushed local militants.
They backed them for blasts
and suggested to cartel for money.
Militants would smoke
some and sell the rest to Europe.
USSR got defeated
there but business stayed.
Before reaching Europe,
the product would land in Kenya.
Where the people were poorer than us.
The government more corrupt than us,
and youth addict more than us.
Mohammed Bobocha was Kenya's Gaitonde.
He controlled 80%
marijuana business there.
And there was a
new dealer in the market.
Purushottam Baria, born stingy.
He was a smart-ass but was a kid.
There was a rumor
among erotica magazine sellers
that he couldn't pop a boner.
I'm too tired.
We need to establish
Purushottam in the market.
Get Bobocho out of the way.
How?
Same as Junk-King Raja Momin did
for Gaitonde.
Over his corpse.
If Purushottam will replace
Bobocho what advantage would I have.
I'll let you know in due course.
What kinda partnership is this,
where I can only count
but she knows all the math.
Ma'am I want to go back Mumbai.
I still have unfinished
business with Isa.
Isa is not coming back to Mumbai.
He got settled in a new country
with new business and fate.
The kind of power he has now, there,
he never had in Mumbai.
You're worthless compared to him today.
And only I know where he lives.
So stop yapping on about Mumbai.
And prove it me, that your worthy
that I should let you live.
This house,
and the guards outside are mine
and you're able to speak because of me.
So, in this partnership,
I'm on 90% and you're on 10.
When you work your way up to 50,
then we'll talk about partnership.
Whether its a lollipop
or a protein shake
but the reality was
I don't have any short-cuts
for now except for Ma'am,
to be a king again.
So I listened to every
bullshit of Ma'am.
And I became Vivian Shah from Gaitonde.
An Indian businessman in Kenya.
And called my boys Gaston,
Pascal and Mathu from Bombay...
... here in Kenya.
To set my own gang.
The dairy business got flopped.
So daddy came here
and started the coffee business.
And asked me to join in it.
But,
I've other business intents.
Purushottam bro,
I'm new in business here,
you know.
I've an intention to
work with right people.
Whom I can trust.
Trust?
This's a big word brother Vivian. Trust.
No one is trustworthy here.
One hundred ten million shillings...
I'll buy six ships from you.
You aren't so raw, man.
You want something else.
Purushottam, I've bigger plans.
What?
Not now.
First, I'll please you,
then I'll offer you drinks.
And when you start thinking
through you dick not head
then I'll tell you.
I'll think about it, brother Vivian.
I have some other work, right now.
Bye.
Purushottam was a Gujarati.
And to do business with
a Gujarati you had to create a need.
First, I tipped off Babocho
that Purushottam is trying
to break in his business.
And when Purushottam
understood our value
then I played my second card.
- Hello.
- What's up ass-wipe?
- Yes, boss.
- I want Jamila.
Jamila who, boss?
Jamila, the one whom
you sent in the jail.
Before meeting her I thought
I would never get boner
again, that Jamila.
Boss, actually I got some
issues with her manager.
Manager?
Since we're running out of cash
so all her payments are pending.
Give me her number.
Hello.
I want to talk to Jojo.
Who?
Vivian Shah.
Who gave you this number?
I got number from Prime
Minister, my dad runs parliament.
Give it to Jojo.
Who gave you this number?
I told you.
But I'm asking. Who
gave you this number?
So you're the Jojo, right?
- Whoever am I, idiot...
- Look...
- Hello.
- Hello, Bunty?
- Yes, boss.
- That bitch hung up on me?
- Who? Boss.
- Jojo.
She's a hard fish to catch,
slips out of everybody's hand.
Hello.
Bunty gave me the number.
What do you want?
One of your girls, Jamila.
So what?
- Yes, that I want.
- Where do you want her?
Did Bunty tell you that I would yell?
- Yes.
- Did I yell?
- No.
- So, move on and tell me.
Need her in Kenya.
Clear old accounts and
pay full advance for this.
Okay.
And I need a deposit of
50% in cheque, not in cash.
Okay, got, I'll do it.
And one of my boys will
be there and stay with her.
Stay with her, where?
Wherever Jamila will go.
He will bring her there and take back.
- He'll bring her. He'll take back.
- So, what'll I do? Jerk Off?
Fuck you then...
There're many rhinos
roaming in Kenya fuck anyone.
Do you know who you're talking to?
Yes, I know.
Maybe your daddy owns
parliament, Ganesh Gaitonde
but I don't fucking care for it.
Do you wanna die?
Yes.
I've tried four times.
What's there to try?
Put a gun over your head, take
a shot, brain scrambled and end.
Will you kill me?
I'll pay in cash.
Why do you want to die?
I'll send you the invoice.
Brother Vivian,
now I'm thinking from my dick.
Tell me what I need to do?
Let's fuck Bobocho.
Meaning?
Purushottam, if you want
to do business, do it big.
Otherwise don't do it.
Have you lost your mind?
Killing Bobocho isn't a game.
It is a game, Purushottam.
And I'm the champion of this game.
And it won't be me,
but you, who'll kill him.
Malcolm!
Open up! I'm the Home
Minister you sister-fucker.
Malcolm!
Hey, bro! Hey, get up!
Stop! Stop it, here!
Stop here.
Wait here, I'll send money from inside.
- Why did you sit, if you had no money...
- Sister-fucker, I'm sending you.
Fucker! Wait here.
Hey, motherfucker.
Hey, you fuckers!
Hey, hey! Motherfuckers!
You motherfuckers, I'm a Home Minister.
If you're from Neeli Ghaati,
you won't get a job anywhere in Mumbai.
This used to be a village.
This became a Muslim
colony after '93 blasts
Why here?
Because there were no place left.
Hey!
Whose shop is this?
- Is this printed here?
- No.
How long has this press been here?
My father's friend got me a job here.
So, I'm here.
This is all there is.
I'm asking...
I've been working here from 6 months.
- Where is this printed?
- As I told you I don't know.
Excuse me!
Is this printed here?
We don't do these types of jobs, Sir.
Then who does?
It's pulp, sir. Must
be a small offset press.
There's a junk shop in Barkat alley.
You should check there.
What I'm going to tell him now?
He's going to say I'm fucking him.
He'll say I'm keeping
a cut in the middle,
what can I say to him?
Tell him that I need my right now...
You're supplying to the all
the printing press here, right?
Yes, Sir. We do provide cartons
and transportation to the printers.
Why? What happened, Sir?
Have you seen this before?
Sir, it isn't very clear.
Yes, its ok. Fine, yeah.
Sir...
Hey, you, come here!
Majid!
Kamble!
Don't move, don't move!
Move, asshole!
Awaish.
Usman.
I need something.
Go back.
Come on.
Hey, get up.
What is this?
You've prepared for the war
and don't even know the enemy.
Incredible, Sir.
What are they planning to do?
Sir, I'm asking to you what they'll do?
What else they could do?
They'll do what they know best.
Right? Bomb blasts, attacking stations,
hotels... What else they'll do!
What they'll do! What they'll do!
Will they blast bombs or
launch a nuclear attack?
What did you say?
Exactly what you heard.
Nuclear?
A nuclear attack, yes.
You mean to say, just like
Hiroshima & Nagasaki?
Like that?
Do I'm look like a moron?
Don't chew Bobocho?
Just maul it and
distribute it among people.
You just said a very
hard-ass word, Gaitonde.
I can't understand.
Bobocho doesn't share
his business with anyone.
He keep everything for himself.
Right? He just opened a new casino.
You need fucking 20,000
shilling to enter.
But you won't do the same.
You'll be an umbrella
and each and every boys of
Kenya will work under it.
And they'll sell
product where they want.
You'll be the Prime Minister
and the rest will be your parliament.
Shoot him in the face. Okay?
People should know who you are!
Kill him!
Shoot, sister-fucker!
You guys continue. The show must go on.
I'm a vegetarian, bro.
Cut.
Should I cut the finger?
Cut the head, you wimp.
I'll make a souvenir with this
head and hang it on my wall.
Everyone should know
that there is big predator
than lion of Massai Mara,
now in the town.
Speak in their language.
They didn't understand a shit.
Now, tell me.
Why did you get Bobocho killed?
Bobocho was handling drugs for
the biggest cartel in Dubai.
This cartel funds ISI.
Who make blasts in India.
By killing Bobocho you've served
your country for the first time.
What's my status now,
have I reached to 15 or 20?
Your buddy got involved
in a cartel, last year.
With ISI.
Memorize the number and burn it.
We became fish, then
crocodile then lion, and then monkey.
But we evolved from monkey
to humans when we got religion.
This video was in their phones.
Even in this they are
talking about Ghazwa-e-Hind.
Hizbuddin, the man of Jihad.
The prophet has claimed in the Hadith,
that there will be two armies.
It's Shahid Khan's voice.
Real religion tells
you what's in the afterlife
what man will become in the next life.
When will this game end?
You don't believe in
religion, right, Sardar Ji?
So I'll tell you what will happen next.