WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
You think we're fucking fools?
Your phone data is revealed.
Who joined virtual training of
Hizbuddin for two weeks last year,
on Facebook Live?
Bhide...
- Bring me some hot water.
- Yes, Sir.
Was it you?
Do you think we're fools, that we've
brought you here for amusement?
Huh?
Do you really need any
reason to pick up a Muslim?
Find out who else is
there in their family.
Have we picked up anyone else?
Okay, Sir.
We'll have to try another way.
Didn't sleep, yet?
These are your father's belongings.
You were listening to Guruji's
preachment yesterday?
Prabhjot Singh Thane West
Papa had joined the Ashram?
He never mentioned it?
He never hid anything.
But you were at Nanded
at that time on your first posting?
My dear, Prabhjot,
I'm doing well.
Today was the 3rd day of Nashik event.
Guruji said something,
in his preachment that shook me
But his words always
have multiple meanings
Ok, I'm going off to bed.
I wonder why
he called me his Ashwathama.
Hello?
Just tell me one thing,
Does one give or receive gifts on Eid?
Gaitonde!
Switch on your TV... watch.
There's a surprise for you.
Hussein Rehmaani allegedly
handled Suleiman Isa's black money
and funneled the money
into the African drug trade.
If sources are to be believed
Suleiman Isa is involved
with the infamous Dubai cartel.
This my Eid gift, in advance.
You've nothing to give or take.
the first of the planned...
You ran away from Bombay only to
become the government's dog. Huh?
I heard that they put you on a
leash and take you for a walk.
And you serve them all the info
that you have sniffed out.
I'll sniff my way to you.
Try pulling
your leash
it won't reach me, here.
Hewas right, Sardar
Ji, that's why it irked me.
I've to reach same
level if I want to reach Isa.
It was year 1995,
One Ganesh idols were drinking milk,
but other Ganesh was getting thirstier.
Hey you fat ass, don't itch your nose?
Do it with virility, motherfucker.
Work faster.
Listen you...
You don't have the fuse to that
button which makes you hard,
once I cut the wire you'll
never get a boner in your life.
You dick.
To reach Isa's status,
I tried each and every shit job.
At times put money on white powder
and at times on black rhinos.
We'll give you $2,000.
No, no my friend, $2,000
that's way to less.
This a rhino horn.
Okay, the powder makes
you a real man. Strong.
Gives you the energy... to you know...
Look, there's huge
demand of this, in China.
And in Kerala...
So...
... its a deal?
But every business was
over crowded like a cattle class.
- Hey, Harsha?
- Yes?
I want to live with you.
Are you crazy?
I'm married.
Don't you love me?
Huh?
You know, what happens in the
underwear, on the bed...
is not called love.
You scared of Purushottam?
He worships me.
And that's the problem.
I'm his goddess...
... not wife.
Then let's also make
our relationship divine.
Lea...
- What're you doing?
- Come here!
Now you go.
Leave.
Push me!
Push!
Take down the number.
+2542609393.
Willson Kamau. He's a friend.
If you've any problem then call him.
Willson, he's Ganesh Gaitonde,
aka Vivian Shah.
- Hello!
- Hello.
Two shipments have left for India.
Army... I mean they're
carrying guns of Kenyan Army.
Some general is messing with it.
Yadav Ma'am's life was
like a suspense mystery film.
She had a kid daughter in India.
Hello, Pilu?
How's your cough, baby?
Yadav ma'am casually mentioned
that Isa has 50% stake in 'Gentleman',
a premium whiskey brand of Kenya.
Now, I found my plan
to bring Isa to Kenya.
Let's fuck up Gentleman!
I stole Gentleman, and called Kanta.
She taught me how to bootleg whiskey.
Mathu also became expert in making hooch
Boss, it's very easy.
Just insert the coin and start betting.
Nobody must have seen it there.
Bunty offered a smart business idea.
He brought Bombay's game to Kenya.
Video games were a kind of lottery.
Cards, betting all on the computer.
We opened a casino called 'Cuckoo' and
began bootlegging whiskey through it.
That whiskey guaranteed one thing
it would kill 2 out of 10 who drank it.
I started butt-fucking Isa
when 20% of workers went on strike.
And also told Bunty to fuck up Parulkar.
Action.
Bring the phone to my ear.
Didn't smack hard enough?
- Took off his undies?
- No, boss.
Do some batting with the undies
off, and give him the phone.
Give him the phone.
Take off undies of this bastard.
How're you, Parulkar Sir?
I told you at that time
don't leave me alive.
Well...
this is like a slow ball of cricket.
Talk.
Isa...
... boss.
I want Gaitonde's gang to be dead.
I want them extinct from the Earth.
You tell me,
how can it be done?
My Gentleman plan hit bull's eye.
People got hospitalized due to drinking
bootleg whiskey, within a year.
And the factory faced protests.
Now Isa would surely
need to come to Kenya.
Everything was going well,
but I couldn't forget Bombay.
I used to call two people,
whenever I missed Bombay.
One was Jojo.
Father, bless me for I have sinned.
It's been 3 days since
my last confession.
Yes Jojo, go on.
Father, last night I tried again.
Why do you seek the end
so hungrily my child?
If I were seeking I would
have surely got it by now.
Did I get it?
Death is a coward's way out.
Living through your
guilt is true atonement.
And the second was Dilbagh
Singh who never picked my call.
While crossing the street, two
men on motorbikes approached us...
Hey, Dilbagh.
You served so much water to Gaitonde,
give some to this lady as well.
Parulkar got his promotion
and left him hanging.
Add 250 grams of onion,
50 grams of ginger.
How much?
It's ok Sir,
leave it, I don't need money from you
'cause you're the
friend of Gaitonde Sir.
The almighty
talks to us in stories.
Joining our stories, connecting them,
putting us in each other's life.
If he has hurt you,
perhaps it was only to save
someone else at that moment
in another part of the world,
escaped from an accident.
Longer ringtone,
it must be him. Don't pick it.
Sartaj!
I'll check it.
How was that?
Why did you take the call?
Go and finish your meal.
Why do you keep annoying us?
We don't want anything from you.
What is the grouse with all you fathers?
You saved my life, otherwise fucking
Parulkar would have killed me.
Look, I saved your life, 'cause
I thought they would kill you.
I go to the temple every week,
and at the very same time
I had to sit in front of you every
week, in the prison.
First I was like, "why I'm
here with this criminal,
instead of serving the Lord."
Do you need an apology from me?
Do you believe in God?
What?
No.
If God didn't exist,
how would humans get the
idea of an entity like God?
You only have
one option, now.
You must dedicate yourself to the God.
I told you I don't believe in God.
If not God, you must
have belief in human?
So, find anyone who
can guide you to God.
Who?
Any saint...
Any sage...
Any Guru...
Guru.
There are many.
So, there must be one for you.
Search one.
This is Anjali's diary.
We found it at Trivedi's house.
Sir, we've found these
numbers in Anjali's diary.
Put these numbers on
'permanent tracing'.
Yes, Sir.
Aham Brahmasmi. Welcome
Aham Brahmasmi.
Raise your hands up.
Please change your clothes here.
What's your work profile?
I've my own business.
Textiles.
What're your expectations?
I'm going through a divorce process.
I've heard this place
gives you inner peace.
My name is Batya Abelman.
I oversee this Ashram.
Pushkar told me
that you've come here seeking peace.
Yes.
My father used to tell me
that Guruji possessed a
great deal of tranquility.
His voice...
His words...
Are still with us.
How long have you been with Ashram?
It's been a very long time.
Now, it feels, it's been 4-5 life spans.
Then you must have witnessed the era
of 20 years before.
When the Ashram's
foundation was laid in Croatia.
It was a great time.
My father used to tell me
that rich businessmen and
famous leader visited Guruji.
Yes.
He would treat everybody the same.
Famous gangsters would visit as well?
That's what I've heard.
Guruji never sent anyone back.
So, has any mafia don ever reformed?
We don't reform people, Sartaj.
We just give them perspective.
I want to ask you.
What do we learn from Gilgamesh?
We learn
that the pursuit of power
and control
is as futile as the
pursuit for immortality.
We learn
to enjoy
the gift
of life.
Ther's a herbal tea placed next to you.
For this solitude exercise
drink the tea.
Close your eyes.
Let the energy seep in.
Lie back on your meditation mats.
Stretch your legs
feel comfortable.
And relax.
Aham Brahmasmi
You take too much stress, Sir.
Son...
Don't be ashamed.
You tried your best.
What is life if not an exercise in...
in replenishing losses?
Loss is the essence of living.
The elixir.
When everything
starts seeming meaningless
only then the desire...
Who's this?
A Guru.
I met him in jail, just like you.
Your Hindi is broken,
and his is too complex.
I'm learning Hindi.
You have such huge contacts.
So, can you help me to
get an... Indian Passport?
Why do you want to go to India?
To do modeling.
With this mushroom nose?
Doctor will change it.
Well, I can't go to India.
Will you forget me when
you'll become a model?
Will you teach me how to kiss?
Boss.
Trivedi is here.
And Isa has come to Nairobi.
Will learn some other time.
- Thank you.
- What's up Trivedi?
You get high on milk?
Much more than this.
Guruji says
that no other drink gets
you more high than milk.
Why does everything you say
revolve around that fucking Guru?
Because Guru solves the riddles of life.
Dilbag Singh had also
told me to find a Guru.
What will I get by finding a guru?
You'll get answers,
for each and every question.
How does he know all the answers?
He has spent years in austerity.
With a pure mind,
and distinct thinking.
There's not an iota of darkness in him.
I suggest, for you also
to believe in Guruji.
Because in the future,
he's going to be our guiding light.
Should I have him speak to you?
Huh?
Aham Brahmasmi.
Yeah, yeah.
How are you Ganesh?
You said I'd stay alive, hence I am.
Trivedi keeps me
updated with your progress.
But you still have
various tests to face.
Here's a test,
Trivedi told me you've all the
answers so I made this call.
So you're testing me, Ganesh?
Go ahead.
I've had something chocking
my throat for years.
I'm going to remove it tomorrow.
You tell me, will I be able to do it?
No, you won't.
Why?
There's someone with you
who doesn't want it to happen.
Who?
The one who is your
poison, and your elixir, both.
The one who's also impressed
and worried with your energy.
There's no need for such details,
just give me name,
I'll finish him first.
There's a differences in telling
future and sensing future, Ganesh.
I don't get what he's saying, you try.
Greetings Guruji.
Yes, Trivedi.
He wanted to talk to you,
that's why I called you.
If you allow me
I'll hang up the call.
It's okay.
Yes boss, there's one more car,
coming to the airport.
Keep following them.
Give me a signal as
they reach the tarmac.
Hey, cover their mouths
with cloth. Gag them.
Are you afraid?
Huh?
Do you remember everything?
Yes.
Don't be nervous.
Give a hot towel to that motherfucker
as he enters the plane.
He'll put it on the face,
and get unconscious.
Listen, get out of here.
What did you get by screwing me over?
I won't stop until I open up his skull.
Save him if you can.
There was an attack on the Indian
Embassy in Tanzania, last month.
The one behind it,
is more dangerous than Isa.
He wants to wipe
India off the world map!
Then let him.
India isn't my responsibility.
I just want to fuck up Isa.
Bombay will also suffer with India.
And I'm sure, that matters to you.
The way to this man is through Isa.
And this man is as important
to me as Isa is to you.
We've checked
with our Russian resources.
The Pakistanis have
moved the spent nuclear fuel
that was stolen from Ukraine
and docked at the Malindi port in Kenya.
What was the quantity?
Six-hundred kilos.
We will wait for 600kg to
come in? No red flags, nothing?
Any word from Beagle?
We've put a collar, but he's
still not started barking.
- Sir, we can't wait more.
- I agree.
PMO is also very concerned.
What about those
Hizbuddin boys? Any word?
We're checking their
backgrounds. They'll talk.
When?
Sir, we're trying a different
route. We'll let you know.
- What now inspector?
- Who's Wilson?
Ever heard this name?
He's the brother of that Hizbuddin guy.
His name is Saad.
Hasn't been home for a week.
How old is he?
Twenty-one.
The locals here are saying
the cops picked him up.
Was he brawling?
I asked the PI here. He said
he did'nt get any report here.
But I've told him to find out.
I'll drive, Sir.
Zoya, come here quickly.
Their people are gunning
down our soldiers every single day.
I want to know.
And India wants to know that why has
a Pakistani woman been lying to us
- for 20 whole years.
- Fucking shit.
Why did you leak it?
I told you that I've
nothing else to say.
You must have.
Gaitonde's friends, family or enemy?
Anyone of that time?
No.
No? And Wilson?
Who's this Wilson?
When you remember something,
I'll tell you a solution
to this problem.
Look, Awaiz.
Just tell me who were
you printing this for.
Hmm?
Just tell me.
Speak.
Start speaking.
Start speaking. Start it!
Start, just speak!
Speak, speak, Man.
Majid! Majid!
- Wait a second.
- Enough. Majid!
Enough.
Come on.
Drink it.
Your brother's missing.
His name is Saad, right?
You people must have picked him.
He's just a kid.
He was never involved
in any wrong thing.
When was the last time you met him?
It's been 10 days.
And you didn't file any report
because if the police had come,
they would find
this bullshit in your press?
We're looking for him in every circle.
We'll find out in the next 4-5 hours.
But before this,
tell me, have you ever met him?
Don't be afraid.
He's Shahid Khan.
I saw his face on Facebook.
He doesn't live in India.
He has firm belief
that one day Gazwa-e-Hind will happen.
The time for that has come.
I don't know anything else.
I was assigned to
deliver all the papers to Ghazala
Bibi's home in Kamathipura.
Ghazala Bibi?
Nasreen had been come to me
2 years ago from Hyderabad.
She learnt the business quickly but...
She got involved 'cause
a bastard client influenced her.
- Which client?
- I don't know, Sir.
She used to go for months.
She went this time as well.
Don't know what disease she picked.
Where's Nasreen now?
In the beginning it seemed like STD.
But its growing so fast....
we haven't received the
medical report's yet
I cant say for certain, but it could
be some kind of nuclear radiation.
Hello.
Jojo.
Why'd you call?
They screwed me up.
Who did?
Just like you've one Jesus in
your life, I also have mine.
But mine is a false god
and a demon, always escapes.
He has good luck.
If I get his horoscope, I'd
know what time to kill him.
The ones who can get early
deaths are very fortunate.
My life-line is on a never ending track.
You talk about death as if you
have a doctorate in all this.
Have you ever seen death, face to face?
Not as much as you.
But whenever I have, I've
always stood firm against it.
Tried embracing it as well, but
again luck wasn't on my side.
Wish I could have guts like you.
I would trick death
into taking me with it.
You can't die until we meet.
I swear I'm dying to meet you.
There's no one in
the world I dial just like that.
Why didn't you meet
when I was in Bombay?
Not Bombay, it's Mumbai.
Hey motherfucker,
even if I call you Kuckoo,
Momo you won't remain Jojo?
Don't call me a motherfucker.
This is the second
time you called me that,
this is my last warning to you.
Do you have any problem with this word?
Hey you faggot, I told you, you
can abuse me with whatever words
but don't use this
word nor say with love.
Understand?
Speak.
I forgot what I had to say.
Okay. Bye then.
Bye.
Tell me.
How did he find out...
that Ma'am will betray me?
Did you say something?
I had told you.
He has all the answers.
But how? Only he can tell.
Do you wanna meet Guruji?
Huh?
Wanna meet?
Time is radioactive.
It decays.
And it stays forever.
It is a circle.
And this circle of time is
divided into four eras.
4 Yugas.
Satya Yuga.
Treta Yuga,
Dwapara Yuga,
and Kali Yuga.
The first one is Satya Yuga.
The Yuga of truth.
The Yuga of purity.
And you know that
purity is like cocaine...
means high class cocaine.
You know how Satya Yuga ended?
Sexual jealousy.
Your orgasm.
Your orgasm is the
biggest force inside you.
If you control it.
You win.
There was something in that guy.
He was aware of the past and future.
And then the third one.
Dwapara Yuga.
Power and narcissism
fuck each other
and give birth
to the thing that we all love.
Materialism.
He said man is fucking
himself because of greed and lust.
And entered in
Kali Yuga from Satya Yuga.
A time when war is business.
Religion is business.
Love is business.
Music is business.
And now, there's only one way
to get out from this Kali Yuga.
If you stop eating Vitamin
C what will happen to you?
Scurvy.
Yes, scurvy, someone said it.
And after that
your oldest wounds, childhood wounds
will come back.
Because nothing goes away.
Our oldest memories
our deepest joys
everything is inside us.
We just have to control our diet.
Our spiritual emotional diet...
... and we'll find Satya Yuga again.
Together.
That's how he became my third father.
He told me that to keep
our digestive system in order,
all the poisons we put in our stomach,
soul, heart, and blood,
it is essential
to keep track and know of.
It's a must that we're aware of it.
Otherwise we'll never know which poison
might turn into cancer and fuck us up.
He said that we all have
our universe in our asses.
- Because...
- Aham Brahmasmi.