WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
They're twin brothers.
Maalam is a decent
man. He loved me a lot.
But, Aalam...
... was a demon.
Where did you go with them?
Africa!
America!
I don't know where they
picked up the goods from.
What goods?
They smuggled things.
What they brought
with them, that time...
... I have no idea.
They threw acid on my skin,
it was burning.
The fuckers didn't wear protection.
Did those two get ill as well?
Or just you?
Nasreen?
Where was that stuff delivered?
We're trying to track
down their boat, Jibril.
How?
Well, this can detect
radio active material
for about a 100 meters.
It's .25 microsieverts not significant.
What we need is just one trail,
then we can follow it.
- Hello.
- Mohit, this side.
Yes, Mohit. Speak.
Rohit isn't going to school.
He goes somewhere, but
we don't know where.
In the middle he disappeared for 2 days.
Mother's really worried.
Tell Mother not to
worry. I'll talk to him.
Sir, don't tell mom I had called.
Okay, I won't tell her.
Hello.
Are your sure they were twins?
Okay, we're coming.
The local PI called.
He's got something for us.
Please come, Sir.
Tell Sir about whatever
you were just saying.
Sir, all I know is that they were ill.
That's all I know.
Lots of sailors come here.
Some with girls, some with booze...
Forget about the booze.
This is it.
Maalam Ali.
This is just only the boat number.
Couldn't you get a proper ID?
Don't you know, Adhaar Card
is compulsory for booking?
In future, for sure, Sir.
Did you ever speak to them?
They called for traditional
Indian food, curry and rice.
- And?
- And...
They used to order medicines.
They did call for
medicines every 2-3 days.
Are you getting any
big orders now-a-days?
For vomiting? Or burns?
You know interconnected network?
The one who invented it
belonged to the Satya Yuga .
He gave it to the world for free.
I mean to say, it's the first
indication that Satya Yuga will return.
That will end individuality
and a connected consciousness
will return back.
You must learn how to use internet.
Aham Brahmasmi.
You have the darkness
of fear inside you.
What fear? I don't fear anyone.
You exist today...
... but won't tomorrow.
That's the fear.
That nobody is going to remember you.
That fear.
Please have it.
What Gochi is this?
If you like this "Gochi"
then spread it in the world.
Ganesh.
Guruji gave me tea
that looked more like...
... a red soup.
Who knows what it was made
from and what was in it.
What Gochi did
Guruji fucking blew my mind away.
Forgive me, dad.
Bastard!
I confessed to the
crime you had committed.
And you left me alone here, to die!
You'll also suffer to death.
You'll face hell for
as long as you live.
You'll never find peace.
That time, it felt like a magic.
suddenly all the heavy weight
of hate poured out of me.
And everything felt so light.
From that day on, I started a new trade,
The Gochi trade.
It was made in Guruji's
Ashram in Dubrovnik.
And I would distribute
it, to all the Ashrams,
and the black markets,
all over the world.
According to Guruji, this was a
way of charity, as well as profit.
His words were'nt any
less affective than Gochi.
Gochi was the only business of mine
that Yadav Ma'am didn't control.
I always provided her information
and was able to keep her in dark.
And away from Guruji.
In 2001 I did business
worth Rupees 250 million.
Thay year Al Qaeda fucked America
in return for its' shenanigans..
Whatever one might say, Osama had guts.
In front of the whole world,
he chopped America's, not one...
... but Twin Dicks.
I'm not feeling this.
I'll take off your Sari?
No! The moon's come out,
he'll be here any minute.
Let it go. Let me take it
off. This doesn't excite me.
Hey, please.
Let me take it off.
Do what you want but this way,
it took me 2 hours to wear the Sari.
I would've rather
banged a hooker then...
Paid money and gotten whoever I wanted.
Did I invite you here
to come and love me?
Talk with respect. Do you understand?
Try to understand!
Once our bodies meet it kills the hunger
only then our souls will meet.
And I'm telling you the moon's
out; he'll be here any minute.
If that's how it is, then go to hell!
I don't want to do
anything like this with you.
And we both remain unsatisfied today.
I'll see.
And celebrate your ceremony
because it'll be your last one.
Once I've chopped off his neck,
you'll come running to marry me.
He's my husband.
Do you understand?
I told you I am a married woman.
Huh?
And talk to me with
respect, I'm not your whore.
Do you know who was
behind the Bombay Blasts?
It was Isa.
And who was behind Isa?
Pakistan.
ISI.
And do you know who
handled the whole operation?
Yeah, you had told me about some guy
Showed me the picture as well.
After the Bombay Blasts, this
'guy' has become very big.
He's earned a name.
So big, that he's got
the nerve to call his boss
the ISI chief, a coward, openly!
Sounds like a cool guy.
He's now set up his own
terror group in India,
It's called Hizbuddin.
His name is Shahid Khan.
Do I have to kill him
or abduct him for you?
Either will do.
I won't do it out of
love for this country.
I want 50 million shillings.
I want a Rolls-Royce.
Shahid Khan's in talks
with the Dubai underworld.
He wants money for Hizbuddin.
It's very difficult to get information
out of the Dubai underworld,
there's only one way.
You'll have to talk to Isa.
If you be just as nice to Isa
as you were when you
spoke about the Rolls Royce
then our job will be done.
What the fuck...
Hold on.
We're done now.
If I see you again...
I'll bury your ass
in the fucking ground,
I thought I closed her chapter.
But I had no idea
that she had me by the balls.
Go, go, go.
My whole business used to run on cash.
And Yadav Ma'am
ratted me out to the authorities
I started losing 50 to
100 million each day.
Any day now
they would just stick
up their hand up my ass
and even snatch away my last dime.
- Guruji?
- Yes.
What's the problem, Ganesh?
If I could know everything
beforehand, like you do.
there would be no trouble.
Give me all your problems.
This is my problem.
There was a demon... called Apasmara.
Who had
a very unique superpower.
He could control
anyone's memory.
But he had a weakness, also.
He used to crave for attention.
One day,
Apasmara
cast such a spell
on Goddess Parvati
that she had lost all her Godly powers.
Then Lord Shiva, in full of rage,
reached Apasmara's cave
and started his angry dance "Tandava".
The high resonance
of Lord Shiva's Damroo
made the veins of Apasmara's ears burst.
He fell at Lord Shiva's feet
and Nataraja stomped on his head.
Since then till today,
Nataraja is holding that position.
Apasmara was pissed that
despite being so powerful
nobody gave two hoots about him.
That's why he fucked with Lord Shiva.
And I was in a similar position!
For the first time in my
life I had earned so much cash
but nobody knew about me
neither in Bombay nor Mombasa.
I was stranded like a ghost of the sea.
I decided
I won't keep quiet like Apasmara.
Won't let the world forget
who Ganesh Gaitonde is.
Where's your boat?
Jibril?
Where did you deliver the goods?
Do you remember Nasreen?
She told us that Aalam loved her truly,
but Maalam was a rascal.
Its a lie.
So you're Maalam?
She was in the hospital for 12 days...
She was in such pain that
she was begging for death.
You'll also be in the same
condition in a few days time.
Allah's the greatest.
You brought the stuff for Ghazwa-e-Hind?
Tell me,
where has it been 'written'?
Have you even read the Hadith?
Yeah yeah... Dajjal.
Where it is? Who is he?
- Donald Trump is a Dajjal...
- Shut up, motherfucker!
Someone just said it
and you believed it?
Even you believed whatever 'they' said.
Motherfucker...
Look, what's this?
Do you know who this is?
Ibn-e-Qasim!
He had captured India,
a thousand years ago.
Ghazwa-e-Hind has already
happened a thousand years back.
They're taking you for a ride.
And the stuff you've brought here
will destroy the whole city.
Are you grasping anything, motherfucker?
That's good, then....
All the infidels will die.
Bastard.
Majid, stop it. What are you doing?
You're going to decide...
Relax. Calm down.
Just leave.
Why did you keep me, if
you had to kick me out.
Go ask Parulkar that.
Take a break. Go home.
So...
How's Operation Makhdoom going?
Rolling on, Sir.
Intelligence Bureau guys
don't usually like cops.
Yes, Sir.
Did they find Bhonsle?
We haven't been told anything yet, Sir.
Does one need to be told to find out?
Had heard that he's been kept
in some safe-house. But...
He's not talking.
Sir, I'll take your leave.
Listen, you will be attending
the marriage anniversary right?
Yes, Sir.
- Jai Hind, Sir.
- Jai Hind.
You want more? Do you?
- Aye, motherfucker.
- Easy. Easy.
Have you guys gone mad?
I've been telling you
constantly I don't know...
... I don't know anything
about anything nuclear...
You remember Patil
Sir's helicopter crash?
Nobody figured out who was behind it.
So... Are you threatening to kill me?
- I'm not threatening.
- Then?
Nobody will miss you if you disappear.
Sir,
Delhi.
Sir.
Jai Hind, Sir.
Sisterfucker...
No, Sir.
Sir, we can't let him go yet.
No...
Sir, media...
Media won't get to know. I promise.
All my boys are very smart, Sir.
We need this, Sir.
It's very serious, Sir. It's
part of Operation Makhdoom.
Yeah...
Fine, Sir.
But I need a...
... one hour with him, Sir.
Thank you, Sir. Jai Hind.
One hour.
Ma'am, what should I
state as the occupation?
Write anything you want.
Ma'am the yearly installments
need to paid for this.
- Who will be paying for that?
- Her lover.
The one screwing will
have to get screwed.
Ma'am do one thing.
Get this insurance
policy from someone else.
My girls go to all kinds of assholes.
In case they get a disease... or die...
Insurance is needed, right?
Fill it out.
Fill the form!
- Hello.
- Still alive?
I'm angry right now, we'll talk later.
Why act so pricey?
You won't be missed even if you die.
You are alive and tell me who cares?
Nobody even mentions
your name in Mumbai.
Don't talk hogwash.
All of Mumbai knows about Ganesh
Gaitonde and Kukoo's love story.
Ass-wipe, I told you I
haven't heard about it.
You will now, if you haven't before.
Decided...
I'm going to produce a movie.
Movie?
What movie?
Story about my life.
Kukoo... Kukoo...
I'll show you, motherfucker.
Hey!
I'm making a movie, motherfuckers.
Is Boss saying something?
Just nod your head.
Aye! Is Ram G Verma checking
the print of his film here?
Shubu...
It's Shivaang, Sir.
How's it sounding?
- Big fan, Sir.
- Idiot, I'm asking how's it sounding.
Good morning, Sir.
Are you going to shoot me?
You don't want to shoot me?
Aye motherfucker,
I've bought your movies tickets
in black. Why would I kill you?
Is it for real?
Motherfucker, do you want
to make another film or no?
Or should I end your biopic right here?
We bagged a big time
director Ram G Verma
to direct the movie.
Why's all this so green?
Green screen.
Yeah, but why?
Then how do I create India in Africa?
Boss, he's showing Africa as India...
India is not so green...
Fucking looks like the Aarey jungle.
He'll make this green into India later.
I wonder why do you work for him,
rather he should work for you.
What did he say?
I made a Gopalmath in Africa,
Zoya became Kukoo... And that dickhead,
Rajeev Sawla, became Gaitonde.
My dad was a beggar.
I did not like that.
He killed my mother.
Then I met Kukoo,
India's Audrey Hepburn.
Audrey Hepburn? Not Meryl Streep?
Meryl Streep... Julia Roberts...
Audrey Hepburn... She was everything...
Meryl Streep is Meryl Streep!
Five, six, seven, eight.
It'll be the expressions...
♪ Let the bottled up love ooze out... ♪
♪ Let it kiss the lips,
and slide down... ♪
And then the villain enters.
Isa!
I show him the colt...
... and take Kukoo away with
me from right under his nose.
Under the nose...
After showing the colt...
colt...
Ohh... that colt!
♪ Hey uptown girl ♪
♪ let those hips sway... ♪
Boss, I've written some kickass
lines, keeping you in mind.
"I'm the downtown don, and
you're the uptown girl..."
"Let's meet mid-way, hidden away..."
♪ I'm the downtown don,
and you're the uptown girl ♪
♪ Let's meet mid-way, hidden away ♪
♪ How you doin' girl ♪
You are the hero of the movie...
Isa is nothing compared to you...
He's not even the antagonist,
he's a stooge, a comedian...
♪ How you doin' girl ♪
I won't be coming.
Not even for me?
Precisely why I won't come.
That's fine.
I'll save you a seat.
Bombay's not safe for you, Ganesh.
Everyone told me not to
go for the movie premiere.
But I wanted to see people
go crazy seeing my story.
♪ How you doin' girl ♪
Nobody came, film folk,
my business folk,
faggoty politicians. None!
I'd put tonnes of action in the movie,
Even made Gaitonde die like
Amitabh Bachchan in the movies,
thinking it would make people emotional.
But people were laughing!
Guruji's story of Apasmara
hit me like a bullet.
The motherfucker had too big a
head, and that is why he had fallen.
I was also down and out.
Nobody remembered Ganesh
Gaitonde. Nobody feared him.
Even I was thinking...
"What does this dickhead
Ganesh Gaitonde want"?
It's the public's right to know...
that why do you keep a low profile
when it comes to your nationality.
- I am...
- Why have you consistently and vehemently
denied your involvement with
the gangster Ganesh Gaitonde,
- inspite of making a debut with his film.
- Exactly...
Tell me, how does your blood not boil?
Tell?
If someone breaks
into your home tomorrow
and raises their hand
against you, will you just
sit quietly or retaliate?
Our revered Holy Cow that
even our saints worship...
these butchers rip open her
stomach whenever they want.
But our brave-hearts avenge
by butchering those butchers...
... and continue to prove that
Maharashtrians are still alive!
Why are the North
Indians trying to become
the protectors of Hinduism?
Why aren't you going to school?
What if Mom finds out?
And what's this nonsense
have you come to listen?
These people first brainwash you,
then use you and then
leave you to die...
You did the same with Dad...
left him to die...
Aye, Rohit... Don't run your mouth.
Yeah?
Take this.
Some money...
... give this to Mom.
Don't want it.
I'm there for Mom and Mohit.
You moron. Sir, is
trying to help you out...
Kamble...
Rohit...
You look tense.
There is some guilt inside.
Let it come & rise.
Don't suppress it.
Don't counter instinct
with intelligence.
Easy to say...
Instinct has been around far longer,
and your instinct has brought you here.
Follow it.
What's in this?
Suppression will only
increase the darkness.
Let your fear rise.
'Letting go' is virtuous.
What's this?
He had gone with you, right?
And was walking on his own two feet.
What should I tell my kids?
What should I do now?
Hello?
I'm sending you the
location. Reach there.
Of what?
Hello?
Don't give him more than 5 minutes.
Poonam, that's Sartaj Singh.
Poonam, her daughter.
Let me know if you need anything.
Please come.
Mom,
the one I'd spoken to you about...
... he has come.
Ma'am,
when did you meet Ganesh
Gaitonde for the first time?
In Kenya.
Mom was deputed in the
Indian Embassy there.
What all did he do for you Ma'am?
She can't remember much.
Brain damage... and Scotoma...
So she can't see much either.
Half her vision is blurred
with random subconscious images.
- Why are you asking her these questions?
- Give her a chance to speak.
She might remember something.
Ma'am, Anjali...
How do you know Anjali Mathur?
Your name was in her diary.
Bloody, Mathur...
Bloody? Why?
Mr. Mathur, Anjali's
father, was Mom's colleague.
Mom...
It'll be a very difficult night
if she gets more disturbed.
You should leave now.
Shhh...
It's okay. It's okay.
Please. I'm sorry. Please leave.
It's all right.
Hello?
You broke my heart today.
I had told you I won't be coming.
I don't watch Amitabh Bachchan's movies,
Shahrukh Khan's or Salman
Khan's. Why would I watch yours?
You run a brothel, provide escorts...
... and watching a simple
movie is sin for you?
I've committed lots of sins.
I've committed tons of sins.
But ever since this pilgrimage started,
killing myself has also become a sin.
How bad a sin did you commit that
you needed to go on a pilgrimage?
We don't call it pilgrimage...
Whatever they call it, You tell me
your sins, and I'll tell you mine.
Everyone knows about yours...
Everybody knows what?
Your movie.
Your big sin.
Your biggest sin. The one you produced.
Why do you speak like that?
Because you wanted to be a hero...
which you are not.
You are Gaitonde.
And Gaitonde's a villain.
And villains don't
dance... which you did.
If you hadn't done that,
your movie would've
been successful for sure.
No fucking body would
have forgotten Gaitonde,
but on screen you turned a
normal guy into a dickhead.
Why don't you actually die for real?
Why don't you come and kill me?
I'll be indebted to you even as a ghost.
- Jojo.
- Yeah?
I'm coming.
Where?
I'm... I'm coming.
Hey, Gaitonde, I... I was...
Turn the car around.
But boss, the airport's this way.
- Boss, it's not safe.
- Motherfucker, head to Bandra.
Boss...
Fucking Hell. Here come our fans.
Drive faster.
Bunty. Take down a number.
Take down a number.
+254202609393.
Call this number and inform them.
- Okay.
- Stop the car.
Hello?
I'm calling from Bombay.
Ganesh Gaitonde has been
picked up by Parulkar.
Are you getting what I'm saying?
I should've known I would run into you.
My ass had been fucking
twitching since morning.
My business,
has become massive now, Parulkar.
Mine as well.
I've stopped playing with bats.
You're... making a
mistake again, Parulkar.
I won't make a mistake again.
Run, bastard.
Run!
- Turn him over.
- Come on.
Parulkar... My business
has crossed borders...
Just ask. Just ask for
whatever you want. Parulkar!
Hello?
The enquiry on the Nusrat
Wahaab Encounter Case
is quite heated.
If the media were to get
your phone call recordings,
the Chief Minister might not like it.
Who's this?
Save my number as Mother India.
Let Gaitonde go.
He won't come back to Mumbai.
Give the phone to him.
Leave him.
I'm doing this out of patriotism,
you should do it for survival...
What?
Please make sure you find the evidence.
Check every corner, every nook....
Found anything?
There are no fingerprints,
Sir. There's nothing missing.
Somebody was searching
for something, Sir.
Any information from Maalam & Aalam?
Hmm. They haven't said anything yet.
What if we separate the two?
Sir, Maalam is scared of his brother.
He won't cut in on what
he's been taught by Aalam.
And Aalam will take
some time to trust us.
They'll talk only when
they are terrified...
And they'll be terrified
only when they are alone.
Sir?
Who do you want to take out?
Sir, give us some time. They'll speak.
If we had time we wouldn't
be going through this shit.
Brother, Aalam?
Where's Aalam?
Brother, Aalam...
Huh?
Aalam & Nasreen...
They both left.
You want to get cured, right?
We've been at sea for years now...
Brought lots of goods for Shahid.
This...
... was the last delivery.
Maalam,
handle the boat. I'm going to sleep.
It was a long one...
that's why we took Nasreen along.
Picked up the stuff
from a ship in Malindi...
Not here.
Easy.
Keep it here.
We woke up one morning...
... and she started vomiting.
Those guys didn't make the full payment.
We delivered half the goods in Mandvi
- and hid the boat.
- Where?