WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
DISCLAIMER - This series is a work
of fiction and is based on the novel
titled "Sacred Games" authored
by Vikram Chandra in 2006.
promote, encourage and support
any action or relationship
displayed between the
characters of this series.
Resemblance of any character of
this series to any persons, places,
real events, linguistic groups,
political parties, communities,
religions or sects is purely
coincidental and unintentional.
Shot!
pitch me the same way, perfect.
One more!
Catch it! Catch it, catch it!
Yes! We got him!
It's above the waist, no ball.
Tell 'em it's a 'No-ball'.
No-ball!
How is it a no-ball?
It was above the waist...
Don't cheat.
- Umpire said it's above the waist.
- It was below the waist...
- Cheating?
- You know the rules? Stay in your limits.
Take him away or I'll
bury him right here.
You got quite a mouth, Aurangzeb.
Get out of here.
Muslim Faggot.
- Motherfucker.
- Hey...
Do you wanna fight you, bastard?
Are you crazy, Saad? Get out of here.
Hey Balu... Vijya..!
What happened? Aye, bring the car out.
Let's go! Get out of here.
Kushal, he's bleeding a lot.
This has become a country of foreigners
and there is no room
for Hindus in Hindustan.
Sir, historically,
first the Moghuls came when we
were fighting amongst ourselves.
Then the Britishers came, we
got divided into class and caste.
We got another opportunity
during the Partition,
but we chose non-violent protests!
Look at 'them', they've
been at it for 2000 years
and we are stuck electing governments
to give us better petrol prices.
- Fools of the highest ord...
- 1400 years.
Huh?
Islam has existed for
1400 years, not 2000.
What are you here for?
Do you know someone by the name of Saad?
The one who comes to play cricket?
Did something happen last week?
He's a crappy pitcher.
I hit 'em all out of the park.
You know what he did?
He bust open Ramesh's head.
- Blood was flowing out like Niagara Falls.
- Then?
- Then we took Ramesh to the hospital.
- And Saad?
- He must have run away.
- Have anyone's number from his team?
Thanks Kushal.
Sir, why are you
messing around with them?
Keep an eye on him.
Motherfucker, what have you done?
Speak.
Speak!
Say it, motherfucker.
Say it, motherfucker. Say it.
Say it. Say it.
Motherfucker.
- Let's deal.
- I know you want a deal, cunt.
Did your boss not teach you
to respect Sir Isa?
You want a deal? Show me your loyalty.
Bring forth your hand...
Prove your loyalty. Do
it or get out of here.
Remember the taste.
This is exactly what Shahid
also doesn't understand.
It's okay to have enemies,
but one must learn to respect the enemy.
Let me get rid of Shahid.
That'll end all problems.
Nope.
I know he's an idiot,
but idiots can come in handy as well.
Fifty million rupees.
Millions won't do.
I want to go to Jerusalem,
see the Qubbat As-Sakhrah.
And obviously I can't do
that on a Pakistani passport.
So, go to your owner, wag your tail
and get me an Indian
diplomatic passport.
It'll be done.
I'll take off.
Yes, you may leave.
"I'm the downtown don"
was a big mistake on my part...
Just need all your blessings now...
Bunty, that motherfucker
had become a poet...
And Zoya, an actress.
And I had become Ms. Yadav's
pet dog, who had to lick asses
Isa's or any other Sheikhs
that was served to me.
South.
Public.
In whose ass should
I shove up this info?
This guy always gives
useless information.
Where to?
Bombay.
It's my birthday tomorrow.
I have a shoot.
I'll call up Bunty.
He'll get the director to call in sick.
Listen, there's a party.
Aditya Johar will also be therel.
Your Hero will be there as well.
Yes, he's helping me out.
Screwing is 'helping' now, is it?
Ladies and gentleman I present to you
the voice of the evening...
♪ What you've lost won't be found ♪
♪ The wish for flight
is now caged-bound ♪
♪ The lips laugh at the crying heart ♪
♪ The wanderer now won't come around ♪
♪ Won't come... ♪
♪ Won't come around ♪
This was my most
expensive birthday party
and also the shittiest.
Even amongst a crowd I felt lonely.
♪ The body, tattooed by your scars ♪
♪ Like the night sky
blooming with stars ♪
♪ Walked through the flames... ♪
I would keep thinking
why did I meet Isa?
Miss Yadav had me pressed
against the wall in my own house.
♪ The wanderer now won't come around ♪
♪ Won't come around ♪
♪ Won't come around... ♪
Aham Brahmasmi, Ganesh.
Aham Brahmasmi, Guruji.
You have my blessings
on your birthday, Ganesh
I know you're in a dilemma.
This story will help you understand.
During the war of the worlds
between the Gods and Demons,
there was a time when
the demons were dominant.
So, the Gods sent an
innocent looking boy,
Kacha, into the Demons'
settlement as a spy.
Shukracharya - the Demons' Guru
knew the secret of Mrit Sanjeevni.
Mrit Sanjeevni was an elixir
that granted immortality
it could bring a dead
person back to life.
And as time went on,
Devyani... Shukracharya's
daughter fell in love with Kacha.
The Demons' got apprehensive.
They did not want the secret
of their most powerful weapon
to reach the Gods.
Hence, the Demons killed Kacha.
Seeing Devyani in despair,
Shukracharya used Mrit Sanjeevni to...
bring Kacha back to life.
Devyani was elated,
And Kacha received assurance
that he could always escape death.
Then?
The rest of the story will follow later.
You still have many births
to go through, Ganesh.
For now, just understand
that to conquer death one
needs to die several times.
How?
How can I go to my next birth?
It is not so easy, Ganesh.
Not strength... sacrifice is required.
- I'll do it.
- Sacrifice?
What's the first step?
The tube you found is
definitely an initiator
to generate neutrons
for the fission reaction.
North Korea has been working on
an assembled fishing
device for some time.
And I think
they're now selling the
design in the black market.
But this design doesn't look like
it needs too many of these tubes.
Not exactly, even 2 or 3 would
do the job of initiating the bomb.
The other tubes just work as boosters.
How many tubes do you
estimate they have?
These ordinary looking
tubes that you see here
could be the biggest
weapon to enter India.
Our lab reports indicate that
they contain lithium deuteride.
This could be boosters
for a fission bomb.
Maalam informed us
there are 10 such tubes.
And we have retrieved five of them.
We believe that they will want
all of them for maximum impact
We have also unlocked Aalam's laptop
and we found a dark net chat room
that the Hizbuddin was
using to communicate.
Rama is working on deciphering
these chats even as we speak.
Fateh... Victory.
What's this, Sir?
16,7,17.
16th July?
Today's the 8th.
From what we have decoded,
16th of July could be D-Day.
We need to scan every
corner of the city.
Follow the nuclear fuel
Coordinate with all check-points.
Yes, Sir.
Any phone numbers obtained
from Anjali's diary
been activated?
Not yet, Sir. But we've got Shahid Khan
and his main man Haroon's voice samples.
- What did we get from the chats, Rama?
- We're analyzing it, Sir.
Analyzing is not enough,
participate in it.
Gain their trust. This is
the best chance we all have.
Get us a meeting with Shahid Khan.
Hey! Get up!
Have a seat, Sir.
He told me over the phone.
Sir, the truck belonged
to Gujarat or Maharashtra?
Gujarat, it had come from Kutch.
Sir, thousands of trucks come.
And you check all of them, isn't it?
Four chatroom histories
have opened up so far.
What are they speaking
about in this chat?
We found some information on Saad.
His friends told us he brawled
during the cricket match.
But no one knows where
he went afterwards.
But we'll find out soon.
Trust us.
Now tell us what this is.
This is not like Whatsapp chat.
Each person has limited
access to information
whatever is designated to them.
What's this 'Girl 6' speaking about?
Who is this?
Is this Shahid Khan?
Yeah.
Some stuff is missing.
The person with the laptop is saying
the stuff won't be
given without the money.
Shahid Khan's replied that
the money has been stolen
and is asking for cooperation.
Search more. What's been
written about the money?
You can't see old
messages by scrolling up.
Will we find something by
typing in the search box?
Yes.
Yes, Sartaj.
Markand Sir, how much money
was found from Jojo's home?
Why?
Please tell me, Sir.
Rupees 900.8 million.
Please tell me the exact number, Sir.
Rs. 908,676,000.
- But what are you doing?
- I'll tell you soon, Sir.
It's working.
What's written here?
He's praising a delivery that
was made on the 10th of June.
Rama, write "We are ready to
give the material for 25,000,000."
Let's negotiate with Shahid Khan.
But wouldn't they get suspicious
if we suddenly change what we're saying.
No, he is afraid. He'll definitely meet.
Oh!
Rama, we're running out of time.
Sir, Can I get you anything Tea, Coffee?
Take out the list for 10th June.
Huh?
Is there a problem, Sir?
Bring the CCTV footage.
Sir, the thing is...
I'll tell you...
- Take him along.
- Sir, I'll explain...
- One second, let me talk to him...
- Get up.
Sir.
Sir, will you have
some? It's local sweet.
No, thank you. Got something yet?
No, Sir. No response yet.
You joined after 26/11?
Yeah,
Joseph Sir had brought me in.
At the time, it would
poison me on the inside.
I would feel angry and
wanted to do something.
And now?
Now I'm used to it.
There's a lot of stress,
but it's fun.
And you?
I don't know.
These days, I'm unable to
understand what am I suppose to feel
- Got any response?
- No response, Sir.
Next time please consult somebody
before you send out
these random messages.
Where were you?
Should've prayed to Allah to
give your men some sense as well.
Please vent somewhere else.
All of us are just as stressed.
- What's your stress?
- What's your problem?
- Your work.
- We are working.
Should I call Parulkar?
Sir please! Move back!
Majid is doing his work, Sir.
Sir... Sir...
response is here.
Password protected...
Can we get it out of Maalam?
He doesn't know anything about
computers. Aalam used to handle it all.
Rama, what do you think?
It's risky to try a hack right now.
If we make a mistake, it will alert them
and we would loose our only chance.
You're home early today.
Half the people just use me,
and the other half doubt me.
They'll take me off this case.
They'll be foolish to do that.
Saw any houses today? Like anything?
Mum & Dad also must be having a
hard time in this small apartment.
If we end up liking an apartment,
its housing society doesn't
end up liking our name.
Today, even Mahesh gave up,
saying he's shown us all the flats.
Told me to select a flat in a
society which allows Muslims.
Otherwise the one in Dahanu...
Yeah,
Have the Muslims stay in a place
where even electricity has'nt reached.
I made a mistake by asking
Dad to move to Mumbai.
He's quite an influential politician.
Congratulations, Sir.
- Thanks.
- Arshia.
Hi, how are you?
Sir...
Three weeks ago some
goods had reached Mandvi.
Someone high up made a
call and let it bypass
the transportation-taxation department.
Who do you think that could be?
You just got here?
- Sir.
- There's a sweets counter.
Quite good. Try it.
Go!
Hello, Sir.
Hey Megha. How are you?
- Congratulations.
- Long time. You're looking gorgeous.
- Thank you.
- Come join us.
- That's Umesh.
- Hi Umesh.
One more please.
Thank you for coming.
Yeah!
- Megha.
- Hi.
I just heard the news. Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'll just be back in a bit. Wait for me.
Yes...
When's the wedding?
Next month.
Why all of a sudden?
Sartaj let's talk later.
You've known him for six months.
- Please, let's talk later.
- Is someone pressurizing you?
There's no pressure Sartaj.
I'm happy.
Please don't ruin it.
How does he manage to keep you happy?
I couldn't learn in years.
And in six months, he...
Will he teach me?
Should I ask him?
How to... keep Megha happy...
I'm pregnant.
Hello Sartaj.
How are you?
She had a problem with me drinking.
I was always proper,
but she would continue to
fuss over some petty arguments
we had in the past. She
used to say everyday,
"Quit drinking, it is not good for you."
She never treated me as
an equal in our marriage.
She was the doctor,
and I was the patient.
I was blamed as the reason
for all our problems.
She was the best thing that
happened to me, but I...
I was just a husband for her.
Sartaj, she has a right
to take her decisions.
When did I oppose that?
Yes, but you're feeling betrayed.
You hardly know anything about me.
I leave the lights on,
when I leave in the morning
Just so that I can feel like
there's someone else when I return.
Someone staying with me in the house
This isn't about loneliness...
but about self-worth, Sartaj.
So it's all my fault?
Self-worth isn't one's fault,
but the entire universe
comes together to
make you feel that way.
And how do you know that?
Do you want to go deeper?
Don't take it, Sartaj.
I am telling you, don't take it.
This Gochi is freaky.
Once its caught you, you'll
never be able to shake it off.
I'm pregnant.
When did you find out?
What's the point of this?
And we had mutually decided
that we won't have a child.
Didn't we?
- Didn't we Sartaj?
- Yes, we did.
- Because you didn't want to.
- Yes, I didn't want to.
My choice has no importance?
That's why I got the abortion done.
It was you who kept harping about
the lack of space on this planet...
Yeah, but we also ended
up fine... In this city.
And are we fine?
Are we fine, Sartaj?
I feel alone.
I have become tired of myself.
When my boys ask for instructions,
I'm slowly dying on the inside.
I know what to do.
But why
I'm lost.
Ganesh, it's the curse of being God...
I am no God.
I'm just running away.
From?
I don't know from whom?
Father, What are you doing Father?
I was weak, that's
why you became this...
It's not your fault. It's
all my fault forgive me.
Ganesh... forgive me.
Ganesh! Ganesh!
Ganesh! Ganesh... forgive me.
I was born a conflict, Sartaj.
My mother was Palestinian,
and my father was a Jewish.
We started Living in Paris.
Life was a midsummer night's dream...
Hectic, crazy, fun...
The first Intifada happened
and more than a 1000
Palestinians were killed.
And my mom started
feeling like a coward.
Living away from Palestine while
her friends were facing the bullets.
She left me this letter and
went back to her revolution.
I was 14.
She was 38.
She died the next year.
It means: Follow your instinct.
For a 14 year old
with no mother and a
traveling father that meant...
... sex...
... drugs...
and bad relationships with
equally destructive men.
And I took it all because
I had no self-worth.
You don't know, Sartaj,
how empty you really are
until someone knocks you down.
My father used to say...
God is in every particle,
God is everywhere.
Just came in my mind.
Nothing 'just' comes in the mind.
I used to think...
there's no one weaker than my dad.
He had nothing.
He was happy accepting
his life as God's pube...
But I turned out to be
even weaker than him.
I'm not going to remain weak.
What do I have to do?
Ganesh you possess a dynamic quality
Great energy...
However, energy leads
to self-doubt as well...
you'll have to sacrifice self-doubt.
Do you remember the story of Katch.
Ganesh, to conquer death one
needs to die several times.
Guruji said I would be born again
If I chose the right
path at the right time.
Okay.
I've organized a Dastangoi
event in Dubai.
Shahid might come.
This is a tale of Muhammad bin Qasim.
Muhammad bin Qasim
the most iconic personalities
in Islamic history.
According to Hindustan, Muhammad
bin Qasim is a marauder...
A tyrant, who because
of his personal ambition
and religious doctrine
attacked Hindustan,
massacred its people and
used violence to spread
Islam through the land.
But in Pakistan, countless
people consider Muhammad bin Qasim
to be their community's
supreme leader...
And the Nation's founder.
Muhammad Bin Qasim
will unmistakably hold
utmost importance in Pakistan.
He was a warrior who conquered Sindh
and made it an Islamic caliphate.
At the age of 17, he captured Sindh
by killing King Dahir...
And informed the world
that an Islamic warrior can go to
any lengths to fulfill his duty.
The masters have taught
us to take the sword
And use it for the
revolution of our community...
Motherfucker, stop digging your
nose so much. You're in Dubai.
If oil springs up, the Sheikhs
will keep you here. Faggot.
Awesome!
And now a comical saga
of the king of fruits - The Mango!
Its nectar is sweeter than the
sweetest honey from the heavens.
The allure is so strong that even
a cripple could climb its
way up a tree to taste it.
Awesome!
This fruit is the result
of a lover's devotion.
Every story reaches a crossroads
from where it could go anywhere
that junction had arrived in mine.
I had the remote control, not
of the bomb but of my future.
If I killed Shahid Khan,
I would live a happy life
but would become Miss Yadav's slave.
If I spared him, life would
be like Guruji spoke about
sacrifice,
rebirth,
God.
In that moment I changed
many destinies, Sardarji.
Shahid Khan's, yours,
and my city, Bombay's...
What happened?
Let's go.
- Miss Yadav...
- Let's go.
The next night, I uprooted
myself from Kenya...
and from the crusty life I was living.
Harsha.
Let's go.
Harsha,
our airplane is waiting for us.
Come.
Harsha!
Mathur, can you stop it please?
- I was making coffee.
- It's irritating me a lot.
I think you should stop
fixating about Gaitonde.
I don't give a fuck about Gaitonde.
I've been after Shahid
Khan for the past 11 years.
Gaitonde's my asset and I
know how to keep him in-check.
You wait and watch.
- Ma'am, there is a call for you.
- Thank you.
Hello?
Is this Jamila?
One second please.
Who's this?
You want Gaitonde off your back?
Brother,
Bunty's sent something to cheer
you up. It's in the bedroom.
Surprise.
You don't think of me these
days. So I came myself.
Why did you come here?
- What do you mean?
- Did you bring her here?
No... Bunty sent her.
Shut the fuck up.
Start packing. We have to leave tonight.
Miss Yadav gave you a call, right?
You told her the location of this place?
We got to pack.
Pack?
If boss said we got to
pack, then we got to pack.
Reiko,
light off.
It was all Miss Yadav. I was scared.
His father's a film producer
and promised me a film.
I just did what everyone else does.
Everyday I think you'll
send Bunty to kill me.
I'm sorry. I'll speak to her.
She'll agree. Please don't be angry.
Don't be angry! Don't be angry!
With my cover blown,
and no place to run.
I found myself stranded
at sea once again
but this time...
I wasn't running anywhere.
I had killed the coward inside me.
I'm not coming with you guys.
My sacrifice earned me my new home,
with my third father.
It felt as though I was within
the beating heart of a storm.
Enjoying tranquility, while
it raged, on the outside.
Yeah, Kamble, speak.
Sir, the truck has been found.
It was carrying the goods.
But the license plate seems
fake. No registration papers...
Send me a picture.
You've worked extensively
on the Shahid Khan case.
He's an ISI spy.
He was involved with the
ISI and in the 1993 blasts.
Did he have any links with Gaitonde?
They were both active at the same time.
He's going to be attacking India.
Gaitonde let him go...
Why ma'am?
Please try to remember.
Nuclear fuel was brought
from Malindi to Mandvi,
and then sent to Mumbai.
We found this truck.
Traces of radiation have been found
on it. What is Shahid Khan's plan?
We need a password to reach him.
Please help us ma'am. Please.
Shahid Khan was crazy
about colonial history.
He would do everything
according to that.
He came on Gabriel.
Jibril!
The King of Calicut refused.
Ma'am... Shahid Khan.
I told you, Vasco Da Gama came
to India in 1498 to capture it.
There was a vendor
from Mandvi...
who dealt in indigo...
Kanji Maalam.
Gabriel...
Vasco Da Gama...
Maalam...
The first attempt at capturing India...
Spain and Portugal divided
up the world in two parts.
Both were obsessed with
discovering and capturing India.
The Spanish headed west,
thinking they'll come around to India.
The Portuguese lost their way.
But then they found a Gujarati
trader on the Malindi port in Kenya.
Maalam, a resident of Mandvi.
And they reached here in 1498,
on a ship called Gabriel,
from Malindi, with Maalam.
Maalam.
Vasco Da Gama?
One second, one second...
We've exhausted all our chances.
We only have one try left.
Correct password.
Sir, a number has come.