WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
DISCLAIMER - This series is a work
of fiction and is based on the novel
titled "Sacred Games" authored
by Vikram Chandra in 2006.
promote, encourage and support
any action or relationship
displayed between the
characters of this series.
Resemblance of any character of
this series to any persons, places,
real events, linguistic groups,
political parties, communities,
religions or sects is purely
coincidental and unintentional.
As-salam alaykum Brother. Aalam here.
Okay.
Alaikum-asalaam.
Brother. Aalam here.
Yeah.
Brother, where should
we bring the Kalimiri?
Military.
How many kilograms?
He hung up.
Boss...
Brother. Aalam here.
Where should we bring the Kalimiri?
Military.
How many kilograms?
By 'Military' he means Military Cafe.
He'll reveal the rest
of the details later.
Good Job. Beautiful.
Made Taj Mahal out of it.
Take this.
Let me know if you need more.
We'll get it sent to your homes.
It's said that Shahjahan
desired to make another Taj Mahal
in front of the existing one.
Using black marble.
But he couldn't get it made...
Because the workers'
hands had been cut off.
Sometimes they ought to be cut.
Good!
Where are you from?
I'm from Himachal.
Okay.
You take off.
I'll call you.
You're still living the same life.
Earlier you'd wear a burqa
while going to work in jail,
and today as well you've
come wearing a burqa.
Ma'am... please save me.
Ma'am?
Doesn't seem right
coming out of your mouth.
Jojo...
... Gaitonde will kill me.
You wanted to grow wings
and reach for the sky.
Now that you've flown near the sun,
you're afraid of being burnt.
I was scared.
He made you an actress.
Today you are a sensation.
Why did you want to fly
next to the sun then?
Well, even he thinks he's God.
Just because he made me an
actress, he thinks he owns me.
That, I'll go to him
whenever he wants me.
- Even I have some reputation.
- Reputation? Seriously?
One call of his gets you shook.
Will you help me?
Why? Won't 'they' help you?
The ones you helped...
in killing Gaitonde.
They didn't kill...
What help do you want?
This...
What's this?
Jameela's passport.
All documents.
My entire previous life.
You remember your previous life?
In case I ever need it...
Just like you couldn't
rid of your previous life.
Still have kept Mary's picture.
There's always
plenty of gossip in the industry...
In the magazines,
blind articles...
But internally everyone knows...
The launch party...
Mary's...
Her film...
Before her film launch
on the roof... she...
Jameela!
You had a meeting today?
With... Manu... Manu Gaba?
It happened.
- How was it?
- Superb.
- Yeah?
- He'll give me a film,
if I take off my clothes.
The day we become big actors,
we're going to take all
these asshole's clothes off.
And if we don't big actors?
You certainly will.
Your looks are enchanting!
- Really?
- Really.
And my grace?
It's exquisite.
Just for that, Mary's special
noodles only for my Jojo.
My dearest Mary, surprise!
- What's this?
- Open it.
Wow! This is the same
bracelet that actress wears.
Thank you!
Go. Get out of here.
You had betrayed Mary...
Don't do the same to me
Bunty?
Sent him three girls
dressed up as dominatrix.
Only then he gave your number.
He said you're out of India
somewhere in the Ashram.
Don't tell me you've become a monk.
The penance I went through for you...
But you were still out of my reach...
What could I do?
Will you return from your
pilgrimage, if I come to you?
India's flushed out an order to
all countries to shoot me on sight.
This life of the
ascetic is all I got now.
Let Jameela off the hook.
She didn't know the shit
she was getting herself into.
Alright, she's off the hook.
Seriously? Easy as that?
You asked me that's enough.
By the way why you
defending her so much?
Repaying a debt...
Had betrayed someone.
Who?
Why do you want to know?
You've become a monk right?
Focus there. I've got some work.
Listen, listen...
Huh?
Cuss at me, for the last time.
Call me a faggot.
Why 'last time'?
Are you dying for real?
Who knows when this pilgrimage will end?
Will I get to speak to you again...
... I don't know.
You and your theatrics.
Come to Mumbai, I'll make you an actor.
And why won't we speak again?
I have your number,
I'm going to call you.
I won't receive
- your call.
- Really?
Even your daddy's going to
come! I'm hanging up now. Bye.
Faggot.
After I left, Miss Yadav
had you by the balls, right?
As soon as you left, I escaped as well.
When was the first
time you met Miss Yadav?
She loves her country.
So...
She got me to work as well,
for the sake of the country.
Don't you love... the country?
I do, indeed.
Although, her understanding of
the country and mine are different.
For her, country means
what it is in the present
and what it will be in the future.
But for us, country means
what it was in the past,
what it could have been today.
And it definitely shall become!
What shall it become?
Satya-Yuga...
Vedic Times.
All Ashram life revolved around
the Satya Yuga scam.
To enter Satya Yuga,
sacrifice was required.
Troubles, pains, hunger
were all forms of sacrifice.
Even during winters, the
motherfuckers didn't give a blanket.
Food was plenty, but not edible.
Yet, everyone was cool with it because
they would always get
free Gochi - the world's best drug.
I had slowly started understanding
what Guruji spoke about.
Guruji was writing a book
related to Satya Yuga
and said he'd reveal
everything at the right time.
One needed to be pure
to enter Satya Yuga,
Guruji would test that by his dice game.
Four.
To be proved pure, the
dice needed to show a four,
which would never happen for me.
Two.
Still, Dynamic.
There were many ways
to make one's self pure.
One was controlling pain.
The other was screaming out the anger.
Another was stashing away your lust.
We consider sex as a type of hunger.
It has a need...
it has a craving in it.
There is need to breath as well,
but it doesn't have
craving or violence it.
We need to make sex
as simple as breathing.
Make love to the soul.
Sex is nothing,
but the exchange of energy
Make it like an exercise
and it will make you pure.
In that lust and Gochi meeting
I saw Batya properly for the first time,
She was closest to Guruji.
And I wanted to replace her.
Gaitonde.
Who knows about our drug route?
Nobody knows.
Don't lie.
Our consignments are getting seized.
Maybe...
Miss Yadav.
Maybe?
- Huh.
- Huh?
I had felt hatred many times before,
but I felt jealousy for the first time.
The connection I felt with Guruji,
I had not felt with anyone before.
Not with mom, dad, Kukoo,
nor Subhadra, with nobody.
But Guruji felt that
way only with Batya.
I've thought of a name for this...
Kaal Granth.
Don't!
Only once we enter Satya-Yuga.
When will we enter it?
"Have patience O heart".
We will, shortly.
And this book...
... will be the last Guru of that world.
With your right hand, on the right side.
We need to keep a very
keen eye on everything.
According to our intel.
Mumbai is the likely target.
The truck drivers who had come in
with the supply have been caught.
What's in the truck?
- Nothing, Sir.
- Show me.
Come.
Stop you motherfucker.
Octroi has revealed...
these trucks have been
coming for the past 3 years.
We've found a lead where the
goods dropped by the truckers.
We have made a sketch too
We're assuming that this Harun
Bilal, Shahid's second in command.
We need to secure other
places of national interest.
Financial hubs, tourist
attractions, religious sites etc.
are being secured by the forces.
All the cash from the RBI
vault is being relocated.
Central oil companies'
fuel is being transported.
Take the pill, Sardarji.
Else, the hand won't stop shaking.
Coming up, Sir.
- Now...
- Sir.
- Are you ok?
- Yes, Sir.
Sir, if I can get 5
minutes with Bhonsle?
Not possible.
Sir, there is a connection
between Hizbuddin and the ashram.
That's what you think.
What about the trucks?
Someone's behind letting them through.
Will see.
Only four days remain
according to your investigation.
Or it could be less, what do you think?
Our evacuation plan is ready.
We can intermittently
cancel all flights zonally,
and use those aircrafts for
evacuation in Maharashtra.
What if we use local and express trains?
Two to 2.2 million people
can be evacuated in a day.
Ma'am we have asked the RTO for a
list of all the available vehicles.
Incoming traffic from
other cities will be barred.
All highway lanes will
have one-way traffic.
The BSF vehicles are also on stand-by.
Your phone call would always
result in one thing at our house...
a fight!
He would just drop everything,
his wife, kids, everything
and run after you.
I've come to speak to you about Rohit.
He doesn't come home. Just
sleeps in the nearby temple
or at a friend's place.
My son has definitely got wrong company.
I had met him.
Tried to make him understand,
but he's very angry.
And he has a right to be...
and you must be well.
I couldn't save him.
I'll make him understand.
Don't worry.
- I'm going.
- Hold on.
Keep this.
- No.
- Please.
Yes, Sir...
Sir, have you ever seen them?
You had said you would co-operate.
And I'm here.
Hmm?
Four-five minutes is all you have.
Joseph Sir, has asked
you to try as well.
Come.
We have got an hour. Let's
see what Sartaj can do.
Have things gotten so bad
that they've sent you?
- Audible?
- Yeah.
October 1996 was the first
time you went to Croatia
to Guruji's Ashram.
What did you say?
October 1996 was the first
time you went to Croatia...
Hey, Sartaj!
What does that have to do with
this case? Stop talking nonsense.
Between 2005 and 2015, the work
done by Gaitonde for the Ashram,
Import and Export...
Who gave the permissions
and sanctions for that?
What is this?
Guruji's close-knit circle
had 10 to 12 people...
You and Gaitonde were
also a part of that...
Gaitonde used to send trucks
full of stuff from Mandvi.
Someone high up let
those trucks cross borders
from Gujarat to Maharashtra.
Did you give the permission?
Sartaj, I don't have
time for this crap...
There's still 2 minutes left, Sir.
Take 'em up your ass.
Speak up.
- Oh, shit!
- What's your connection to Ganesh Gaitonde
Are you drunk, motherfucker?
Leave me, motherfucker!
How does the motherfucker
have the audacity to touch me?
Bhonsle knows something.
Sir.
Are you out of your mind?
I don't know how did he managed
to stay in your department.
He barely managed, Sir.
I'll go to Bhonsle's house to apologize.
Yes, please. We don't want him
calling the press and talking rubbish.
Let me handle this.
Illegal drug traces have been
found in your blood stream.
You're suspended from the SIT.
Sir...
Majid, keep an eye on him.
Sir, one second... Sir.
Sir, I think Sartaj was asking
Bhonsle about the trucks.
- So?
- Sir, I've also received a tip.
that an insider is involved in
giving clearance for the trucks.
Who?
Don't know, Sir.
I listened to your
advice I found a Guru.
Wish you luck.
What did you say at
home while coming here?
Nasik.
You...
Why did you choose him in
particular? Why not any other Guru?
Do you know of Vikarna?
If he's some local don, then yes.
When Draupadi was getting raped,
Vikarna was the only man to protest.
Our Guruji is just like him.
The entire world is on
the verge of destruction,
and only Guruji is speaking the truth.
KAL GRANTHA
Speak to us O' Earth, this
throne is feeling the dearth.
There was a time when every king
would have certain people in his court,
who would spend all day having
their ears touching the earth
and would be able to
detect horses footsteps
of the enemy's army even
a hundred miles away.
Today, the earth is speaking up again.
The soldiers of darkness, are
quickly approaching on horseback.
The time has come to elect a commander
that can hear the horses
footsteps of the approaching enemy.
This someone must not be
blinded by the darkness.
Ganesh,
take us into Satya-Yuga.
Two years later when Guruji made me
of the Satya-Yuga Project,
I thought he loved me as well.
What are you doing, Guruji?
Worshipping your purity.
Slowly I earned Guruji's love
and Batya's place.
Today, your life of
purity begins, Ganesh.
If I'd known that day what Satya Yuga
had planned for my future
I would have fucking burned
that monk's outfit right there.
I shouldn't get a call
from the Dean. Understood?
Yes, I'll tell her.
- Anjali?
- Yeah.
She's getting totally out of hand.
She stole mangoes from
the Dean's orchard.
Well?
Girls who play rough now,
won't get roughed up
when they're grown up.
Huh?
Listen, you can catch
Gaitonde in the morning.
Let's go to bed.
Come on.
What is it now?
Huh?
You didn't get enough of
me already, the entire day?
Now more questions?
I've come to apologize.
Then, apologize.
I apologize... On the
department's behalf as well.
Parulikar,
I've been playing
this game for 25 years.
How many years?
Twenty Five.
don't teach your daddy how to fuck.
Leave now.
Leave!
Joseph gave you Bhonsle and you...
Only two more minutes I
would've got it out of him.
You would've got two minutes
if you weren't taking dope.
It's not dope.
What was it then?
You got something from the Ashram?
What's the news on Shahid?
Just got an update.
We've been told to stay in this area.
He'll let us know the timing. Our
team is waiting at Military Cafe.
I'm not sure,
but Parulkar might have given
clearance for the truck...
that came from Kutch...
How do you know?
I just know it was someone
from our department.
In our force, there's not
a bigger bastard than him.
Did you tell Joseph?
There's no proof.
but I hinted at it.
Parulkar's a bastard. Why do
you play on his side so much?
To hide my name.
It's much more beneficial to be known
as Parulkar's man, than Majid Khan.
Yeah...
Did Shahid call?
Yeah, I'm coming.
Stay here.
Sir, I'm in position.
Copy.
Go speak to the owner.
Guruji had made me the commander,
at the time, I had no idea why.
I found out after 3 years
It was my duty to keep an eye on Bombay,
after coming to the ashram I
had become slightly drowsy.
But that day, Guruji planned
on shaking everyone up.
The world was about to change again.
This is Satya-Yuga...
and this is Kali-Yuga.
We need to go from Kali-Yuga
into Satya-Yuga.
Batya.
The journey is long...
It'll take some time. How will we go?
The earth is dying with
the burden of our weight
The cancer has metastasized.
Our lack of humanity
is bleeding us dead,
by a million cuts every day.
Who here doesn't get the
thought at least once a day...
that it'd be better if this world
ends today rather than tomorrow.
However, there is a way out,
which in scientific terms
is called a wormhole.
Time and space can be bent
to reach from one end
to the other in a flash.
Kali-Yuga is slow death.
We need to speed up this process.
We need to make sacrifice.
Are you people ready for sacrifice?
- Are you ready?
- Yes!
Yes!
Ganesh?
I'm ready.
You work for Shahid Khan?
It's not necessary that every
question has just one answer.
Gaitonde and Guruji's connection...
Yours and Batya's connection...
Dilbagh Singh and Ashram's connection...
What is the meaning of all this?
Gaitonde dying in front of
you wasn't a coincidence,
but destiny.
The two of us meeting here
isn't chance, but fate.
The stars have chosen you to
succeed where Gaitonde failed.
You will find all the
answers you desire,
by following the
footsteps of your father.
All life on earth was
born from a single cell.
Over time as this cell mutated,
it gave birth to new organisms.
All it needed was a small
push in the right direction.
To cause the creation of a new being.
There exist three important
historical conflicts in the world.
South and North Korea...
Second, Israel and Palestine...
Third, the biggest one
India and Pakistan.
They have been at war for over 70 years.
And this is not a war
of religion or nations...
This is a war of civilization.
We have the next 9 years
to push this world into
the next stage of evolution.
The world will remain
unstable for the next 9 years.
There will be financial
difficulties in America,
discord in the Arab world...
New dictators will rise
to power around the globe.
The people from the
first-world countries
will fight over global warming.
The Earth beneath us all,
is ridden with waiting mines.
One small step in the wrong
direction will cause calamity.
All we need to do is set one off
between the borders
of Pakistan and India.
Which will cause an explosion so big,
The flames will lure
everyone else in the fire.
If any of you wishes to leave
this Satya-Yuga project
is free to do so.
My love for you will always remain...
You can go.
Do you remember what we
spoke about Sacrifice?
The time has come for another sacrifice.
A new man will be born
with this new world
with the sole purpose...
of achieving the peace and truth
of our ancestor the first single cell.
Time the master of
the universe and life,
omnipresent like nuclear
energy and ever consuming
We will capture and control time...
with a nuclear blast.
Precisely 9 years from today,
there will be a nuclear blast...
And we shall return to the
nucleus that first created us.