WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Aham Brahmasmi.
Sir, where are you going?
You can't just enter li...
Get back.
Sir, where are you going? Sir?
Aham Brahmasmi...
Guruji is alive.
I'm sure he's around here somewhere.
Gaitonde had warned me
that his third father is
about to do something big.
Are you ready for the truth?
Follow me.
You'll understand everything.
He had been dead before I got there.
Looks like a clear suicide,
We're waiting for forensics.
So Malcolm who was dealing
in weapons with Gaitonde
is Shahid's proxy?
Hizbuddin has a history
of utilizing mercenaries.
Malcolm Murad has been a part of
almost every terror organization,
in Asia and Europe.
This looks like more than that.
Gaitonde... had Hizbuddin's
flyer hidden in it.
And his Guru that
Sartaj was talking about?
Sir, there's definitely a link
between the Ashram and Hizbuddin.
Contact Sartaj and tell
him I want to speak to him.
Take one.
It'll help you understand better.
You're not on duty.
Since when do you know I'm a cop?
All along.
Have it.
Otherwise this discomfort
will become paranoia.
What I'm about to tell you
is beyond the grasp
of your understanding.
Try to keep an open mind.
The plan is simple.
For the next 9 years,
you must focus solely on
increasing the suffering
by taking advantage of
the world's weaknesses.
From global warming
to the religious
propaganda on the internet.
Our fellow human beings are bent upon
unknowingly destroying this world.
Pakistan will attack India, and
get destroyed in retaliation.
China won't sit silently and
spectate. Neither will Russia.
Nor the USA.
They will begin attacking each
other like a bunch of mad dogs.
Their fight
will result in the end of mankind.
The earth's temperature
will fall rapidly.
Pushing the planet into a nuclear winter
while we watch safely
in our special bunkers.
We shall wait in those bunkers
and wait for our penance,
sacrifice, patience and truth's power
to take us into Satya Yuga.
You people are insane. Deranged.
It's the world that's gone mad, Sartaj.
It's a lie.
How can you destroy this world?
It's not us, the world
is destroying itself.
We are just a catalyst.
Look around you.
Earthquakes, tsunamis, global warming.
They're all signs from this earth.
What kind of world are
you trying to save, Sartaj?
When 3-year old children are getting
raped in the name of religion?
What's there in this
world that should be saved?
Do you have even one
reason to save the world?
Nobody will believe all this.
Dilbagh Singh believed in it.
This photo was taken on the day
Guruji revealed his vision to us.
Join us Sartaj. Finish
what your father started.
I told Guruji that
Shahid is beating a drum in the street,
begging for money to destroy India
Malcolm claiming to be
India's enemy met Shahid
and gave him money to
fulfill his insane desires.
Whether it's the Afghan
war or the war on India,
ISI has a bad habit.
They set flames to their surroundings
while hiding in the shadows.
The time is now to attack like bandits,
but they behave like petty pickpockets.
Not everyone has the courage.
You are right.
In 1947, the courage and character
Mohammad Ali Jinnah showed,
has vanished from today's world.
Looking at you one
can't be accused of that.
If one fights to the end,
he will surely perish, but...
But he will light a
candle of revolution.
Beautiful.
Just keep in mind
we can't turn back now.
- Think carefully before you join us.
- There's nothing to think.
It's Allah's will.
We are merely vessels.
I've spoken to Shahid. He's ready.
We just need to provide
him with nuclear fuel
and a place for assembly.
He'll do the rest.
Guruji's idea of ending the world
by adding fuel to the world's
flaming problems was a masterstroke.
There was huge crisis
in the Middle East.
We gave weapons t o those people.
The one's who didn't
die, became homeless.
The Americans were angry
because of the recession.
We gave them guns to vent their anger.
Guruji said he'd conquer
darkness with darkness.
his world had to sacrifice itself.
Now, the book Guruji had been
writing for the past 20 years,
was finally finished.
This book would teach us the
way to live in Satya Yuga.
They were the best days of my life.
Guruji made me believe
that I was special
and I would be the God of
the upcoming Satya Yuga.
And I believed everything he said.
Ganesh, I am going
into samadhi,
away from this life.
A millennium of darkness
needs to be vanquished...
And that requires immense
penance and purity.
I have to leave
But we will meet soon....
In Satya Yuga.
We will meet soon...
Guruji faked his death to the world.
So he could remain in monastic penance.
Strength and sacrifice were
needed to enter Satya Yuga.
Guruji would provide the
strength, and I would sacrifice.
I had to finish the job
with that bitch Batya.
I used to really miss Guruji.
I really wished for this world to end,
When I was exiled 12 years ago,
I had thought I made all
the needed sacrifices.
But little did I know,
the biggest was yet to come,
the sacrifice of Bombay!
To make the new world, it
was my job to plan in Bombay.
Batya left the Croatia Ashram
and made a team of 100 pure
people to enter the new world.
She brought all of them to Bombay.
Bhonsle used his political
influence to buy land worth millions
for pennies.
To build the Ashram in Bombay,
We will get every single artifact
that Guruji has worn, has
touched, has blessed...
I planted the false threat
of Pakistan in Bhosle's mind
and he provided all his men
with weapons, to spread terror.
But the bastard didn't know
what the actual plan was.
There will be more than 1000 tankers...
The trucks Bhonsle
used to smuggle weapons
were used for carrying
parts for the nuclear bomb.
My old factory was given to Malcolm
for assembling the
nuclear bomb with Shahid.
While above the ground,
Shahid constructed the bomb.
Under it, Batya began
preparing for the Satyug Project
and somewhere in the middle,
my third father remained hidden.
Everything was ready for
the 'Sacrifice of Bombay'.
They have something huge.
What do you mean?
I mean something so
dangerous that can...
destroy the world.
C'mon, spit it out?
This city might not survive.
And what do you mean 'they'
have something? Who's 'they'?
Who has something huge?
Wait. Joseph has asked
me to talk to you.
Sartaj, Listen to me.
No action will be taken
against you. Come with me.
Tell Joseph about Guruji,
the Ashram and whoever else...
I'll come myself.
Sartaj.
Sir, I would always
bring them up to here.
Have you seen him?
No.
- Have you seen him?
- No, Sir.
- Sir...
- Did you find anything?
No, Sir. There's nobody there.
Have you seen him?
Mahmud of Ghazni asked Ferdowsi
to write a book in his honor.
Mahmud said he'll pay
Ferdowsi 60,000 Dinar.
But when the book was
completed, he paid him only 200.
Ferdowsi cursed him so much
that Mahmud got malaria and died.
- Yeah.
- Boss.
Maggots are messing up our meal.
We may need to dump it.
Let's see we haven't found...
In teams of two...
The mold suggests
that it can hold about
20-30 of those booster tubes.
And at least 30 kg of fuel.
Joseph, the impact could be massive.
How massive?
I'm guessing that they
are aiming at about
80 kilotons of yield.
Hiroshima was... 20.
What'll you have Sir?
Scrambled? Poached?
Sunny side up? Gaitonde's special?
- The special.
- Right, Sir.
Sunil the chef of our old
hangout place didn't recognize me,
but he was still using my
name to advertise his joint.
The taste of the eggs
was still fireworks.
Fuck, it's still great!
- Hello.
- Bunty.
- Who is this?
- I saw your show on TV.
It fucking sucks.
Motherfucker. Who is this?
Hello?
- Hello.
- Tell me this.
Did they cut off your third leg as well?
Motherfucker. Who the fuck are you?
Come face me if you've got the balls.
Or I'll come there to stuff
your asshole with my umbrella.
Tell me the place.
You bring your ass
and I'll bring my belt.
You...
Speak up ass-wipe. Tell me the place.
Boss?
Welcome boss. Welcome.
You've returned after 13 years.
We are going to celebrate
13 years in one night.
What's this 'welcome'? You've
become quite sophisticated.
I thought you'd be... dead by now.
I'll die only after you, schmuck.
You remember...
what I had told you, then?
Did you stop thinking from your dick?
Well...
The blood doesn't flow there anymore.
It all keeps riling up in here.
Do you miss Badariya?
Sometimes.
And me?
It was your fear that kept me
away from India all these years.
Subhadra?
- Did you miss me?
- Nope.
Never.
Brother, I can't tell you how happy
I'm feeling with you sitting with us.
It's like when I fucked
for the first time.
What about Santa's money?
It seems as if I'm seeing your ghost.
Where were you all these years?
What would have I done
by coming to Bombay.
God has forbidden you
from fooling around.
What happened?
I had a younger sister, Mary.
Mary fell in real love with
Sameer, the producer's son.
He promised to launch her as an actress.
He even threw a launch party for her.
For years, Mary and I used
to give auditions together
and would get rejected together.
All of a sudden her life
became a Bollywood movie,
where she got everything in one
shot. Love, happiness, and a lead role
It made me jealous.
Oh, sorry! I'm sorry!
Mary!
Are you crazy?
How much longer are you going
punish yourself for this?
If I thought like you, I would
have died a thousand times already.
It's different with you.
You kill to save yourself.
Whom did I save by killing?
Whom did I save by killing my sister?
I fucked up so bad...
to get a shitty role
that it cost me my sister.
I was an idiot.
Let it go.
She comes and sits in
front me of everyday.
Look there, she's here.
"Ok, I'm sorry bitch."
What else do you want?
This city of Bombay gave me everything.
From being a waiter I
became the God of Gopalmath.
I'm...
It then struck me.
Can you give without expectation
of anything in return?
What could be purer than that?
If people could get this,
he whole world's 'darkness'
would finish right away
and there wouldn't be a
need for Guruji's plan.
The bomb that crashed into
Hiroshima was 15 kiloton.
This one is 120 kiloton.
That's, eight times stronger.
It'll wipe off 800,000
people in the first hour.
Plus, the next 8 generation of Indians
will come out decayed and rotten.
Inshallah.
We'll pay off the debts of
1965, 1971, and 1999 in one shot.
Aham Bramhasmi.
I want to speak to Guruji.
Why are you calling on
that line? It's not safe.
Where's Guruji? Do you know?
Gaitonde, you know no one
is allowed to speak to him.
He'll speak to me. I need
to tell him something.
Nobody.
Tell him it's urgent.
I just saw the bomb.
Motherfucker.
Now, there was only one
way to stop the plan...
To stop the money.
Gaitonde? What is all this?
It's your armor.
Armor?
Don't worry. I'll sort everything out.
Yeah, but will you tell
me what needs sorting out?
- What?
- Why aren't you sending the money?
Last payment is also pending.
In Kutch, Aalam is
holding on to the delivery.
- Have me speak to Guruji.
- Guruji's left.
Motherfucker, if you don't
have me speak to Guruji,
I'll piss on his 'New Day Project.'
Gaitonde, don't stop the work.
You know I can yank out the
money from your intestine.
Can you? Do it then.
Now I had to save myself and the world.
Bunty had made a mall which never
opened on Gopalmath's old junkyard.
I made a bunker for me underneath it.
to save my ass from
Guruji's runt, Malcolm.
Listen to me. I have decided.
This world is going to stay as is.
I'm going to tell the police.
Tell whoever you want.
Everyone is with us.
Aham Brahmasmi.
Your elephant has gone wild.
I told him everyone is with us.
And If he is not having Gochi
he will start to feel
paranoid very soon.
We have time Guruji, but not much.
Whenever some shit has
happened in my life,
it's always been because
one of my fathers.
That's just how these
father's are, Sardarji.
Throwing away your dad's
stuff won't do anything,
the more you try to get rid of them,
the more they fuck with your head.
Ultimately, I trusted
you to save this city.
And you are getting twisted in
Dilbagh Singh's story. Don't.
Talk.
Sir, we have found Awaiz's
brother, Saad. Please come fast.
I am coming.
Now, show us your dance
moves, motherfucker.
Move over. You go there, motherfucker.
Get up now, faggot Muslim.
Pick him up.
Pick up the asshole.
Beat him.
Give me the tire.
Get up.
Watch me hit a home run.
Give the ball.
Watch this home run.
Watch this fucking home run.
Innings complete.
What's there in this
world that should be saved?
Do you have even one reason?
Sir, no!
Sir, I haven't mentioned you as On-Duty.
Sir.
Sir...
Sister, Not right now.
Sir, I beg of you.
Sir, don't enter Rohit's
name in police records.
It will ruin his life.