WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -
Guruji, where were you?
I'm losing my fucking mind here.
It's essential. Ganesh,
every setback is essential.
I don't want to do all this.
I am aware.
I am also aware of the reason.
Guruji, I understand why
you want to make a new world.
But I don't give two
hoots about the world.
It can end today, for
all I fucking care.
Ganesh, Kaal Granth (Book of Time)
is complete. Do you want to see it?
This country doesn't need
any more fucking books.
Why did you write another one ?
Come here.
Time...
is just like this '8'.
It has no beginning or end.
You are not the first
or the last person,
to have faced doubts.
The new world that you want can be
brought about in a different way.
Tell me
Dynamic? Pure? Dark? A word full
of dicks? Name it and I'll provide.
Just keep Bombay out of this.
Otherwise I'll rat all
this to the fucking cops.
Wasn't I supposed to be God?
Isn't God supposed to be loving?
Calm down, Ganesh.
Fuck this.
A God doesn't hesitate
to accept sacrifice.
Then I'll take Malcom's
head as my first sacrifice.
How dearly you love this dark city...
Whatever you wish will happen, Ganesh...
Today will be the last time
for the 'Lotus position'.
Leave it whenever you want.
Aham Brahmasmi.
I am Lord Brahma's dirt.
I love every one.
I don't love any one.
I am an Aghori .
I am an Aghori.
I can stay alive by eating the dead.
I have repeatedly murdered my father.
I have repeatedly murdered my son.
I have repeatedly murdered my wife.
I have repeatedly murdered my wife...
I have murdered my mother.
I am God Kali of Kali Yuga...
... Son of demons and father of sin...
I am Kalki too, the savior of
Kali and Vishnu's 10th avatar
I am Kalki too.
I am supreme.
I am insignificant.
I am gruesome.
I am fierce.
- I am Brahma.
I am Brahma.
Only I am Brahma.
Only I am...
We've got the confirmations.
Our neighbor has been in
talks with North Korea,
to buy the designs of an
assembled fission device.
Apparently, they've been doing
this for the past 15 years.
We've also found out that the
commitments had already been made
and the resources had already
started changing hands.
You know the atmosphere in Pakistan.
The Prime Minister changed,
the Army Chief changed,
and then both, Shahid Khan
and Haroon were thrown out.
By that time, the alliance of
our enemies was already in place.
So they're getting Shahid
to do everything without
associating themselves?
They couldn't have asked
for anything better.
India will be under-attack
and they won't be 'accused'.
What are our options?
We're nearly out of options
The Home Ministry has
ordered the following:
the Commissionerate must
be transferred to Nagpur.
And you have to start
evacuating Mumbai...
immediately.
You both wait outside.
Jai Hind, sir.
Sir, is there any emergency?
For how long you been allowing
those trucks to come in?
Sir, I don't follow...
What don't you follow?
If an enquiry happens
you won't be spared.
We need to save this city.
Tell me why those trucks
were coming in to the city.
And if you don't know find out.
That's your only chance
to save yourself now.
Out.
Get out.
Brother...
... Phone.
Hmm.
The trucks you had asked me to bypass...
Hmm, you didn't get your cut?
No, call is not about that.
What were the trucks carrying?
India's most famous doughnuts.
You ever tried 'em?
My dad was the chef there.
It's gotten quite messy.
A top-level, very high-level
enquiry is going on.
My name has also come up in that.
Is this the first time
your name's come up?
How is Bhonsle... involved in this?
Look, I got no clue.
I owed my friend.
He asked me for a favor and
I asked you to get it done.
Which friend?
The one you guys let go in
1993 before coming after me,
forcing me to leave Bombay.
You involved me in Shahid Khan's job?
- Sir, a meeting is in progress.
- Wait, sir.
- You can't go in.
- Please stop. Sir!
Sir, I asked him to wait.
Bhonsle Sir,
I need to speak to you
for a couple of minutes.
Let's wait outside
Your mind is a mess, decide now.
Bite or let go.
Who spoke to you about granting
the permission for the trucks?
Had Isa called you?
Dubai's Isa?
Have you and Sartaj been
sharing a drink together?
I know you've been
granting those permissions
for the past 3 years.
Isa had called me for the last
truck's permission from Dubai.
Parulkar, I've no idea
what you're talking about.
Everything will be finished in
3 days, destroyed completely.
If you can't speak the truth
even while sitting on that chair,
then what's the point of power?
The political game you've
been playing for 25 years,
has become bigger than you.
They're using use you... and me!
They're using you! I
am of no use to them.
Do you know who Isa works for?
For who?
Shahid Khan.
And I don't need to give
his introduction to you.
Get up, Parulkar.
Get up.
Motherfucker, Get out.
Get out.
If I mention your
little game that you're
playing with Dubai to any outsider
Your uniform will be off and
you'll be suspended in minutes.
Your daughter is getting married
to the DG of Police's son,
I'll ensure that doesn't happen.
So, don't use your head
unnecessarily. Get out now.
Just remember if my
name comes up anywhere,
I'll make sure the world gets
to know what you really are.
Get out. Get out.
Motherfucker.
Guruji.
Nothing will stop
everything is here except one
last consignment.
I didn't expect this from Ganesh.
That dog's gone wild.
He needs to be put down.
First, we need the Kaal
Granth (Book of Time).
Time will punish him.
This was not the way to go.
This was not the time to go.
You always said,
We choose our journeys ourselves.
We choose our struggles,
our purpose, before we
are born on this planet.
Why did you choose this?
Why?
Guruji, forgive me.
Forgive me, Guruji.
How will you destroy what is inside you?
How will you silence the
voice that hasn't reached you?
Shut up, motherfucker.
You do not have a choice, but
to listen to this story, Ganesh.
This story sowed the seeds
of Satya Yuga in my life;
the story of my parents'
first conjugation.
Do you know, what came first?
Amoeba.
One became two.
Like this.
Then, two became four.
And four became eight.
Gradually, a pyramid was created.
If two people, created out
of a single cell amoeba,
connect to each other ancestrally
to become a single cell,
that concept is known as
a soulmate.
It is said that Lord Krishna
had sixteen thousand lovers...
But he is worshipped everywhere
only with Goddess Radha.
- Why?
Soulmate.
It's all a proven science,
not some superstition.
Okay, but what are you trying to say?
That, if a human being
finds its soulmate,
its purpose of life is accomplished.
When two soulmates come together
to reproduce, an Avatar is born.
Our job is just to find the soulmate,
the Avatar will handle everyone else.
And where will this Avatar come from?
I wasn't born a human,
but an Avatar.
My fathers' unusual
pharmaceutical practices,
my mother's ancient yoga practices and
once-in-a-lifetime planetary positions
combined and I came to Kali Yuga.
At the age of four, I
knew the Gita by heart.
Whenever religion decays an Avatar
is born to reinstate truth of...
I would deeply feel,
that I was born to change
the direction of time.
Father,
where are we going?
My father would have replied,
but in 1975,
Indira Gandhi's government
fearing my father's
protests took him away.
He never came back.
My father never told
me whose Avatar was I,
I needed to find out myself.
Whom did I need to destroy?
I would ask myself
that question everyday.
One fine day, the answer appeared.
I needed to destroy the world
this world that could not
accommodate a wise man like my father.
I needed to destroy Kali Yuga
and bring Satya Yuga.
You can try all you want, Ganesh.
but Satya Yuga will definitely arrive.
And when that happens,
you won't be able to live
with any of your lies.
Trivedi, do whatever you
got to do in prison now.
Lies such as: you hate your father.
Lies that he is dead.
You will never find peace.
Ganesh, there's still time.
Walk the path of forgiveness.
Save yourself and your father.
Dilbagh Singh also wished
to see the new world.
I am glad you thought about it.
What do you need from me?
Gaitonde killed Guruji
and stole the Kaal Granth.
Malcolm searched for it
everywhere but was unsuccessful.
You are the last person he spoke to.
You both have a cosmic connection.
He must have told you something.
You need to think harder.
Whether you help us or not,
this world won't survive.
You have two options,
either you die like a nobody,
or you help bring a new world.
A new world you can be a part of.
A new world, Dilbagh Singh believed in.
All good, Sardarji?
Yes.
A Lot of work needs to be done
before we enter the new world.
No problem. We'll get it done.
Thank you.
I've been trying the numbers,
found in Anjali's Diary
constantly, but I can't find a lead.
My eyes ache staring at them.
I don't know what we're doing, sir.
Rama...
we're short on time.
Sorry.
Your family stays here as well, right?
Yes, in Sewri.
Tell them to go back to the village.
- Where is the village?
- Vidarbha.
The Chief Minister will make the
evacuation announcement by evening,
but it'll be too chaotic by then.
Tell them.
Sartaj,
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Sartaj.
Joseph Sir, Sartaj has
gone into the evidence room.
Sartaj... open the door.
Sartaj...
Open! Sartaj!
INTERNATIONAL DHAMAKA
Open the door...
Aye, open!
- Stop!
- Sartaj!
Aye, Sartaj!
Sartaj, put your gun
down. You can't escape.
- What are you doing?
- Close the door.
Sartaj...
- [
- Come in.
How did all this happen?
- Umesh?
- He is gone out.
This news is reminiscent
of the Indian Ocean tsunami of 2004.
The destruction caused
by this event was such,
that took years to reverse.
This world is about to end.
... has triggered a tsunami, that's...
- What?
- It's considered to...
- Sartaj...
- The Mumbai Police has allegedly,
been asked to escalate the evacuation
process in the city overnight.
From Kanyakumari to Port Bandar,
coastal cities have
been put on high alert...
Sartaj...
We're getting information...
Please rest for a bit.
Huh?
Will go to the doctor soon.
Please, leave from here.
Please!
The tsunami alert is fake.
For the past 20 days, we've
been searching for a bomb.
This city needs to be evacuated,
otherwise millions will end up dead.
Only 40 hours are left..
Yeah, okay.
We'll leave.
Please rest for a bit.
I'll be back soon
I repeat do not stay at home,
you will not be safe in your homes.
The authorities have said,
not to head to higher
altitude regions in city.
I repeat, do not go to higher regions,
police will have no way to retrieve you.
Parents are advised to
carry infants in their arms,
to prevent an injury.
I think this will fit you.
... carry your personal
belongings with you,
to make your journey quicker.
I'll be back soon.
... please follow the instructions,
move in haste and be safe. Goodbye.
My dad was a character.
He was the village priest
and used to beg for donations.
He loved me,
but he killed my mother.
I didn't know whether I should have been
happy or sad, after the
police took him away.
Trivedi, do whatever you
got to do in prison now.
What will happen in 25 days?
Everyone will die.
- Only Trivedi will survive.
- Trivedi who?
You're going to call the cops here?
I'm not going to call,
they are waiting downstairs.
I have proof of every
kind of debauchery,
that takes place in this
beautiful home of yours.
Don't you know how to
talk straight, faggot?
Why've you kept them waiting downstairs?
Should've invited them up here.
Hey, all of you come
up! Your pimp here...
- What's your name?
- Sharma.
Sharma...
here is throwing empty threats.
Come up if you've got balls.
I want to speak to Gaitonde.
Please, hold a bit harder.
You want to speak to Gaitonde?
You needed the cops
help to say just that?
Hello. Some dickhead
has come to speak to you.
- What?
- Some Sharma...
He looks like a dick.
- Who's this Sharma?
- Speak to him.
Aham Brahmasmi.
Ganesh, what have you done?
What do you want, motherfucker?
I want a meeting.
Yeah, I'll tell you later.
Get the fuck out of there.
You done?
Get out of here.
Miss Yadav...
Excuse me.
I told you not to...
Do you remember anything
about Gaitonde's father?
You've startled her, by
asking all these questions.
May I please get a glass of water?
Please.
I'm sorry... but this is urgent.
Is Gaitonde's father alive?
Is Gaitonde's father's name Trivedi?
Gaitonde killed his mother.
But it was the father
who went to prison.
- He told me...
- Water.
Can you please wait
outside for a moment?
She doesn't speak in front of you.
Please.
Is his father alive?
I had written it.
In a diary?
Miss Yadav, where did you write it?
Where did you write it?
Let her go!
Mother!
What are you doing?
She must have made some notes.
She would have given you some
information if she wanted to.
And if she didn't want to, she
would have kept quiet. You saw...
Leave now.
Aye, Mutthu.
It's Mathu, not Mutthu.
That's what I said. Mutthu.
You're going to keep acting
like teenagers your whole life?
- Look straight, please.
- Click it.
- When will the passport be made?
- In 4 days.
Boss, what kind of jobs
are we going to do now?
We're going to go to China.
The Chinese are taking over the world.
We're going to crack deals for them.
Holy fuck,
back to where we started from.
No,
this is going to be like
formal white collar jobs.
Boss, what's the deal with Guruji?
Didn't I tell you not
to talk about that?
I always knew there was something
off with that faggot Guruji.
You want me to send you a memo now?
Didn't I fucking say not to
mention that fuckers name?
Sorry, Boss.
Ganesh...
How long we have to hide like
this boss, lets kill that cunt.
How did he find out?
Nothing leaked from our end.
Ganesh,
why don't you hide in your
bunker. Nobody can reach you there.
It gets lonely there.
It's better here with you guys around.
Hey Gaitonde,
what are you thinking about?
I've never seen you like this before.
You won't mention it to anyone, right?
I won't, tell me.
Tell me.
I hear a voice...
Guruji's.
Voice?
Here.
Inside my head.
All day and night,
even in my sleep.
It keeps telling me random shit.
It curses at me, it gives me advice...
At times it feels real,
at times I feel I'm crazy.
I'm losing my...
No, no, no.
Gaitonde, don't worry.
We're all here together.
You haven't had this for a while.
Just keep it on your
tongue and it'll be fine.
Shall we go...
or are you going to piss
out the whole sea right here?
Chill. Hold on a second.
Listen...
Bring Trivedi to me. I want to meet him.
That's my father, Sardarji.
The thorn of my life.
I think this is for you.
Don't want it.
You take care of your sins,
I'll take care of mine.
Dear Dad,
please forgive me. I could
not do anything for you.
I am sending you a book.
If you take this book to Batya,
she'll take you in to Satya Yuga.
There is everything in this book.
The story to end this world and
the mantra to start the new world.
And if I know Guruji, the way to
save the world is in here as well.
Majid Sir...
M...
Hello, sir. One number got traced.
- Hello, Nair.
- Yes, Gama.
- How's the weather?
- Its hot.
This is Haroon, his right hand man.
Its great. Cold, like ice-cream.
We'll come over with
customers? Ready to serve?
- Yes, come. Don't be late.
- Okay, Gama.
Bring a spoon.
The phone isn't switched
off. It's in downtown.
- Rama, send the live location.
- Let's Go.
- What happened, sir?
- Listen.
Have you seen him?
He's staying in 202.
Get up!
Get up, motherfucker!
Where's Shahid Khan?
You can go back if you want.
But there's same pain
and same failures there.
Will you come with us?
Aham Brahmasmi.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -