WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -
- Hello, Naz.
- Yes, Dad.
- How are you?
-  I'm good, Dad. How are you?
I'm good.
Where's grandma?
She's here.
How's she doing?
Not so good.
Her memory's really giving up.
She keeps saying random things.
- Like what?
- One minute.
Father is on the phone.
My father.
Your son, grandma.
Mother.
- Shahid?
- Wow, you recognized me.
When will you take me
to the Golden Temple?
See what I mean, Dad?
Mom, I had told you
not to talk of these
things in front of anyone...
You had promised me we would go.
Yes, we will go.
I'm making the arrangements.
Really?
Yes, Mom.
I'm your son.
Whether I meet you or not,
the Golden Temple is yours.
I just...
... need your blessings.
The evening news, lakhs
of men, women and children
are crossing the Radcliffe line,
marking the border between the two
nations India and Pakistan...
- Hurry up son
- Yes father, almost done
- Show me some light.
- Here.
Satti, turn that off.
Mother.
You hear that?
I'm telling you, Sheru's following us.
- It's not Sheru.
- Sheru!
Sheru!
Navneet, have you gone crazy.
- Stay inside and be quiet.
- But Sheru?
We've come 15 miles. Sheru
can't follow us that far.
Navneet, Sheru will be safe.
He's neither Hindu nor Muslim.
- Please stay inside, sweetheart.
- Why did you leave him there?
Navneet.
Calm down.
I can hear his bark.
- Navneet!
- Sheru!
- Sheru! Sheru!
- Prabjyot you stay inside.
- Sheru!
- Stop.
Navneet!
Leave me.
- Leave the girl.
- Leave.
- Dad...
- Stay back
Leave me.
- Leave me.
- Go inside!
- Dad...
Dad...
Golden Temple...
Speak up! Where's Shahid Khan?
Motherfucker, I'll open your mouth.
- Do you know where the bomb is?
- Not yet.
- When will we know?
- We made few raids.
- What will that do?
- We arrested one.
Joseph, I am extremely disappointed
with your team's inefficiency.
Whenever we ask you say we are on it!
Get me results
- or be ready for suspension.
- You can suspend whomever you want,
but this is not the time for threats.
I made a mistake should have given
this case to the Centre a week ago.
And they would have solved
the case with a magic wand?
They wouldn't be waiting
around like your team.
Ma'am I promise.
My team will not budge
unless we finish this job.
This is our vow and our responsibility.
Sir, I've got a tip.
Sir, one question.
We have heard that the
Tsunami threat is hoax
covering up a nuclear
threat? Your comments, sir?
Lord Ganesh is protecting us.
All will be well.
- Sir...
Are you saying that
you were just informed
about the nuclear threat?
You are being called a political
prostitute, in parliament.
What did you say?
Do not touch...
Everyone move back.
All of you are so insistent on
representing a specific community,
that the same community
has become a threat now
under you garb of secularism.
Ask the CM about the
nuclear attack threat.
And ask DCP Parulkar why
Hizbuddin couldn't be located.
Jai Hind. Jai Maharashtra.
And with that explosive confirmation
of the widespread rumor,
Maharashtra Home CM has sent the
financial capital of the country
into a spiral of shock and horror.
If true
this is the biggest threat faced by
India in its 70 years of existence.
We are being informed
that the Centre has activated
multiple companies of
the Army and the CRPF
to control the panic
and neutralize the threat
but it remains to be seen.
Is it all
too little too late?
Aham Brahmasmi.
Move it. Take off your pants.
Here.
All okay?
Or should I show you by
peeling off the skin as well?
Gaitonde will peel off
the skin, don't you worry.
You look like an actress trying
to get a break in the movies.
Put your clothes on.
Sinner.
Move.
Stop.
What is all this?
The new world.
Isn't this what you
wanted to make. Enjoy.
Ganesh, why did you do it?
We'll forget Guruji's murder.
We have already forgotten.
Just give us Kaal Granth (Book of Time).
Pull it out.
Is there anything to drink?
- Has he come?
- Yes
Mathu brought him.
Ok then.
Our biggest problem is
that we think small...
Isn't that what Guruji taught us?
I've called you hear to
listen, not speak. Understood?
And tell Malcom to get off my ass.
- It will be done.
- And cancel this bomb planting bullshit.
Did you get that, motherfucker?
Understood?
Don't start something you
can't finish motherfucker!
Cunt!
Leave me. Leave me.
Motherfucker, Stick to
speaking, knives are'nt toys.
Don't try to be something you aren't.
And what are you Gaitonde?
Faggot,
you've forgotten who I am?
- Who are you?
- I am Gaitonde.
Who is Gaitonde?
I am Ashwathama.
And who made you Ashwathama?
- Huh?
- You created me?
Not me. Your daddy!
- You made me?
- No.
Faggot, did you make me Ashwathama?
Saved you. Destroyed you. Clothed
you. Gave you food, did everything.
You are a stray dog.
We made you our pet and
took you for a joy ride.
While you stuck your
tongue out of the car.
Who killed Subhadra?
- Isa.
- Was it Isa?
It was those buttfuckers:
langoor, ghaslet, Abdul.
Bunty got rid of them all.
Try to remember his face. Try, try.
You had met him at Guruji's Ashram.
Remember Lohane? He had
later given you water as well.
We staged every character in your life.
Who do you think sent
Jamila to your cell?
- Bunty.
- No I had.
You became a shriveled penis in jail.
Jamila got you hard again.
Who got you out of prison?
Tell me? Who was it?
He is lying, Ganesh.
You're lying.
I took you out of prison.
You're not Ashwathama. Neither a King.
You're just a slave
for Guruji's new world.
You're a slave. Nothing more.
- Slave?
- Fucker, you're just a slave for Guruji.
- Motherfucker.
- You are Guruji's slave.
Bastard.
You are Guruji's slave.
Motherfucker, I am Ashwathama.
Son of a bitch.
I am Ashwathama.
Motherfucker.
Faggot.
I am Ashwathama, motherfucker.
Boss, write down this number.
+ 971...
Who is it?
Did you kill Subhadra?
Gaitonde.
You killed Subhadra?
I don't kill women.
Tell me what I asked, faggot.
You're right. I must
have killed some women.
But I didn't kill Subhadra,
or any of your lovers.
And Kukoo, you know, you killed her.
Motherfucker.
Bastard.
It's nice to hear your voice,
to know that you're alive.
Come to Dubai if you
need a place to hide.
It's hot, but the meat is great.
You're going to protect me, fucker?
You... Who's dying himself.
You have cancer, right?
Speak softly, the devil may hear you.
He arrived as a Messiah
for our Salvation
but hung a martyr of revolution.
What?
A poem by Zulfi.
Say 'Hello' to my city.
Your city?
Bombay.
All of you are so insistent on
representing a specific community,
that the same community
has become a threat now.
Ask the CM about the
nuclear attack threat.
And ask DCP Parulkar why
Hizbuddin couldn't be located.
And with that apparant
visuals coming from Mumbai
it has caused a chaos to the
financial capital of India
and with the widespread rumors
the conditions are getting worse
with the false news of a
nuclear and Tsunami attack.
Several hundred's are injured with
no hospital staff to tend to them,
Several subway's and bridges...
Parulkar,
you've come to apologize again?
Do you also want a diplomatic passport?
Do you also want a diplomatic visa?
Hey...
Huh?
Do you also want a diplomatic visa?
We're facing a fucking storm
and everyone is concerned
with their fucking Visa
Motherfucker.
Speak up, Parulkar.
All the religions of the world
have manipulated the idea
of God, desecrated it,
in a time when Humanity
was rotting beyond repair
a small group of enlightened souls
came together.
To restart this beautiful world
with consciousness
as its central pursuit.
The world, as we knew it
and were born into, is over.
A new world dedicated to pure life,
will replace the old dark world.
When the cloud clears,
Satya Yuga will begin.
Aham Brahmasmi.
- Aham...
- Brahmasmi.
Aham Brahmasmi.
- When did you find out?
- How does it matter?
We had mutually decided
that we won't have children.
Did we not?
- Did we not, Sartaj?
- Yeah, we did.
Because you didn't want to.
Yes, I didn't want to. Does
my choice have no value?
What is the problem in having one
The problem is that your ego is hurt.
The problem is you don't say the truth.
And the truth is you don't
think I can take care of a child.
And that's why you keep
making up random excuses like:
choice, the crowded cities
and god knows what else.
Megha, you have no idea
how bitter you're making me.
All this will end
and we'll have to
start everything again.
How will this all end?
While the world outside
may get destroyed,
The real one resides within you.
How will that disappear?
Megha, you do not know.
Everything will end.
You are angry I made
my choice on my own.
And you?
Whose going to destroy
this entire world?
Have you consulted anybody
else before doing this?
You're just imagining
that everything will end.
You might forget everything
about this day, your anger,
the ego behind it, and
the guilt behind your ego.
But your lack of
self-worth will never end.
Fighting the world isn't going
to solve anything, Sartaj.
You need to wage war with yourself.
I kept thinking of my cursed life,
I couldn't have had worse one.
But when I put the gun to my head,
everything became clear to me.
The sweets my mom made on Diwali...
The rush from jumping into
the icy pond in the village.
The way my heart grew
soft and beat faster
when a girl hugged
me for the first time.
I thought I'd melt.
Bunty's dance moves...
Mathu's English after getting drunk...
And Kanta Bai's head
always smelling of fish...
I realized, they must have
shared such soothing moments too.
I started seeing all their lives...
But it all vanished within a second:
Every beautiful moment,
those people, those places...
Everything got burnt to ashes.
By the time I understood all
this I was already in my grave.
But you are not, Sardarji.
Save this world.
All the religions of the world
have manipulated the idea
of God, desecrated it.
in a time when humanity
was rotting beyond repair
a small group of enlightened souls
came together.
What's your name? What is
your name? Say your name.
Haroon Bilal.
- How long have you been in India?
- Since 2013.
Where is your home in Pakistan?
Peshawar.
Haroon, where's Shahid Khan?
Don't know.
Where's the bomb?
Its with Shahid
Where's Shahid?
You both had decided
the bomb's location.
You know! Didn't you
both decide the location?
Doctor, increase the dosage.
Haroon, what can be seen
from where the bomb is
planted? What can be seen?
Mumbai.
What's ahead of it?
Any local train tracks?
- No.
- Metro tracks?
- Can the ocean can be seen?
- No
- Can a lake be seen?
Can a lake be seen, Haroon?
Hello.
I'm busy now. Later.
So?
Driver, stop the car.
- What now?
- I hear voices sometimes.
They're telling me you betrayed me.
Get out of here. I need to go.
Malcolm's after my ass and
Guruji's stuck in my head.
I need to know the truth from you.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Let me go to church I'll
talk to you after that. Scoot.
Drive the car. Take a right.
Did you not hear what I said?
Drive the car, motherfucker.
Why have you brought me here?
What is all this?
I'm talking to you.
I don't have much time left.
I wanted to spend what was left
with you, that's why I got you here.
Who had told you to send Jamila to me?
Ganesh, you are very afraid right now.
Shut up, motherfucker!
Who had told you?
I don't remember.
I only trust you.
Everyone else is fucking...
Then don't trust me. Who
asked told you trust me? Don't.
It can't be you.
I can't be that much of a dumb-fuck.
Actually, you're much
more than you think are.
What do you mean?
Yes, I'm with them.
With who?
From Day 1
They all told me:
"Keep Gaitonde in-check."
- Be quiet.
- Why?
The truth made your cock disappear?
What are you doing?
Jojo, stop it.
Then let me go. Give me the keys.
There's no way out now.
Keys to the door.
This door doesn't open with a key.
Does it open with a cock then?
Jojo, you motherfucker.
You are the motherfucker.
Your father's the motherfucker.
I told you I want to leave from here.
Motherfucker, I'm
going to die in 4 days.
Not in 4 days, but in
4 hours, you'll die.
As soon as I get out,
I'm going to tell 'him'
to finish you off.
You know who I'm talking about, right?
- Malcolm?
- Correct answer.
[fading footsteps
How does the door open?
For that, you've got to get the cock up.
Yes, I knew
how they took you for
a ride for 20 years.
You cannot fight destiny.
MAHARASHTRA POLICE
- Majid.
- Where are you Sartaj?
Did you find the bomb?
Yes, in Powai. The old
parking lot behind the IT Park.
Majid? Majid?
There's a sniper in the building ahead.
Majid? Majid? Majid?
Let's move.
Move. Move. Move.
You, motherfucker!
You won't speak?
You won't speak.
Ponnuthai is trying
to diffuse the power.
You won't be able to stop anything.
The bomb you're seeing today
was planted in 1947,
it's been awaiting
explosion for 70 years.
How will you stop it?
It needs to be accessed physically.
Temps.
We got access to the motherboard.
- How much time is left?
- Checking, Sartaj.
11 minutes 43 seconds.
This is asking for a pattern.
We've got only 5 attempts at this.
Incorrect password.
Get up, motherfucker. Get up.
What's the password?
Gazwa-e-Hind.
Say it, motherfucker.
What's the password?
You won't be able to save anything.
Incorrect.
- Jigar...
- Sir.
Move all the forces. Evacuate
this place immediately.
Ok, sir. Everybody out, move...
We have to move fast, let's go...
Sir? Sir? You can't
just leave from here.
Are you blind, Sartaj?
Everything's finished.
We lost.
Move.
C'mon. Let's go.
C'mon. Hurry up.
Ma'am, could this be the pattern?
Let's go Sartaj.
Sartaj, we have no time. Let's go.
Come on.
Sartaj.
Sartaj, please. Let's go. Please
No, sir.
KAAL GRANTH (BOOK OF TIME)
Sardarji, I would have saved
this world if it were so easy.
I called you after all doors had shut.
There was nobody in this city
who could be trusted
besides Dilbagh Singh.
You have 25 days. Save your city.
But even you didn't listen to me,
and brought the cops with you.
Don't do this, sir.
I've been mind-fucked for
the first time in my life.
You don't know the whole story.
Tell me the rest of it in prison.
My story was left incomplete.
Guruji used to say that every
big task requires sacrifice.
Why do you think I sent you to Bombay?
How would I know?
Sacrifice of the most
dear is always the Purest.
So you wanted to sacrifice me?
Ganesh, this world
is resting on stories.
there aren't any
stories, without sacrifies
there wouldn't be any scriptures.
God, heroes, villains, principles.
Ganesh, these are all stories.
If not you someone else
will do the Sacrifice...
Come with me.
Our work will never stop, Ganesh.
Who did Dilbagh Singh make you meet?
Our work will never stop,
drop your gun.
RIGHT PATH
Son,
do not be ashamed. You tried your best.
Aham Brahmasmi.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -