Faizan Bhai, please excuse us.
I have a very special mission for you.
Mission Zulfiqar.
We have a huge stock of nerve gas.
I want you to use it
to attack Delhi.
Do you realize what you're suggesting?
This will be the biggest attack on India.
And it will lead to a war.
Listen carefully, Moosa.
Only a few people know about this.
And now, you are one of them.
Even Faizan has no knowledge about this.
Do you get me?
But ISIS won't let me go.
If I was in their place,
I wouldn't have either.
But don't you worry.
Getting you to India
is my responsibility.
You'll get the rest
of the details soon.
India won't be the only country
that will try to stop this plan.
Even Pakistan will
create hurdles for us.
That's why I want you to
create a backup plan.
Plan B.
God forbid if somebody asks you
to abort the mission midway...
even if that is me...
it will only mean one thing.
Plan B.
Only two people know about this.
Me and you.
But what is Plan B?
-Another bomb?
-Something like that.
It's been in Delhi for many years.
We just have to activate it.
And what do I need to do?
Go meet him.
He's critical for Plan B.
You look nice.
And...
how's the new job?
It's nice.
How was Kashmir?
Kashmir? It's a long story.
Let's go somewhere...
on a holiday.
I'll tell you about Kashmir.
And you can tell me about
your new job in detail.
Holiday?
Why not?
We can drive...
to Lonavala.
Or...
Mahabaleshwar.
Alright, let's drive
for twelve hours and go to Goa.
-Good idea.
-I'll drop the kids today.
But the auto-rickshaw guy is here.
So what?
I am their father,
I can drop them.
The auto-rickshaw guy
is not their father.
Wow!
Shall we?
Dad, you won't believe it
but Suchi is a better driver.
Oh, please!
Is she really that good?
Good? She's amazing!
Just like Fast &amp; Furious.
Dhriti, what's trending
on Instagram nowadays?
Any new update?
What do they call it?
"May-may."
It's "meme," Dad.
Not "may-may."
-Get it right.
-All right! Meme.
You haven't checked
your phone even once.
First tell me.
-Are you and Mom getting a divorce?
-What?
-Where did that come from?
-What do you mean?
Earlier, you never used to be home.
Now, even Mom's never home.
You two don't talk like you used to.
And we never go out, like never.
And you tend to disappear.
I feel like I don't
even know who you are.
Do you even know what's
going on in my life?
Or Mom's life?
You know nothing!
If you two get divorced,
I am warning you...
you guys will have it from me!
Dad!
I found your secret gun.
What?
-Where?
-In your room.
Now don't go around
advertising that.
Shall we go for an ice cream
after class?
Ice cream won't do,
I want an iPhone.
Bye.
Stop, motherfucker!
-Give him one.
-No.
I did yoga this morning.
Don't ruin it.
One Vada Pav
won't make a difference.
-Give him one.
-Major terror plan averted in Kashmir.
Actually, their target was Delhi.
The spokesperson for the NIA
issued a statement saying
the planned terror strike in
Delhi was way bigger than 26/11
in terms of scale
and lives lost.
Nonsense!
This is their regular shit.
If they could have avoided
26/11, why didn't they?
Were they playing marbles then?
These people from NIA and MIA
sit in their AC cabins all day
and lounge about.
And then, those assholes speak
of averting terror attacks.
-Good morning, sir.
-Good morning.
Sir.
Srikant, I'm afraid
there's some bad news.
We started celebrating
too early.
I am sending you a recording.
Listen to it.
Yes, bhai?
Tell the groom right away
that he shouldn't go collect the turban.
-Has the wedding been called off?
-No.
The wedding will take place
on the decided date.
Now listen carefully.
Tell the groom right away to go to Delhi
and meet his elder brother.
Meet his Chettan.
He has chosen another
girl for him.
He'll explain everything.
The groom stands for Sajid.
Turban stands for nerve gas.
And Chettan means Moosa.
Another girl means they
have another bomb...
or another backup plan.
Zulfiqar is not over.
So what's the plan of action now?
We need to go to Delhi.
Right away, sir.
-Good evening, sir.
-Water.
Thank you.
Hi.
Can we speak privately, Vaibhav?
Have we met before?
Come.
Whoever you are,
there's nothing you can do.
The Supreme Court
has made this legal.
Try telling this to your wife.
Motherfucker!
Who are you?
-If you act too smart--
-1311...
Mayur Vihar, Phase 1, Pocket 2.
That's your address, right?
Please don't send it to my house.
I don't have anything to give you.
I'm an employee in a chemical factory.
My salary is barely enough
for my expenses.
-If you want I can--
-Did I ask you for money?
Then?
You'll get a phone call.
Just do as you're told.
What do I have to do?
Listen to me. Excuse me...
You still didn't find it?
Are you looking for a camera?
-Did you find it?
-Finders keepers.
I'll pay you for it.
Please give me that camera.
You'll need to pay a lot for it.
Do you have that kind of money?
How much do you want?
I'll take at least 500 rupees.
Send Moosa's and Sajid's pictures
to every news channel.
Tell the Delhi Police to use
its social media cell
to flash their photos
through every handle.
All police stations
should get these instructions.
Their patrolling vans should
be on alert, 24 hours.
We can't afford a single mistake.
We have to be at our best.
Carry on.
-Srikant.
-Yes, sir.
-Any updates.
-No, sir.
-Delhi police are on red alert.
-I have a meeting with the NSA.
-Keep me posted, please.
-Sure, sir.
Sharma, let's go.
Zoya, keep monitoring
the CCTV cameras.
Milind, toll-free number?
Sir, we got many calls,
mostly false alarms.
Although we're following
a couple of leads.
Keep all the lines open.
You'll surely get some information.
-Yes, sir.
-Okay?
On it, sir.
40 rupees.
If you have any information
about Moosa Rahman or Sajid
call the number listed below.
The informant will be rewarded
with ten lakh rupees.
Ten lakh!
Will I get my money?
The government has promised it.
You will get it.
The government also promised us
15 lakh rupees.
That's why I had a
bank account opened.
I haven't received a single rupee.
Tiwari, we found Moosa's mother.
-What?
-Yeah.
Finally.
Get her to Delhi right away.
You really think that will help us?
After the riots,
when Moosa was searching for his family,
he found his mother
sitting next to the cremated
bodies of his father and sister.
She had somehow managed to survive.
She went into trauma.
It took Moosa many years
to help her recover.
When the doctors reassured
him that she wouldn't die
he left home to seek revenge.
Tell me. Helpful or not?
How do you know this?
Moosa told me...
along with all the other bullshit!
Sir, we got a call from a bar called Oaks.
The bartender saw Sajid.
Okay, check it out.
Come on, guys. On it.
Let's go! Right away.
Hi, I am Kareem Bhat.
That's Nissar and Iqbal.
We will teach Deshpande and
his supporters a lesson.
They killed two of our Muslim brothers
because they suspected that
they were carrying beef.
Today, we will feed beef
to Deshpande and all his men.
Jonali, they're hunting us
down like animals. Shit!
I hope you find this camera
and that justice prevails.
I love you, Jonali.
Yes, that's him.
So many people come here.
How can you be so sure?
I remember him.
He was with Vaibhav.
Vaibhav is a regular customer here.
They were sitting at that table
and chatting for some time.
Then suddenly, this guy left
and Vaibhav broke into tears.
He seemed worried.
What is Vaibhav's full name?
-I don't remember.
-How does he pay? Cash or card?
He always paid by card.
Could you please
get the card receipts?
Thank you.
His name is Vaibhav Therani.
T-H-E-R-A-N-I.
Vaibhav Therani.
Yes, get all the available
information on him.
Moosa?
What are we going to do
with so much water?
We'll need it.
This is not normal water.
I have mixed metallic impurities in it...
to make a colloidal solution.
This water is very useful, Sajid.
-Okay, sir. I am leaving,
-Good night.
Bye.
Vaibhav. Vaibhav Therani.
He's a production manager
at Orion Chemicals.
-Anything else?
-Not much.
-Milind.
-Sir.
Vaibhav's phone is switched off.
I spoke to his wife.
He's usually home by
this time, but not today.
Maybe he's in office.
We don't know exactly where he is.
What if Moosa and Sajid
planned to steal chemicals
from this factory?
Is it possible?
Milind, both of you...
go to Orion Chemicals and look around.
-Keep updating me.
-Yes, sir.
Okay?
Puneet, I need all the
details of Orion Chemicals.
Banking transactions, balance sheets,
funding sources, the lot.
-Open the gate.
-The factory's closed.
We want to meet your
manager, Vaibhav Therani.
He left for the day.
There's nobody inside.
You can come back tomorrow.
Shut up and open the door.
Please speak to the supervisor.
Get him.
Sir...
-Whom do you want to meet?
-Vaibhav Therani.
He left.
There's only the security staff now.
What are these tanks?
E1, E2, and E3.
How are they connected to each other?
E1 and E2 are connected to E3 via inlets.
What is the available stock
of methylamine and phosgene?
Answer the question!
E1 has 30 tons of phosgene
and chloroform compound.
E2 has 20 tons of methylamine.
What are you guys going to do?
Shut up and open the door.
Do you have a warrant?
You need a warrant?
If you act too smart,
I'll throw all of you behind bars.
Just open the gate.
Open it.
Stop them.
Moosa, there are a few
policemen downstairs.
-Why?
-I don't know.
-Bablu is with them. Hurry up.
-Okay.
Let's continue.
We'll go ahead.
You two, go there.
Let's go this way.
First, release the nitrogen from the tank.
That's very dangerous.
What are you doing?
Enter the password.
Do it!
-What's that?
-Control room.
We should take a look.
Ma'am, you don't have the permission.
Yeah, yeah!
I told you, Vaibhav's not here.
You'll get all of us in trouble.
Moosa, they're coming
towards the control room.
Come on, quick!
What did you do?
Are you out of your mind?
You are killing everybody in sight.
What do we do now?
Yes, sir?
Yes, sir. We are at the factory.
Yeah, Vaibhav is not here.
In fact, the factory is closed.
Right, sir.
Okay, bye.
Srikant wants us back.
Let's check it out anyway.
Let's go. Come.
Let's go.
What do we do now?
We got what we wanted from him.
I'll take care of the rest.
-Anything?
-Nothing at all, sir.
Let's go.
When MIC mixes with water,
it results in an exothermic reaction.
I've put phosgene and methylamine
in the third tank
so that they react.
We just need to disable
the scrubber tank.
You sound like...
a kid in a toy store.
You see this tank?
Do you know what it does?
It diverts all the toxic gases
from the factory
to a caustic soda chamber.
This removes all the
toxicity from the gases.
We need to disable this chamber.
Now one last thing.
You saw that flare tower outside?
It burns all the toxic gases
so that they don't mix
with the atmosphere.
Disabled.
Perfect.
Now Delhi will pay for its sins.
That was it?
That was a bit underwhelming.
Remember the 1984 Bhopal disaster?
Thousands suffered
a painful death.
Delhi will become
another Bhopal.
But a big blast
would've been more fun.
You don't get it.
Our purpose is not just
to kill them,
but also punish them...
and their future generations.
They will die a pitiful death.
Even the unborn will die
in its mother's womb.
And if some bastard does manage
to take birth
he'll live with a
crippling disease.
Then those bastards won't ever dare touch
our mothers and sisters.
They won't ever dare
kill our family members.
Tell me, is this
spectacle good enough for you?
Tiwari, please sit down.
You're stressing me out as well.
Milind said everything's okay
at the factory.
Circulate Vaibhav Therani's
photo to all police stations.
Ask someone to go
speak to his family.
Ask Milind and Zoya to go there.
-Are they back?
-They're on their way.
-Hurry up, man.
-I'm sorry.
Where the fuck is
Vaibhav Therani?
He's neither home nor at the factory.
Where do you think he'd be?
Some bar maybe?
Something seemed off at the factory.
Don't you think?
What?
Weren't the guards
a bit strange?
You know, come to think of it,
the other guard was also behaving
-very strangely.
-Something is amiss.
It's my instinct.
Do you remember the control room?
The guards told us the factory's shut.
Then why was the computer on?
And did you notice the water tanker
outside the factory?
-Yes, why?
-Nothing...
I just asked for a list
of stolen vehicles
in the last 48 hours in the area.
And I think I saw...
I knew it!
The water tanker.
-You think it's the same truck?
-Shall we go check?
Moosa Bhai!
-Are you two leaving?
-Yes.
Should I leave too?
-No.
-Yes.
Stay here.
Ensure that nobody gets in.
And leave before the factory
opens in the morning.
Alright.
You said all of Delhi will
be a graveyard by morning.
Yes.
And by that time we will be
far away from Delhi.
And what about them?
You asked them to stay there all night.
War involves sacrifices.
They will be martyred.
They will enjoy heaven.
Let her sit in the waiting room.
We're coming right away.
Tiwari...
she's in the waiting room.
-Who?
-Moosa's mother.
Have you thought about
what you're going to say?
There is only one way
to make a mother talk.
-Namaste.
This is my friend, JK.
Where is my son?
What did you do to him?
I want to meet him right now.
Please take me to him.
Ma'am... I know
very little Malayalam.
We can talk in Hindi.
-Hindi?
-Yes, Hindi.
When my mother passed away...
I wasn't able to speak to her.
The wind is strong.
The gas should engulf
Delhi in two hours.
Inshallah!
I can't wait to read the
papers tomorrow.
War is inevitable now.
There will be destruction
as far as the eye can see.
We have done what our brothers
were attempting for so many years.
You and I, Sajid.
What are you going
to do after this?
I'll go to my hometown.
Kerala?
Yes, Kasaragod.
I'll look for my mother.
-Fill it up.
-Okay, sir.
I'll be right back.
...mother of wanted terrorist Moosa Rahman
has appeared on national television
appealing to her son, to return.
Moosa, my son...
I refuse to believe whatever
I've heard about you.
I have come to Delhi to see you.
Where are you, son?
I want to meet you, Moosa.
You must prove their
allegations wrong.
Son, please call
me on this number.
Will you call me, Moosa?
Moosa, our years of hard work,
all our planning...
everything will go in vain.
We're not aborting the mission.
We're just delaying it by a few days.
We'll never get a better opportunity.
-So far, nothing's gone wrong.
-I know.
But I did it, didn't I?
And I can do it again.
We'll find another factory.
If not in Delhi, then in Mumbai.
-A larger number of people will die.
-Think about it.
For all you know, everything
must be over by now.
If the gas must've started leaking,
-we'll get stuck.
-So what do I do?
Let my mother die?
Sorry, Moosa. I won't let this happen.
Turn the car around.
Fuck! We have to inform Srikant!
Call for backup.
Listen to me, stop the car.
Moosa, don't force me to do this.
I said turn the car--
Fuck, there's no network.
Bablu Bhai, the police are here.
Milind!
Tiwari!
They found Moosa's body.