-How long till we're in Kochi?
-An hour.
The engine will heat up if
we continue at full speed.
This is the coast guard.
Identify yourself.
Over.
Don't stop. Ignore it.
Identify yourself.
-Keep going at full speed.
-And defy the coast guard?
Son of a bitch!
Keep going at full speed!
Unless you want to
join your captain.
Speed up, motherfucker!
Asif Bhai, what are you doing?
Moosa, stop it.
I know what I'm doing.
Son of a bitch!
It was not a good idea
to hijack the boat.
Shut up, Moosa!
We should've stayed in Lakshadweep
for a few more days.
We should've waited, Asif Bhai.
Moosa, for the last time.
Stay out of this.
I'm the one in command.
Abu, you're a mechanical engineer, right?
Can you fix the engine?
Let's fucking get them!
We'll take them by surprise.
Asif Bhai, I'm telling you,
it's not a good idea.
Shut up or I swear to God
I'll kill you first!
You son of a bitch!
What the fuck did you do?
I don't want to die here.
Not unless I kill you first!
All aboard, come onto the deck.
Drop your weapons.
I repeat, drop your weapons.
All aboard, come onto the deck.
Hands in the air.
I repeat, hands in the air.
Sri, did you take your tablets?
-I kept them on the table.
-Yes, I did.
Did you pay the electricity bill?
They've sent a disconnection notice.
I went there yesterday,
but the counter was closed.
Don't make excuses!
These days, everything can be done online.
Listen.
-Will you drop the kids to school?
-No, I can't!
Srikant, I do everything for the kids!
Can't you help me just this once?
I have a joint class and I'm not prepared!
Sri, please?
Please, Sri.
Just for today. Please?
Dhriti, stop it!
-No phones.
-Mom, I don't like Idlis.
Since when?
There's sambar,
chutney, and podi on the side.
What else do you want?
Mom, I don't like ghee anymore.
All you kids want is junk food.
You're satisfied only
when you eat that stuff.
Finish it.
I'm not hungry.
You'll stay hungry till lunch?
There are people starving to death
and here she is,
throwing tantrums.
Should I make a sandwich?
-You're spoiling them!
-I am not spoilt!
I love Idli, Suchi.
I know, darling.
That's why you are the sweetest.
Okay, I'm leaving. Bye.
-Bye, Suchi.
-Bye, Mom.
Bye, Suchi.
Eat this.
Hey, hurry up.
Dad, I don't like cheese.
Forgive me, Your Highness.
Would you like some junk food instead?
-Yes!
I want McDonald's.
It's hot! Let me switch on the AC.
-Dad!
-It's so pleasant.
Why do you need the AC?
Learn to breathe in fresh air.
Dad, when will we buy a new car?
When you start earning.
Dhriti!
There's a world outside your phone.
Look around once in a while.
She chats with boys all day.
Shut up, asshole!
Hey, what kind of language is that?
Mind your tongue
in front of me!
Dad, if you join a software company
you'll get a new car.
Why do you want to
continue with this job?
Because there's not much to do
in a government job.
-Right, Dad?
-Really?
Why haven't you accepted
my friend request yet?
You're not my friend,
you're my father.
She is scared, Dad.
If she accepts your friend request
you'll find out about her boyfriends.
Hey, you mother...
-What happened?
-Nothing.
-What did you say?
-Nothing, man.
Say it, asshole.
What is it?
Why are you cussing, man?
There are kids in the car!
Can't you see?
I'm letting you go
because of them.
Knock some sense into your dad!
Fucking idiot!
Why didn't you say it?
I knew what you were going to say.
What are you scared of, Dad?
Fine, I'll say it.
Hey there, mother-trucker!
Fuck! Shut the windows!
-What did you say?
-Nothing!
What did you say?
Say it again! Fucker!
Are you out of your mind?
If your mom finds out,
you'll be grounded.
And then blame me for it.
Ridiculous!
You go to such a posh school...
and use such crass words!
Now what's the difference
between you and that biker?
You want to grow up to be like him?
When I grow up,
I'll punch everybody in the face!
There's no fresh air,
the windows are up.
And you were apologizing
to that loser...
even though it was his fault!
I'm telling you...
the doctor accidentally
handed us somebody else's baby.
My real brother, that poor thing...
is with another family.
Take that!
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Don't do that, Dhriti!
-Stop it!
-Continue!
-Stop!
Let me drop you off at the gate.
-No!
My car's not that bad.
You guys don't know
how lucky you are!
I used to pedal five kilometers
to school every day.
And grandmother used
to swim across a river!
Ungrateful kids!
I'm on my way, damn it!
Get off my bloody ass!
You're quite early.
Just an hour late.
Don't kick a man when he is down!
I had to drop the kids off at school.
Sharma is going to fuck you up today.
Seriously?
Just a second.
There it is!
You're screwed!
Yes, sir.
There was a terrible accident.
Yes, sir. No, not me.
A taxi knocked down a Vada Pav vendor.
Sir, he lost a lot of blood.
Not the taxi driver.
The Vada Pav vendor.
I left after the
ambulance arrived.
I'm on my way.
I'm coming right away, sir.
Okay.
Sir, do I survive in this story?
That depends on the boss' mood.
Are you being trained
in making up stories?
You came up with one in a jiffy.
Get married.
You'll start inventing a lot of things!
-Hey, handsome. Spare some change for me?
-I don't have it.
-Good morning. All good?
-Good morning, sir.
-Looking good!
-Sir.
Srikant, JK...
you're late for the meeting again.
Really? Are we?
Sorry.
Upstairs.
These three were trying to
cross in through the sea route.
They hijacked a fishing boat
and killed the captain.
Caught in Indian waters, south of Kochi.
They're in the coast guard's custody.
Moinuddin alias Asif.
Trivandrum bus blast.
Mysore High Court blast...
A suspect in both the cases.
The boat was registered
in Lakshadweep.
Our guess is they were
hiding there for a few days.
Who are the other two?
All from Kerala.
They stay in Asif's neighboring villages.
They had disappeared
a few years ago.
It was suspected that
they had gone to Syria
to join the ISIS.
Although there is no
criminal record against them.
Moosa Rahman from Kasaragod,
24 years old, IIT Kanpur!
Imtiaz Aboobacker...
There are orders from Delhi...
to interrogate them and
gather intelligence.
The court has granted
us a week's custody.
The CISF team will be
handing them over today.
Both of you go and supervise it.
Force One will be there
for tactical support.
The flight from Kochi
will land at 2:00 p.m.
Don't take a detour to eat Vada Pav.
No, sir.
Sir, he's the one fond of it.
I only give him company.
Okay, sir.
Sir, about the home loan...
-Can we talk about this later?
-I was just asking, sir.
I have informed HR...
to prioritize your case.
When there's an update, I'll tell you.
Okay, sir. Thank you, sir.
There's a junior analyst
joining us today,
transferred from IB.
One of you do the orientation.
-Okay--
-I'll do it, sir!
Okay, sir.
Thank you, sir.
The recruit!
That's why you were so keen!
Have some shame, Talpade.
She's a new recruit.
Don't be jealous, Tiwari.
It's injurious to your health.
Welcome to Threat Analysis
and Surveillance Cell.
We report to the NIA
and we work
in close coordination with RAW
and Force One.
Our main job, of course, is to
predict attacks before they happen.
As you can see, we keep
a very low profile.
We track everything.
From social media posts,
to chat messages. Everything.
The algorithm filters any
suspicious activities
anything, anyone
that could be a
potential terror threat.
Privacy is a myth,
just like democracy.
Although there are some apps
which we haven't been able to
track, like Telegram.
What about the dark net?
Most of the threats
are found there, right?
Correct.
Nice.
-Do you have a boyfriend?
-What?
Do you have a boyfriend?
-Sir, why is that relevant?
-Very relevant!
Only those, whom we trust the most
can know about our work.
Of course, sir.
I have been briefed about this
by the department.
-I'm sure I can--
-I know.
I was just reiterating
an important point.
Of course, sir.
Call me JK.
-Of course, Mr. JK.
-Just JK.
-Of course, JK.
-Okay.
-Shall we?
-After you.
-Would you like some tea?
-No, thank you.
And this is senior analyst,
Srikant Tiwari.
The Srikant Tiwari?
"The"?
What have I done now?
Sir, we have heard
a lot about you.
Your work in the field
is still used as a case study
in the academy.
It's so good to
meet you in person, sir.
Where are you from?
Sir, I am Zoya from Lucknow.
How one misses the
grand attractions of Lucknow!
The food there is delicious!
I am Srikant Tiwari,
originally from Banaras.
-Nice to meet you, sir.
-How did you land here?
It just happened, sir.
I was pursuing engineering.
One day, I realized it wasn't for me.
So I switched careers.
And you landed in Intelligence.
It's a long story.
I'll share it some other time.
Well, you'll get to learn
a lot from him.
He's got two lovely kids,
and a very beautiful wife!
-Shall we?
-Sure.
-Would you like to join us?
-Me?
You will get to learn
from an expert and a veteran.
Shall we go?
-Srikant Tiwari.
-Hello.
JK Talpade.
-Hi.
-Hello.
-Zoya.
-Hi.
-From TASC.
-Imran Pasha, Force One.
Have you been newly posted in Mumbai?
Yes, I was with the NSG.
The flight is delayed.
Please wait there.
It's my responsibility to safely
deliver those three to you.
So just stay out
of my way, please.
Okay.
What's his problem?
Forget about it.
Does he think he's Rambo?
Ignore.
Just tell him,
we are field agents.
We aren't here to...
Let it be. Come on!
Thank you.
What?
Asshole.
I hope the sugar's okay.
Mr. Srikant Tiwari?
We are calling from
Saint Archer's School.
This is regarding
your daughter, Dhriti.
Yes, tell me.
-Your daughter--
-Can I please talk to him?
Dad, can you please
come here immediately?
-But what happened?
-Nothing.
They are just creating a ruckus
over a little tablet.
Tablet? What tablet?
-It's an anti-spasmodic tablet.
-What?
-Why?
-Dad!
Anti-spasmodic tablet!
Okay, right.
Alright.
Don't worry, just relax.
-Did you call your mother?
-If I do, she'll scold me.
But how can I just leave?
I am busy!
You can't just call me
and expect me to show up.
So, you are not coming?
Darling, it's just not
possible for me right now.
Your mom will handle this better.
Why don't you call her instead?
She knows these kinds of things.
Dad, these people are going berserk.
They want to suspend me and shit.
Suspend?
No. No way!
Stop whining! I'll be here
as soon as the flight lands.
And I'll do the paperwork alone?
You've already started
working alone, haven't you?
Enjoy your coffee.
Tell me the truth.
You haven't taken any
dubious tablets, have you?
Dad, my stomach is hurting!
Really?
Okay. Sit down.
I'll handle it, don't worry.
-Mr. Tiwari.
-Yes, ma'am.
This is not like
any other school.
In this school, we take
discipline very seriously.
-Yes, ma'am.
-If we are not disciplined
how are we different from animals?
Yes, you are absolutely right, Sister.
Yes, we take our
rules very strictly.
This is not a light matter that
we are discussing, Mr. Tiwari.
Very sorry, Sister.
I left an important meeting midway--
What is more important...
than raising your daughter?
They are here.
Your daughter was caught
consuming this tablet, Mr. Tiwari.
Do you know what it is?
I am sorry, Sister.
Yes, it's...
an anti-spasmodic tablet.
That's what she says.
Do you know really know what this is?
Is it prescribed?
I understand your concern, Sister.
But Dhriti is not
that kind of a girl.
She's a very good girl.
-And I know my daughter.
-"I know my daughter"?
Your daughter comes to my
school five days in a week.
How much time do you spend
with her, Mr. Tiwari?
I am sorry, Sister.
My colleague JK,
is suffering from clinical depression.
He recently got divorced.
He's unable to come to terms with it.
And he's very introverted.
He doesn't open up to people.
That's why he keeps calling me.
And I fear that
if I don't answer his calls...
he might commit suicide.
Yes.
What were you saying, Sister?
Sir, I am not a terrorist.
I am just a computer engineer.
I haven't done anything, sir.
If my mother finds out...
she'll die of shock, sir.
Please, let me go.
Shut up!
Don't beg to these infidels, you dog!
You there, shut up!
I know what you're thinking.
"What are we doing?
What's the point of it all?
Anybody could do this."
-No, I wasn't thinking--
-No! You're right.
This is not our job.
This handover is supposed
to be a Force One operation.
But it is important
for us to be here...
to supervise.
Supervision is very critical.
Son of a bitch!
Shit!
Shit! They are gone!
-We need backup.
-Get on top!
Sir, they are heading
towards the slums.
Since this is her first offense...
and the classmate
didn't take the tablet...
I might go lenient on Dhriti
this one time.
Mr. Tiwari.
Don't make me explain this
-all over again--
-Fuck!
I have to go!
JK is on the terrace.
He said he'll jump.
-Mr. Tiwari--
-Sister, please try and understand.
I have to go and stop him, please!
Are you serious?
What about your daughter?
I'll have to suspend her, Mr. Tiwari!
Please let me go.
We'll talk about the suspension tomorrow.
Okay? Please try and understand.
-She's in the mood to suspend you today.
-What?
But you were supposed to help me!
What did you do?
Don't worry.
I'll handle everything tomorrow.
And tell your mother that the
principal was in a horrible mood!
No, I am not going
to lie to her.
What?
You're not going to lie?
And what about
all the lies I tell her to save you?
Just wait till your mother
finds out about this!
You don't know what's
in store for you!
I'll be back.
They must be hiding
somewhere in here.
They have guns.
Don't think twice. Just shoot.
-Okay, sir.
-Give me your gun.
Shoot to kill.
Okay, sir.
Go upstairs! Go!
Get inside! Inside!
Up! Upstairs!
Yes, sir.
I spotted them.
They are going towards the church.
Asif Bhai, listen to me!
Shut up!
I don't want to die unnecessarily!
Will you shut up?
Let me talk to them.
We can surrender.
-We can surrender.
-They're trying to kill us!
Take it! Or I'll kill you!
Asif Bhai...
Let us get out of here.
Move it! Hurry!
Move away!
Can you see him?
If you get a clear shot, take it.
-Come, "The" Srikant Tiwari!
-Sorry, man.
Pasha's lost it!
He's killing them all, one by one.
He's already killed two.
How much time more?
I need backup!
Fast!
Pasha!
You want to kill them all?
We need them alive!
If we hadn't killed them,
we'd all be dead by now.
Let us do our job!
TASC is a part of this operation.
-It's not yours alone.
-Those fuckers killed my boys!
That doesn't mean you kill everybody.
Who the hell will we interrogate?
Stand down.
But if he shoots even once...
I will go inside and shoot his head off.
Backup on the way, sir.
What's his name?
-I'm not sure--
-Sir, Moosa. Moosa Rahman.
The one who got shot
first was Aboobacker.
The other one is Asif, their leader.
Moosa!
Moosa Rahman!
That's your name, right?
Put your hands in the air...
and come out.
Do you understand Hindi?
I haven't done anything!
I didn't start all of this.
Listen, Moosa, both your friends...
have been killed.
If you want to stay alive
put your hands in the air and come out!
They are not my friends.
I did not want any of this.
But Asif never fucking listened to me.
I am just a computer engineer.
I just wanted to get out of Syria
and go back home, to my mother.
I just want to go
back to my mother!
Get some information on his mother.
You want to go back to
your mother, right?
Then you shouldn't give it
a second thought!
Surrender.
I promise you,
I'll take you to your mother.
You bloody infidel!
I know what you will do.
As soon as I come out,
you will shoot me.
Just like you shot
the other two.
No, that won't happen.
I give you my word.
I don't trust you at all!
You don't trust me, right?
But... I trust you.
I will leave this pistol behind
and come to you.
Got it? I am coming.
Are you crazy, you bloody idiot?
-I know what I am doing.
-Balls!
-Why are you becoming the bait?
-So what do I do?
If I don't go in there and talk to him
that fucker standing behind you
will blow his brains out.
What if that asshole shoots you?
Why do you always
think negative, fucker?
Just pray to Lord Ganesha
that nothing happens to me.
-Hail Lord Ganesha.
-Hail him!
Exactly.
Look, Moosa.
I'm leaving my gun behind.
Look, I am unarmed.
All right?
I am trusting you with my life!
My colleagues think I'm a moron,
for doing this.
Shit!
Don't shoot me accidentally.
May I come in?
Hail Lord Ganesha!
Close the door!
Shit, shit!
I am the only one who wants you alive.
Moosa...
-you need to see a doctor urgently!
-Shut up!
I know you are not like the other two.
I know you are not a terrorist.
-I haven't done anything!
-I know!
But... my mother will think...
The poor thing.
How will I face her?
She will die of shame...
when she finds out that...
Moosa, you are losing a lot of blood.
If you don't do
anything about it,
it won't be good for you.
Moosa, let me take you to a hospital.
Don't you dare!
-Moosa.
-Don't you come near me.
Do you really think
I don't know what's going on?
Don't come near me.
All right.
Please, Moosa.
Please.
Believe me...
I know exactly what you're going through.
I was in Nagaland.
I got the news my mother was very ill.
By the time I came home,
she had already been cremated.
I didn't get to see my mother
when she was dying, Moosa.
The mother used work as a maidservant
and toil all day,
doing menial labor
so that her son could study
and achieve something in life.
But her son wasn't present
when she was breathing her last.
I do and I will regret it...
for the rest of my life.
Moosa, for me it's my country.
For you, it's jihad.
It is important.
But it's a mother we're talking about.
And your mother...
would rather see you alive than dead.
Moosa, come out.
Hey, gun down!
Stand down!
Give me a soda.
One for me too.
How did you convince him to surrender?
The same old...
"Mother."
Killed your mother again?
I can't help it.
The "mother" sentiment
really is something.
I think I should get a ritual done
for my mother's well-being.
When your mother finds out that
you kill her every other day...
she'll perform your last rites!
How are they doing?
Sir, Aboobacker is dead and Asif
is in a very critical condition.
How was your first day?
-First day!
-She's learnt a lot today.
Of course, sir.
Sir, you were
absolutely unbelievable.
The way you handled
Moosa Rahman, that was...
-Thank you.
-Excuse me.
You need to handle the wife now.
That's important as well.
Yes, Suchi.
When are you going to
pick up the kids from school?
I am there.
At the gate, I mean.
Which gate?
The school gate.
Atharv!
Dhriti!
I can see the kids.
I have already picked them up.
If you have more children,
please tell me their names.
Tomorrow, I'll pick them up too!
How about a drink?
There's going to be
a world war at home.
If guns are going to be fired,
you need one.
It will act as a bulletproof jacket.
Major Sameer is coming.
Faizan Bhai.
I hope you liked the
arrangements we've made.
Of course!
You have made
excellent arrangements.
General Ansari sends his regards.
Wa alaykumu as-salam.
Please thank him for his hospitality.
Of course.
How did the Americans find out
that I'm not in Syria?
Word gets around, Faizan Bhai.
The situation is bad in Islamabad.
The Prime Minister is trying
hard to impress the Americans.
It will be better if you lie low.
-What do you mean?
-Don't worry.
We are here for your protection.
The Americans won't find you
as long as we're around.
The CIA has announced
a million-dollar reward for my capture.
And you say I shouldn't worry?
I...
-Please have some.
-Let's talk outside. Come.
The mujahid you sent from Syria
was captured in India.
What?
Unfortunately, their boat was
spotted by the coast guard.
-Is he a martyr now?
-No.
That is the problem.
What do you want from me?
We need another mujahid...
who's already in India.
First, you need to tell me
about the mission.
It's a top-secret mission, bhai.
Only a few know about it.
Then include me among them, Major.
India has never retaliated
to Pakistan's provocations
with a major assault.
We got the parliament attacked.
There was 26/11...
but the Indian government is fast asleep.
It's time to wake them up.
We'll make the Indians...
scream for revenge.
It'll be clearly construed
as an act of war.
The Indian government will have
to declare war on Pakistan.
This war will enable us to
conduct a coup in Pakistan.
It's time...
that Pakistan shows its
strength to the world.
That's why we have
named the mission
Mission Zulfiqar.
Wonderful!
The name of the sacred sword!
Does Islamabad know about this?
No.
I have all the details for this mission.
The ones who are going to
fulfill this mission
know only about their
particular tasks.
There's a young man...
who's destined to carry this out.
But it's a bit difficult to tame him.
In Intelligence lingo, he's a lone wolf.
He's overwhelmingly passionate.
He wages jihad in his own style.
He's preparing for something as we speak.
We can recruit him for this mission.
He'll listen to me.
Then it's time to send him a message.
Talpade, look at this.
This place costs 14,000 rupees
per square foot.
It has a gym and
a swimming pool as well.
The cost is 16,000 rupees
in other buildings.
-That's good.
-It's a good deal, right?
It's good.
But I don't understand this obsession.
-What?
-Of buying a house!
This is Mumbai!
What do you get here for a house?
A bloody matchbox!
You become a bloody matchstick inside!
I say rent is a wiser option.
Your math makes no sense...
when it comes to emotions.
A man should have something
that he can call his own.
Something Suchi and the kids
can call home.
Suchi is always so busy
handling the house.
And even if I want to,
I just can't help her.
I can't stop working, right?
And if a man can't even leave
behind a house, then it's...
Don't talk about dying, man!
It's a fact.
In our line of work,
we can't predict when we're gonna die.
How long will I lie to Suchi?
That all I do is
pass files around in the office.
That I don't work on the field
or take risks.
You know what you need?
Don't say Bangkok.
Let's do a surgical strike
in Bangkok tonight--
I said no Bangkok!
We'll enter at night,
and leave early in the morning.
The mission will be a success
and the enemy won't know what happened.
I'm telling you, Tiwari, you need this.
And betray Suchi?
I'll advise her the same.
Even she should enjoy herself.
Why should boys have all the fun?
Why not?
That music can drive anybody crazy!
You scared me!
Dhriti has been suspended from school.
What?
What were you doing with those tablets?
Is that why we send you to school?
And she was giving it
to other students as well.
-What?
-Mom, I told you it was a--
Shut up!
Don't argue!
You have an answer
for everything.
Just like your dad.
One lie after another!
And you!
The principal was talking to you
and you just left!
No...
I needed to leave immediately.
How can you be so insensitive, Sri?
Do you have no interest
in your daughter's future?
Of course, I do.
Then you wouldn't have
left in the first place.
It was an emergency.
What is it with you and
your "emergencies"?
Come on, not again!
-Why don't you understand?
-Because I can't.
Make me understand, I am listening.
Just a second.
HAS THE CIVIL WAR BEGUN?
IS THE BULLETPROOF JACKET WORKING?
-Go on, finish it.
-No, that's fine.
I am sure it must be JK.
He's your first wife anyway.
He was asking about an important file.
Suchi! Please listen to me.
If it wasn't important,
I would've talked to
the principal all day.
But there was a routine handover
at the airport, that's why...
Actually, there was a quarterly
meeting in the office.
The boss had flown down from Delhi.
Then, I was bombarded with phone calls
because they couldn't find
a file for the meeting.
I had to leave.
Otherwise, why would I go?
What were you saying about the airport?
What airport?
-Did I say "airport"?
-I am tired, Sri!
There's something important
at work every day!
But your family's important as well.
Come on, I know that.
You will go to Dhriti's school
and fix the situation tomorrow!
I promise, I will fix it.
I really hope it's not
your field work again.
Of course not, Suchi.
Dad...
can you guess the song?
We are wasting our money
on this little chimp.
Listen, son!
No more music classes for you.
We did not give birth to you.
You came into this world by accident!
Put that aside, right now.
After so many classes! Useless!
Feeling better?
I hope you know...
if you ever want to talk
about anything
I am here for you.
Like I said before,
you are a big girl now.
You should consider me your best friend.
And what's the first rule of friendship?
No more secrets.
You call yourself our "best friend."
But whenever you want,
you turn into a mother!
Why are you still up?
Go to sleep.
You have ten seconds.
This is not best friend behavior.