Say something, Doctor!
How many cigarettes
do you smoke in a day?
I smoke only when I'm stressed.
And how often are you stressed?
And drinks?
Well...
once in a while.
Sometimes, you know...
two, maybe three.
At the most, four or five.
In a week?
Daily?
-And meat?
-Absolutely not.
My family is vegetarian, Doctor.
Whenever I eat out,
otherwise never.
And how often do you eat out?
Srikant, your blood sugar levels
are fluctuating again.
Do you still feel giddy sometimes?
Do you keep chocolates with you?
Doctor, I eat more chocolates
than my kids do.
I always keep some with me.
-Do you want one?
-Look at your report!
Try keeping your cholesterol
under control.
You have to quit eating meat,
fried food and smoking.
And one drink a day
should be the maximum.
-And minimum?
-Do you not want to live?
Come on, Doctor.
What's left to stay alive for?
-This is not a joke!
-I know, Doctor. But...
please stop scaring me.
I'll wet my pants.
And stop being so stressed out.
Take some small breaks in between.
Spend some time with your family.
-Don't think about work--
-Just a second.
Yes, JK. What happened?
What?
Kala Ghoda?
I'll be right there!
-I haven't finished.
-I got it, sir.
I have to avoid drinking, smoking
fried food and stress.
Basically, I have to stop living.
Why don't I just kill myself?
Move back! Come on!
Walking with my friends...
Be very calm.
You know what you have to do.
-Put the jacket on him.
-Yes, sir.
Radio check, radio check.
-Step aside.
-Move.
Please step aside.
If the bomb goes off,
you'll get a great selfie
of your bloody remains, moron.
-Move.
-Step aside.
I'll be giving you
instructions over the radio.
Just follow them. Okay?
-Now get going.
-What the fuck is this?
At least give me a decent suit!
Quickly get some duct tape.
Did you check the
scooter's number plate?
-Whose name is it registered under?
-It's a fake.
Chassis number?
BDU. Come in, BDU.
-Who's at the scooter?
-Chirayu.
Chirayu, come in.
I need the chassis number.
What the fuck!
Do I look like a mechanic to you?
Please, just check it.
It'll blast, fuck off!
Dumbass.
Write down the details.
There is no chassis number.
It's a stolen vehicle.
Not available.
Did you check the CCTV footage?
CCTV...
One minute.
Chirayu, if you have any doubts,
abort the mission.
I repeat, if you're not sure,
just abort the mission. Over.
Fuck!
Give me a puff.
I need the CCTV footage from
all the cameras in the area.
Yeah, 9:00 p.m. to 6:00 a.m.
Yeah, I'll hold. Sure.
Hey. Here you go.
Latest code names and transcripts,
please keep them in the data base.
How did this happen?
How the hell did we miss this?
The PM is asking the NIA why
we could not stop this attack.
TASC was created...
to prevent such attacks!
So, what the fuck went wrong?
Sir, this doesn't seem to be the work
of a sleeper cell.
It looks like a lone wolf's job.
A solo operation, sir.
Otherwise, something would've shown up
on the radar.
-We are investigating--
-Sir.
Sir, I think it's a one-off attack.
You better be sure.
This is no bigger than you say it is.
Sir, I think it's not possible.
Sir, I think it's possible.
I'm sorry, sir.
But...
we need to thoroughly
investigate this, sir.
I need this report on the PM's desk,
tomorrow morning.
Do you understand?
-Yes, sir.
-Sri, you guys can leave.
-Thank you, sir.
-Sharma, please sit down.
-And Sri.
-Yes, sir?
I want you to come with
me to the airport, please.
Of course, sir.
How the hell did we miss this?
We have all the
infrastructure in the world
and not even a single red flag?
Red flags only get raised
when the threat pattern
is more than 50%.
None of the threat patterns
were more than 50%.
Have you heard of this thing
called "human intelligence"?
How can we always fucking
depend on those stupid machines.
Sri, I am on it.
Didn't the doctor ask you
to quit smoking?
Give me a puff.
Halfway into the year,
and we've already lost 42 lives.
Another such blast and...
the toll could reach a hundred.
Sir!
Hello, Doctor.
Srikant Tiwari, NIA.
-Any progress?
-No progress.
We don't know when he will
come out of coma
or if he ever will.
But we're keeping his vitals stable
so that he stays alive.
I'm not hungry.
You'll recover only if you eat.
Medicines won't work
on an empty stomach.
The rest is up to you.
Where are you from?
Kottayam.
I'm from Kasaragod.
How did you know I'm a Malayali?
I just guessed.
Did you grow up here,
or in your hometown?
I've been brought up in Mumbai.
That's why my Malayalam
is not very good.
Just like my Hindi.
Sir, what are you doing?
You're not allowed here.
Please wait outside.
You're disturbing the patient.
I am from NIA.
-Oh.
-Yeah.
It's okay, Sister Mary.
-Mary, yes.
-Nice meeting you.
Don't worry.
I'll look after him.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Bye, sister.
Moosa, my man!
Living the life!
Enjoying a luxurious stay, aren't you?
When people like me fall ill
we have to stand in long queues
in government hospitals.
But they've blocked
an entire ward just for you.
Sir...
can I ask you something?
Easy.
-Do you still regret it?
-Regret what?
That you couldn't see your
mother when she passed away.
Of course.
I regret it every single day.
I want to meet my mother.
Sir, please.
I want the same for you.
But if the department
asks me how you're helping us,
and why am I being so nice to you,
what will I say?
You help me and I assure you
that you will meet your mother.
That's my promise!
When did you join ISIS?
Three years ago...
I left Kasaragod.
Asif...
was already in Syria.
He arranged everything for me.
They had me handle their websites.
Websites?
Yes.
What did you think?
They can't even stand
the sight of Indians.
They treat us the same way you do.
Indian-Muslims don't even get
proper work out there.
We get jobs like cleaning toilets...
sweeping and mopping.
If you're educated,
they put you on a computer.
Asif...
Wait, let me.
Easy.
I was tired, sir.
I just wanted to
get out of that place.
That's when I came to know
that Asif was planning
a mission in India.
I begged Asif to include me in it.
It was the only way
I could came back to India.
Did Asif ever mention
anything about the mission?
Whenever I asked him...
he'd say that something big
was going to happen.
Something big?
Anything else?
Try to remember.
No, he didn't tell me anything else.
Try to recall.
What big thing was he referring to?
What does it matter, sir?
Now that Asif and Abu are no more
there will be no mission, right?
Asif is alive.
He's in a coma.
He can regain consciousness
at any moment.
And once he does...
we won't need you anymore.
We'll extract the information from him
one way or the other.
That's why I'm telling you,
think it through but hurry up.
Or else...
you can tell me
what I should say to your mother
once you go to jail.
Let me know.
Sir?
I've quit.
-How are Suchi and the kids?
-They are...
They're doing good, sir.
I've trained you for three years.
I can tell when
you're lying to me, you know?
It's nothing, sir.
It's just that Suchi thinks,
I should quit this job
and take up a private job.
She makes sense.
There's more money, security
and less risk in a private job.
But never forget why you chose this job.
Right, sir.
When I was in Nagaland...
I almost lost my life in an IED attack.
My wife was exasperated.
She told me to quit this job.
But after a lot of arguments,
I convinced her
that I would stop risking my life
and just do paperwork.
-What happened then, sir?
-What do you think?
She still thinks I do paperwork.
Back then, it wasn't very difficult
to convince people.
In those days, there was neither
social media, nor many TV channels.
There was just one channel.
I have been in your position.
Somebody has to step up
and do this job.
When the country is safe...
only then can our families be safe.
I have a lot of expectations from you.
What did the doctor say?
Everything is fine.
Care to elaborate?
You know what they always say.
The same damn thing, rephrased.
"Don't stress, control your sugar,
avoid eating fried food."
My sugar's already in control.
And I'll quit meat.
Everything will be fine.
What about your smoking and drinking?
That's fine.
As long as it's in moderation.
Is that what the doctor said?
Doctors are never straightforward.
Always beating around the bush.
But that's the gist of it.
Are you going to meet
Dhriti's principal tomorrow?
Or, as usual, I'll have to...
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
The flute's gone?
Major Sameer, what's this we
hear about Mission Zulfiqar?
With such a dismal start...
how do we trust you
to fulfill the mission?
How confident are we about
the success of this mission?
Don't you think we should
look at some alternatives?
Your doubts are justified, gentlemen.
There have been a few hurdles.
But don't lose hope.
We are going to succeed in this mission.
We hope you're aware of
its importance, Major.
Mission Zulfiqar is important for us
and our country.
The future of our country and its people
depend entirely on the mission's success.
There was a time
when the very mention
of the Pakistani army
would make the Indians wet their pants.
But now those Indians cross the border,
enter our homes,
and carry out surgical strikes.
At this rate,
we'll not only lose Kashmir
but also Baluchistan.
It's time that
Pakistan gets the respect
it has always deserved in this world.
I'll not disappoint you.
Mission Zulfiqar will succeed,
by hook or by crook.
Any news about our fighter?
He's in the hospital, sir.
But the good news is that
the Indians are clueless about our plan.
Faizan has suggested another fighter.
-I've heard that he's a capable man.
-Very good.
But he's just carried out
a scooter blast in Mumbai.
And now the Indian authorities
must be on his trail.
You don't need to worry about that, sir.
I am monitoring their investigation.
I'll make sure they don't
find our fighter.
Be careful, Sameer.
We can't afford to make
any mistakes at this stage.
Sure, sir.
A toast to the
Islamic Republic of Pakistan!
-Cheers!
Just watch.
They'll waste the entire week
on deciding the curriculum.
Correct.
They won't even add anything new.
It'll be the same outdated syllabus.
-Correct.
-I don't understand why
everyone feels compelled
to give some input.
Stop laughing.
-What do you care now?
-I didn't say a word.
Okay, listen.
I have thought a lot about this.
You've been doing this job
for nine years
and you're good at it.
But you hate it.
I know this job gives you
flexibility, security, benefits.
Even the pay scale is decent.
It has everything.
Except for one thing.
Challenges.
You're the kind who
thrives on challenges.
Maybe you don't realize it.
-I'll be straightforward--
-Come on, Arvind.
Just quit this stupid job
and join our company.
You're getting a job
without an interview.
What more do you want?
Are you done?
I knew you'd come back to this topic.
And you know it's not happening.
-But--
-Let's go, I need to get to class!
-Good morning, sir.
-Good morning, ma'am.
Good morning.
I hope you know this.
Some of the students here
think that we're a thing.
-What?
-Yes.
-No!
Really?
Go on.
Alright, stop.
That's it.
We have to demolish all of this.
-Right from here, all the way over there.
-Excuse me.
What's going on?
-Are you the principal?
-Yes.
Here's a notice for you.
We'd sent you a notice before
but you didn't respond to us.
This structure is illegal,
we need to demolish it.
We did not receive any such notice.
And please get rid
of this bulldozer.
Ma'am, we're just following the orders.
If you have a problem,
please call up the BMC Commissioner.
Let me just do my job.
And shut the gate.
We don't want the kids
to get in the way.
Ask them to close that gate.
-Wait, wait!
-Ma'am, we have orders.
-Hey, let's begin.
-Good morning, ma'am.
Mr. Tiwari, please, not now!
What's happening, buddy?
We're here to work, not explain
ourselves to everybody.
Step aside!
Take the vehicle ahead.
Come on, tell me.
Mr. Tiwari, this does not
concern you, please!
Ma'am, let me just talk to him.
What do you mean "talk to him"?
I can also speak English, okay?
-Let's get going.
-Mr. Tiwari.
Just a second, ma'am.
Don't you have any manners?
-What?
-Don't mess with me.
I'm being respectful and so should you.
Hello!
Shut that damn thing.
Or I'll come up there and thrash you.
-Shut it!
-Mr. Tiwari.
Mr. Tiwari, why are you--
Sister, please.
Let me talk to him.
Didn't you hear me?
Shut the damn bulldozer!
One phone call and
you'll be begging for forgiveness.
-Who are you?
-I am from the BMC.
Got it?
You want to call someone? Go ahead.
Go on, do it!
These days, you fine an idiot
a hundred rupees
and they dial the
Chief Minister's number!
There's nothing you can do.
This is the BMC Commissioner's order.
Step aside! Roll ahead!
Are you done?
Who's your commissioner?
Mhatre, right?
Do you know his full name?
GM Mhatre.
What's up, Mhatre?
How are you?
Not at all.
I'm at my daughter's school right now.
Sir.
Sorry, ma'am.
I didn't know that sir would...
They just told us that
we had to go to another school.
-Another school?
-Yes.
Sorry, we had the orders so...
-Thank you, sir.
-Okay.
Get the vehicle out!
Thank you, Mr. Tiwari
for saving our school!
You don't need to thank me, ma'am.
It's my duty to help.
What are you looking at?
Apologize.
I am sorry, ma'am.
I...
I'll take your leave now.
I just wanted to know how long
will she be suspended for.
Oh, no. I'm going to
revoke her suspension.
No, no.
You don't need to do this, ma'am.
She should realize her mistake!
I think she's realized her mistake.
Dhriti, you're very lucky
to have a father like him.
You should learn from him.
Now, could you excuse us
for two minutes?
Yes, sure.
-Mr. Tiwari.
-Yes, ma'am.
-This is a tender age.
-Yes.
And there are a lot of
bad influences around them.
You know, drugs, alcohol, cigarettes...
I hope my name didn't come up.
The principal did ask me.
But I told her it was my tablet.
You're safe.
And then the guy was like...
"Sir, step aside.”
And the principal was like,
"Mr. Tiwari, just stay out of it.”
And Dad was like, you know,
"Ma'am please be quiet.
Let me do the talking.”
Listen up, musical prodigy!
Your sister's saying something important.
-I am listening, kind of.
-"Kind of!"
And then, Dad stopped him,
called up somebody
and gave him the phone.
And you know what that
man said after the call?
"Sorry, sir. Sorry, ma'am."
And then he left with his bulldozer.
Tell them what happened next.
Shouldn't you tell the whole story?
Dad, don't push it, okay?
What do you mean?
You should tell them the whole thing.
Alright.
She can resume going to school, right?
Of course. No excuses.
Ma'am, hello!
After dinner, keep your schoolbag
and the uniform ready.
Don't look for your books
in the morning. Okay?
You didn't blackmail them, did you?
-What do you mean?
-Well, you could have...
dug up old records and
threatened the poor Sister.
Is that what you
think of your husband?
Don't act all innocent.
I know how you get things done.
Listen.
-I wanted to discuss something.
-Tell me.
What if I quit this job and...
try something new?
I mean, I've been doing the
same job for nine years.
Suchi...
people spend their entire
lives doing the same job.
I cannot take it anymore.
I am tired!
Suchi, what's the problem?
It's a good job, you're back home in time
and you get to spend some
time with the kids as well.
What more do we want?
Is it just my responsibility
to spend time with the kids?
-That's not what I meant
-Remember what we had discussed?
That both of us will take
some time out for the kids
and equally share their responsibility.
Do you think I don't want
to spend time with them?
You know the nature of my job!
What's the point of such a job where
you don't have time for family?
Suchi, why are you doing this?
Sri, you told me that
you'll quit this job...
and look for something
where you won't be
slogging it out on the field.
I don't do anything field-related.
I just pass around files
in the office all day!
-You know what the problem is?
-What?
You expect me
to be very understanding
about your job.
But when it comes to me,
you have no empathy!
Have you ever asked me
if I am happy with my job?
You know what?
I've made up my mind.
I want to try something new.
That's it.
I can't spend my whole life
giving the same damn
lecture year after year.
I'm sorry.
Sri?
-Sri!
-It's urgent.
I'll have to run!
-What's the alert?
-I'm patching you in. Take a look.
There's a group on Facebook
called Almighty's Army.
We've been monitoring it
for quite some time now.
They've been orange-flagged
16 times in the last six months.
We've been monitoring
three members closely.
Arshad Dalal.
Hussain Gudur
and Riyaz Younis.
They work for a gaming company.
Initek Games.
All three of them have
been to Saudi together for hajj.
They also went to
Dubai for four days.
And Hussain has recently applied
for a visa to Turkey.
-Turkey, the backdoor to Syria.
-Yes.
They were in constant touch
with the ISIS leads in Syria
through video conferencing.
It is Allah's will
that we have the strength
to wage war against the infidels.
We are at war not with
one country but--
The first voice is from Syria.
Voice-print analysis shows
that this voice belongs to
a known online
recruiter from ISIS.
The second voice,
is from Pakistan.
And Arshad, Hussain,
and Riyaz, were on this call.
How's this connected to the blast?
Here.
So what? A lot of people
celebrated that accident.
Yes, sir.
But not before the news
made the headlines.
The news about the blast
broke out after an hour.
And there was no mention
of Kala Ghoda anywhere.
But Riyaz put up this post
just ten minutes after the blast.
Team meeting. Twenty minutes.
-Right.
-Okay, sir.
Run along.
What do you think?
Is this evidence enough to arrest them?
Sir, I think these boys are plain stupid.
They must've been brainwashed
about the glory of jihad
and now they're
running after Jannat.
But I'm sure they
knew about the plan.
And they can lead us
to the scooter bomber.
Pasha, how much time will it take
for your team to get ready?
Won't take long, sir.
What's your plan?
The plan is to catch the
three of them together, no matter what.
Because if eve one of them finds out,
that the other has been caught
we'll end up with only one.
So, we need them all to be in one place.
That has to be in their office.
Of course.
Let's go and wish them all
a Happy New Year.
-But we'll have to be very careful.
-Yes, very careful.
This is the IT hub of the city.
We need to work very discreetly.
Unlike last time,
we cannot rain bullets on them.
Sir, I am not a barbarian.
But if anybody fires at my men,
I won't bow down in front of them.
Nobody's asking you to do that!
-But at least spare the civilians!
-Okay!
Is that possible?
-Yes, sir.
-Alright then.
I don't want a commotion.
I want a simple,
in-and-out operation.
I don't want any media
attention on the case.
-Okay?
-Yes, sir.
I hope they don't know
that they are under surveillance.
-Not at all, sir.
-Okay.
Let's move on them, tomorrow...
quietly.
-Co-ordinate well.
-Yes, definitely.
Let's go.
Hello.
I left my wallet in the office, guys.
Tiwari!
Come, please.
CEO.
-Do you know him?
-Yes. He's our employee.
He's been working here for a year.
-Is there a problem, sir?
-Please swipe ahead.
He's also an employee.
He was recruited six months ago.
Go on.
He's been here for two years now.
-What's the matter, sir?
-Nothing.
We just want to talk to them.
Just co-operate with us and
everything will be fine.
Nobody should know we're here.
Alright, sir.
Let's go.
We're done here.
Pasha.
The CEO will meet you
at the back entrance.
Okay.
Let's go.
Good luck.
You call that undercover?
Dress him in a saree and
he'll still look like a fucking commando.
Guys, safeties off.
That's Arshad.
He's in the sixth row
to the extreme right.
Riyaz is in the tenth row
to the left.
And Hussain is in
the central section
on the second-last row to the left.
Come on.
He's escaping!
Catch him!
Stop!
Where's Hussain?
How could you assume that
the kids are only my responsibility?
Why are you taking me for granted?
Come on.
That's not what I meant!
Then what did you mean?
I'll understand only if you
talk to me!
Why can't we have a proper conversation
like a normal couple for once!
Please, don't get your
psychology into this.
How is this psychology?
We were in the middle of
a discussion yesterday.
Your phone rang and
you left mid-conversation.
You didn't talk to me
even when you came back.
Suchi, please try and understand.
You must be thinking,
"Suchi keeps whining all the time.
If I ignore her,
everything will be back to normal--"
Suchi, I have to go.
I'll talk to you later.
-That's the bastard!
-Motherfucker!
Let's go!
Catch him!
What are you looking at, fucker?
Just catch him!
Run!
Catch him!
Don't let him go!
-Come with me.
-I will wait for you.
Fucker! You want me to catch him
all by myself?
Step aside!
Move!
Stop, stop!
Stop! Stop, asshole!
Stop! Please, stop!
-Please stop.
-Who the hell are you?
He stole my wife's Mangalsutra!
Mangalsutra! Hop on!
My wife will divorce me!
Run, fucker!
Let me see how far you can run.
If you stop,
I'll kick your ass so hard
you'll scream every time you take a shit.
-Yuck!
-Sorry, ma'am!
This is the only way to talk to them.
Otherwise, they don't give a damn!
Run!
What happened? Tired already?
Are you tired?
Stop, ma'am.
-How dare you steal the Mangalsutra!
-Oh, yes.
-Give me the Mangalsutra back.
-Mangalsutra?
You may leave, ma'am.
Thank you.
-Don't spare him.
-Thank you, ma'am.
-Sorry...
-You think you're Usain Bolt?
Does it hurt here?
Fatima, I'm going to give you some pills.
It's okay, you can pay me the next time.
Come on. You don't have to.
-I'll be right back.
-Alright.
Give me a couple of apples.
Keep it.
Sir, you forgot your wallet.
No problem.
I'll give it back to him.
Sir!
Your wallet.
Thank you.
Tell me, who's your boss?
I don't know who you're talking about.
The one who planted the bomb
at Kala Ghoda.
I don't understand, sir.
What do you know about
the scooter blast
that took place in Kala Ghoda?
Don't be so coy, darling.
You can't hide the truth for long.
Tell me, or else...
I'll shove my hand down
your throat and get the truth out.
Aren't you fed up of running?
Every time...
Oh, fuck!
Pasha.
Whether this is good news or bad news,
I'm not quite certain, Srikant.
But a sleeper agent of RAW
from Balochistan has tipped us.
Something big is being planned.
Those three men who
were caught in Kochi
and the scooter bomber
are involved in this.
We need to find out what
they're up to
and when they plan to pull it off.
This mission is called...
Zulfiqar.
Okay, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Pasha, give me your pistol.
Why?
What do you mean why?
Give it to me.
Trust me, I won't do anything.
Hussain, I'm a bit exhausted now.
Okay?
I am done talking.
Just tell me.
What?
-This is illegal.
-I don't give a fuck!
Motherfucker!
-Srikant!
-Hussain!
Riyaz!
Are you serious?
Srikant!
Hussain!
Get me out of here!
I'll tell you!
I'll tell you everything!
I've never talked to him.
He always calls up Arshad...
-and speaks only to him.
-I only get messages.
He tells me what to pick up and
where to drop it off.
He shares manuals,
like how to make bombs,
how to escape from the cops.
How to avoid being traced on the
internet and mobile phones.
All that sort of stuff, sir.
-Did you ever practice those?
-No, sir.
He never meets us personally.
He always leaves something in a drop box.
We get a message whenever we
need to retrieve something from it.
We were talking about him yesterday.
Maybe he's a Pathan.
Maybe...
-we don't know.
-And?
I think he must be in his twenties.
Or...
Yes, definitely younger than 25.
Where's the drop box?
In front of the Victoria College Hostel.
Sir, I think he studies
at Victoria College.
He stays in the hostel.
I'm telling you the truth.
We'll have to
monitor the drop box.
Get it done.
By the way...
good job.
Bullets were fired.
Of course you liked it.
Next time you fire,
at least warn me.
Oh, wow!
Rambo is a smoker!
Please tell me you drink as well.
We can drown our past quarrels!
Kareem, please don't create a scene.
Get up.
-Sit.
-Kareem, just get up.
Just sit down.
Hey, get up!
He's not standing up!
Get up!
Can't you see
the national anthem is playing?
There's no rule that
says I must stand up.
There's no rule to respect
your parents either.
Come on, stand up.
Our soldiers die for us at the border
and you can't even stand up?
The same soldiers who kill
innocent children in Kashmir?
-What did you say?
-Stand up!
-It's your national anthem, not mine.
-Our national anthem?
-Are you from Pakistan?
-Hey, don't touch me!
Thanks.
Do you want me to come up?
Not now.
I have some work to do.
Bye.