-What are you doing tonight?
-Nothing new.
I'll go home and listen
to my wife complain
that the boss pays a measly salary
and I work extra hours.
Step on the gas.
Let's get there before seven
and watch the new Salman Khan film.
If you buy me the ticket,
I'll get you there before seven.
Done, buddy.
What's going on?
Looks like there was an accident.
Get rid of this!
Let's get the hell out of here!
You there! Stop!
-Stop! Damn you!
-Get out!
Where are you coming from?
From the market.
I see.
What's your name?
Cat got your tongue, fucker?
Let's see some ID, shall we?
Feroz Ahmed.
-What are you carrying in the truck?
-Nothing.
-Is it beef?
-No, it's not beef.
Check the back of the truck.
-What is it? Tell me.
-It's mutton.
Mutton?
-Bhaskar!
-Yes?
These motherfuckers
are carrying beef!
Motherfucker!
Brother, it's not beef.
I swear to God!
Fucker, come out!
How dare you!
Come here, motherfucker!
I'll show you!
Did you really think
that if you'll kill our holy cow
we won't do anything about it?
We'll slaughter all of you!
You dare slaughter
the holy cow, our mother?
You will be slaughtered too!
Beat the fuck out of them!
Hold him straight!
Motherfucker!
Two men, Amjad Ali,
and Feroz Ahmed
were beaten to death
by a mob outside Pune
under suspicion of carrying beef.
One died on the spot and the other,
on the way to the hospital.
Investigations reveal the meat
was not even beef--
Why do you watch such news?
Is it going to stop them
from doing such things?
That's not what I meant.
Then what do you mean, Jonali?
You want me to stop
thinking about this?
Kareem, you can retaliate.
But not through anger.
Retaliate through your work,
the way you always do.
Mere words won't help.
Kareem, such thoughts don't make
you any different from them.
This is the only language
they understand.
Because people have
become numb from within.
They watch such news every day
and then they say...
"What's going on in this country?"
And that's it!
People have a five-minute
attention span these days.
After five minutes
they watch a funny video,
and forget everything.
Kareem, please!
Stop being this negative!
Sometimes, you seem
scarier than them.
That's good.
Today, you're scared
-tomorrow, they'll be.
-Oh, shut up, Kareem!
Not everyone's wielding a sword.
But the ones with the swords
are calling the shots.
Hello.
Are you new here?
-Yes.
-Got cigarettes?
No.
Give me a cup of tea.
I'll need to make it.
It'll take time.
No!
Don't touch the teddy bear.
-Will you make the tea or not?
-You really want it?
I thought you won't wait for just a cup.
-It will take time.
-Do you not want customers?
You come here to sleep?
-Hello, this is Shinde.
-What's the update?
I've been watching the box
since I arrived.
I'll let you know if something happens.
Bulletproof glass!
You know why it's here?
So that your fellow terrorists
can't attack you.
Then, there's us fools...
trying to save your life.
Tell me the truth.
What's Zulfiqar?
Zulfiqar?
Mission Zulfiqar.
I don't know anything
about this mission.
-I just want to see my mother--
-If you loved your mother so much
why the hell did you go to Syria?
Do you remember the 2002 riots?
At that time...
my uncle used to live in Baroda.
Mom, Dad and my sister were visiting him.
They didn't step out of the house
for two days.
They were hoping...
that the riots would end soon.
But they didn't.
Two days later...
a mob entered the house.
My mother and sister hid under the bed.
They witnessed it all.
They watched the mob slaughter
my father and my uncle.
My sister screamed involuntarily.
Those bastards dragged them out...
and thrashed them like animals!
My mom wasn't lucky enough.
She survived.
Since then...
she wakes up screaming
every single night.
My father, sister, and my uncle...
appear in her dreams every night.
You have a family as well.
If something like this
would've happened to them...
what would you do?
I can't even imagine what
your family went through.
But an eye for an eye...
will leave the whole world blind.
You want to meet your mother, right?
Then tell me something useful.
You're not going to stay here
as a patient forever.
Think, Moosa!
Excuse me.
Smoking is not allowed in the hospital.
-Where is it allowed, then?
-Outside the hospital.
Moosa, I'll be back.
The students of Victoria College
have always been this way.
They just call themselves "students."
But in fact, they're always
bitching about the country.
And I'm sure you're right.
I suspect them too.
One of those bastards
is responsible for the blast.
Do you suspect anybody in particular?
Someone with a criminal record
or something.
I have the list ready.
They're all anti-nationals.
Alright. Okay...
Tell me the names of the ones
with prior arrest warrants.
There are four.
The first one is Junaid.
He's been studying here for two years.
Then, there's Sait,
who's been here for three years.
Sajid. He took up
a three-year course
but has been at it
for six years now!
Amir Peeran, he's from Pune.
But he used to study
in Saudi Arabia before.
All of them are in custody, sir.
Hold on!
I asked you to make a list.
How could you arrest them
without a warrant?
Don't worry about the warrant, sir.
Leave it to me.
It's a routine.
And these bastards are elusive.
Let's use our time with them wisely.
-They are locked up in a cell here.
-Okay, I'm on my way.
Why have you arrested us?
Do you have a warrant?
Bloody motherfucker!
This is my warrant!
Want me to shove it up?
Fucker!
You've arrested us
because we are Muslims.
Damn it! Has he lost it?
Sir...
Sir, I don't even know them.
-Why am I here with--
-Shut up!
-You're a fucking coward.
-Don't call me a coward.
-I am nothing like you.
-Shut the hell up!
You think you're here to gossip?
Just answer my questions, that's it!
Sir, we don't know anything
about the bomb blast.
Why are you questioning us?
You piece of shit!
Hello, sir.
Do you have any evidence
on the ones you have arrested?
What will we do with evidence, sir?
-We already know everything.
-Really?
They're all anti-nationals.
Sir, they were partying
on the day of the blast.
And if Pakistan wins
a match against India
they'll party all night!
And that makes them anti-national?
Have you lost it, Jadhav?
Sir, you'd asked me to
conduct an investigation
and to round up
suspects in the college, right?
Sir, just give me two days.
I'll shove a baton up their asses
and get the truth out.
You'll get a written confession.
Do you want a written confession
with a baton shoved
up their asses?
What a waste of time!
Any movement at the drop box?
Crows are shitting on it.
Nothing else.
The local police have the place
under 24/7 surveillance.
I hope they don't doze off.
I hope so, too.
For fuck's sake!
Get lost!
Don't touch the teddy bear, asshole!
-Yeah, Arvind?
-Hi, Suchi.
-Where are you?
-What happened?
-Are you going home?
-Yeah, why?
I'm at Potluck.
Can you come over for fifteen minutes?
I want to discuss something important.
It's a bit urgent.
Yes, I can.
But what happened?
Just come over.
It won't take long.
Call me when you reach Potluck.
Okay.
Please stop here.
Welcome, ma'am.
Do you have a reservation?
-Yeah--
-Hey, Suchi!
Thanks for coming.
I want to introduce you to
the CEO of my company, Nikhil.
What?
-I mean... How?
-It's okay.
It's just a casual meeting,
nothing formal.
Once you meet him,
it'll be easier for you.
What will be easier?
To decide whether you want to join us.
What are you talking about?
Arvind, first of all,
I don't know what you do.
I have no idea what
I will do in this company.
And what will I say?
You're great with people,
so just relax.
And it's a start-up.
We're not a corporate structure.
Knowing you, you'll easily learn
on the job, in no time.
I think you'll be great.
Trust me!
I wish I had as much confidence
in myself as you do!
You know what the secret
to confidence is?
Pretend to be confident.
-Nikhil, this is Suchitra.
-Hi!
So, you are Suchi.
-Nice meeting you, finally.
-Nice meeting you too.
It's okay if I call you Suchi, right?
-Yeah, of course.
-Please sit.
Arvind's always talking about you.
I'm glad Arvind convinced you.
I promise, you won't regret it.
So what made you change
your mind?
I mean, do you have an idea
what exactly we do
what our goals are,
what our plans are?
Well...
sort of.
But, Arvind has,
you know, given me a--
Sorry, I don't mean to rush things.
Relax, it's not an interview.
We can chat about this later.
Let's order something.
Excuse me.
Thank you. Please order.
You know, I've noticed that
people consider psychology
just as an easy subject
in the college syllabus.
They don't know how it could
have any use in real life.
But when Arvind told me
about the initiative
you guys were starting,
I finally felt
that there's a chance to
do something in real life.
I thought it was a brilliant idea.
The best part is that,
it's not just an app.
You're actually synergizing
it with a 360 vertical.
And I love the fact that
we're going from theory to practice.
So...
Wow! Even I cannot explain it so well.
No wonder Arvind thinks so highly of you.
Is it okay if I borrow some
of these lines?
Sure.
-You ambushed me!
-"Ambushed"?
I did nothing of that sort.
I wish I had some more time
to prepare better.
Why do you need to prepare?
You were just great!
Yeah, right!
Arvind...
how will I manage it all
in such short time?
You know, it's not just about
changing jobs.
There are other factors,
like travelling and timings.
Besides, there are no benefits in the job.
Forget that.
The main reason I took up
a teaching job was my kids.
So that I could give them quality time.
It's not as complicated
as you think.
It will work out.
I don't know what Sri will say.
I'm taking the same route,
do you need a lift?
-No, don't worry about it.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah, don't worry. I'll see you.
-See you.
As-salaam alaikum, Altaf Bhai.
Wa alaykumu as-salam.
It's an honor to meet you
after such a long time!
The honor's all mine, Kareem.
I love reading your blog,
your work, your exploits...
You are a hero, a real hero.
I trust you a lot.
-You know that, right?
-I know.
And I also know why you've called me here.
Altaf Bhai, I've told you already.
I won't join your group.
I prefer working alone.
Don't worry, it's something
you'll understand.
I have something
you need to see.
These bastards need a taste
of their own medicine.
-It's not for you.
-What is it?
I said it's not for you.
I know what it is.
I've watched the ad on TV.
There's a girl in the ad,
who looks very stressed.
But once she uses this,
she becomes energetic.
Then, she runs and
jumps around everywhere.
Shut up and move along.
Why don't you just tell him?
-What's the problem?
-What do I tell him?
It's not a bomb.
It's a sanitary pad, okay?
There's nothing to hide about it.
Girls have periods,
and boys are dumbasses.
Hello, hello!
What kind of language is this!
Where are you learning this?
At the school you send me to.
-Tell me something.
-Yes?
Does your sister have a boyfriend?
Yes, she might have one.
"Might"?
Does she have one or not?
Yes, she does.
And she should.
What do you mean "she should"?
Just tell me if she has one or not.
Yes. I think so.
You think so?
Just tell me,
does she have one or not?
She does.
How many times do I tell you?
Hello. Whom are you talking to?
Dad, there's something
called privacy, okay?
If you were hungry,
you should have said so.
Why did you steal?
Once you finish your job,
it's all yours.
Damn it, the memory card is full!
Do your work diligently.
Otherwise, you'll be screwed.
This card's not working!
Bloody Chinese goods!
It was working fine yesterday.
What the fuck happened today!
It's working now.
Oh! That's the guy you were waiting for!
Fuck!
What do you want to eat today?
-Pasta!
-McDonald's!
Something that can be cooked at home.
Can you cook chicken?
Chicken?
If you even think about cooking chicken
your mother's forefathers
will turn in their graves.
Fine, make veg biryani.
Veg biryani is an oxymoron, okay!
What's an oxymoron?
Like veg burger,
like "good Atharv!"
But I'm still good.
No, you're an oxymoron
and a moron.
-And you're a much moron!
-Alright, veg biryani.
Okay? Alright.
-No peas.
-And no onions.
Let's just boil some rice and eat it.
What's that?
Our supplies.
You're selling those chocolates?
You kids get a little freedom
and you raid the whole damn place!
You two--
Are you sure?
Whenever they start forgetting it
it's our duty to show them their place.
Today, they're killing and eating
our holy mother, the cow!
Tomorrow, they'll barge into our houses,
chop us and eat us, and our women.
What they really want to do is
throw us out of our own country!
Bloody traitors!
Whatever happens
it is our sacred duty
to save our motherland!
Slaughter each one of them!
Don't worry about the police.
I'll take care of them!
Bhaskar...
He was inciting them in broad daylight!
And then they went on
to kill those two Muslims.
This is clearly a pre-planned murder!
Kareem, we should
show this to the police.
What do you think will happen then?
You think the police will
arrest that minister?
They'll throw us behind bars instead.
And then eat biryani in his fucking house.
Jonali! Jonali, wait!
Where did you get this video from?
Does it matter?
Kareem, please!
Don't do anything stupid!
Jonali, just stay out of it.
Please!
There is no other way.
We've to give them
the taste of their own medicine.
It's our turn to strike!
-Shinde.
-Yes, sir?
Where's the recording
that shows him using the drop box?
-Were you asleep?
-No, sir!
The camera's memory card was full.
I was replacing it when--
Shinde, please wait outside.
Yes, sir.
-Any intel on this boy?
-Kareem Bhat from Srinagar.
He's been in Mumbai
for the last four years
pursuing a post-graduation in Victoria.
He's quite active on
social media as "Mighty Kalam."
He also writes blogs
on the situation in Kashmir.
A few years ago,
one of his videos went viral.
Even a dog doesn't give birth
to so many puppies.
We need to stop them
before they outnumber us.
We need to save this country!
We need to protect our religion!
Sir, why are you spreading hatred?
-Who said that?
-Hey, move aside.
The truth is always bitter, son.
To stay in this country--
Nothing after this ink attack.
He's kept a low profile ever since.
He's in touch via Facebook and email
with people who have links
to extremist groups.
-Criminal records?
-No, sir.
-Has he ever been arrested?
-Never.
There's no evidence of his
connection with a terrorist group.
That means he works alone.
Lone wolf!
Why are you jumping to conclusions?
First confirm it.
Don't involve the local police.
And keep that fucker Jadhav out of this!
He roams around with a
trident to hunt anti-nationals!
So, we do this in-house?
Contact the operations team.
Put Milind and Jayesh on the job.
You, Zoya, and I will co-ordinate this.
-Oh, Shinde.
-Sir!
-Are you from the local police?
-Yes, sir.
That's why your brain runs faster
than a train.
Thank you, sir.
But you see, Shinde...
along with those brains,
you also need to keep your eyes open!
They just have one job, anyway, right?
To see.
Yes, sir.
-Good job.
-Thank you, sir.
Oh, Shinde.
Bye.
-Are you sure?
-What do you mean?
Sir, we've done our homework.
This college is a nightmare!
First the papers leaked,
then a drug racket
and now this!
Sir, the lightning doesn't ask
before striking.
This is our warden, Mr. Gupta.
And this is Mr. Pimple from the NCDC.
Listen.
We'll need to evacuate the
extension wing of the senior hostel.
But none of the students
have complained yet.
Will you take action
only when someone dies?
-No.
-Sir.
What kind of logic is this?
Mr. Gupta, what kind of logic is this?
Will you take action
only when someone dies?
-How much time do you need?
-Ten minutes, sir.
So this is worse than dengue?
Ten times more so, sir.
That's why we have special chemicals.
Shall we begin?
Sir, why don't you let us do this?
-We'll let you know when we're done.
-Let me see.
Sir, this gas is poisonous
and the virus, dangerous.
We'll finish and let you know.
I have an eye on Kareem.
-We need to make it quick.
-I know. In and out.
I'm sweating out of new
orifices in this suit!
It's alright.
-All the best.
-Yeah, all the best.
What's the status?
He's nearby. Just a ten-minute
walk from the hostel.
Finally!
A little bit to the right.
-Perfect! Lock it.
-Here you go, okay!
Is the mic okay?
-Can you hear me?
-Yes!
-Great.
-Okay.
Putting cam two.
What are you guys doing here?
We're releasing a disinfectant gas here!
Come on, clear out!
Kareem is heading back.
Hurry up!
Kareem is on his way back.
I'm on it. Chill!
Be on the lookout.
Hello!
-Oh shit! Hurry up!
-I'm on it!
-Hello!
-Sir, what are you doing?
-I'll call NCDC.
-Don't come here.
-The gas is poisonous.
-Nobody's coming in.
He's getting into the hostel.
Guys, be quick!
-Fuck!
-Stop. Call your supervisor first!
Call your supervisor.
Sir, we'll be done in five minutes.
No, this is not good.
I'll call NCDC.
-Wait, I will call.
-Oh, hello!
Where are you going?
The gas is poisonous!
Get out of here.
Who cares! We breathe this
toxic shit all day.
-He's coming inside.
-Okay!
Milind, hurry up.
You have five seconds.
Hello!
Fuck!
It's safe now.
You can use the toilet.
Thank you.
Cam one online.
CCTV from the hostel is up.
Sir, I've accessed all of
Kareem's social media accounts.
His email, his blog, everything.
I am in!
Why don't you leave?
Leave, buddy.
The kids must be waiting.
All right, guys. See you.
-See you, sir!
-I will see you in the evening.
Give me a cigarette.
There was a new stall here.
Where did it go?
He was here for two days.
I don't know where he's gone.
How's that possible?
Strange fellow.
He had no interest in running
his business.
Who knows what he was doing here!
Thank you.
Mom, what are you doing here?
Go outside, please.
-Listen--
-I don't need any help.
I visited Swami Sarvanandji.
-I've brought you--
-Mom, look at this!
Thanks to you,
I look like a hermit.
Put this on.
-Right.
-Okay.
And take this.
-What's this?
-The prasad.
Listen.
Don't give it to anybody else.
You need more protection
than anyone else.
I always have a bomb
in my pocket, don't I?
You're impossible.
What's cooking?
I'm not staging a
performance here!
Why are you guys here?
I don't need any help.
You just want to steal
my recipe, don't you?
-Go on, leave.
-May I say something?
You look very fit.
-You look like his younger brother!
-Did you hear that?
He's running around a
lot lately, isn't he?
Chasing someone or the other.
What do you mean?
You haven't visited us for so long.
Do you even remember the
last time visited us?
There's too much work at the office.
I just don't have time.
Yeah, he often says that his mother--
Shut up! Will you?
I mean, he always talks about her.
-He thinks about you all the time.
-Whatever!
Once we settle the home loan
we'll move somewhere else
so Mom can stay with us.
No chance.
-Mom has settled in Powai.
-Shut up!
She's got a few good friends there.
-Dad.
-Yes, darling. Tell me.
Hello, Laxmi.
How are you?
Hello!
Thanks to the grace of Swami,
we're all well!
How are you and your wife?
Thanks to Lord Ayyappan's grace,
we're all good!
Two melodious cultures
come together
to create a huge din!
Dad, here.
Why is he talking so loudly?
Does he think we're deaf?
Is she deaf?
Why is she screaming so much?
Come on, Dad!
Where's Mom?
She had some urgent work
at the Matunga Tamil Association.
-What are they chattering about in Tamil?
-Mom!
I hope they aren't talking about us!
Please don't start.
-Hello, Grandpa!
-Come here.
How are you, darling?
Where's your elder sister?
Thank you, Grandpa.
Same to you!
What is this?
Doesn't he understand Tamil?
Why don't you talk in Hindi?
Let us in on the conversation.
Today, India is going to be split apart!
All I am saying is...
children should learn
their mother tongue.
It's enough to know the
national language, Hindi.
Hindi is not our
national language, ma'am.
-Please!
-What?
Hindi is just one of the
official languages, ma'am.
Don't you realize the
importance of Hindi?
Hindi has evolved from Sanskrit.
And Sanskrit is the
world's oldest language.
But Tamil is much
older than Sanskrit.
Says who?
It is a fact.
Seriously? What are we watching?
Switch it off!
We've been told to keep
a constant watch on them.
-We can't miss anything.
-Milind!
Punit!
You never let me do my job.
Lower the volume.
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, dear Atharv!
-Smear some cake on his face.
-No!
It's the first piano I've ever eaten.
-Okay, Atharv!
-Dad!
Feed the camera!
-It's good.
-Thank you.
You bought it from Madras?
No, from Matunga.
Not everything is from Madras.
I hope it doesn't have egg in it.
Will I ever offer you
a cake with egg in it?
I called up the
bakery just for you
and gave him
strict instructions
to give me an eggless cake!
Come on, eat up.
Did you ever think
you would have to do something like this?
Watch people make out?
I know.
But we just need to do certain things.
A lot of it feels wrong.
But I keep reminding myself
I am doing this for the greater good.
Hopefully.
Guys, come in, we have a guest.
Let's go.
-Did you get the van?
-Yes.
-When are we getting the stuff?
-Tomorrow.
Who is it?
I'm not sure.
-Did Nissar get the floor plan?
-Yes.
-Guest list?
-He's on it.
He said he'll get it
directly to the base camp.
He didn't want to email it.
-I had asked him not to.
-You're right.
You never know who's sniffing around.
Fuck!
They're planning something big.
Good.
This biryani is good.
But, if you'd put some meat in it
it would've been more delicious!
Keep your voice down!
If my father-in-law hears that,
you'll be slaughtered.
Please! Your mom is the same!
People are getting
slaughtered in the name of biryani.
And we think the ISIS is brutal!
-Suchi!
-Yes?
Please tell him to take up an IT job.
He's not going to listen to anyone.
Let him be!
Why don't you leave this job?
You've been serving the
country long enough.
Now it's time to work for yourself.
JK, please convince him.
Okay, but who'll convince me?
Stop it, Suren.
Don't start the same old conversation!
Listen, Suchi.
When Srikant was in school
he was everyone's darling.
Everyone thought he
would make it big!
That he'd be successful.
And what did he do?
He became a patriot and
got a government job.
Stop it!
Everyone has their own priorities.
He wants to serve the nation.
It's his choice!
Listen, all I am saying is
his job should pay him good, right?
Just being patriotic
is not enough
to fill up your bank account.
In fact, even I am serving the nation.
-I'm boosting the economy!
-Really?
Do you think you can
boost the economy
if the country is not safe?
-Let's shut down everything.
-Sri!
Try boosting the economy then!
We're fucking morons, aren't we?
Change the topic!
Let's boost the party, not the economy.
-Good point!
-Sri, one couplet.
-I'm not in the mood!
-Come on!
-Please!
-One couplet, please!
What's that word? Irshad!
Let me think.
Okay, here goes.
"There is no hope now...
There is no hope now
I can't find that lovely face now
Once I used to laugh at my heart
Nothing makes me laugh now"
What does it mean?
Now, one has to first say a couplet
and then explain it to this generation.
Because there was no hashtag
in the couplet.
There's one for people like you too.
Listen!
This is an original one.
"There was a time when you could see
God in children..."
When we were children,
one could see God within us.
"There was a time when you could see
God in children..."
But now you see children
Only on Instagram"
You should be on Instagram, okay?
Wasting your 1000 grams of brain
on Instagram!
-One more.
-Okay, let me think.
-Cover your ears.
-Why?
Can you ever listen to your father?
Come on, Dhriti.
Cover your ears, please!
"Her youth would incite
A jaljala inside me"
"Jaljala" means volcano.
Correct!
"Her youth would incite
A jaljala inside me
I know it would make my heart burst
But my phone always rang first"
-Ditto.
-Did you hear that?
I need to go.
-It's kind of urgent.
-Just two more couplets.
-It's an emergency.
-Do you need to go?
Suchi, it is an emergency.
Sorry! You guys, continue.
Talpade...
I read Suchi's messages.
You've started checking Suchi's phone?
No, I wasn't checking.
I went into the room,
her phone was on the shelf.
And she got a text, so...
What's that thing called...
"Review"?
-Preview
-Yes, the preview, on the screen.
I read that.
I wasn't checking her phone.
Of course, you weren't.
You were just reading her messages.
Fucker!
Will you listen to what I'm saying?
Stop preaching!
-Her colleague--
-Tiwari, have you lost your mind?
Don't jump to conclusions!
Who texts a lady in the
middle of the night?
-And, Suchi--
-What?
I've been noticing her.
She's always on the phone,
like a teenager.
So what?
If you won't talk to her
she'll need someone else to talk, right?
Fucker! I'll throw you out of the car!
-What kind of a friend are you?
-Tell me something.
-Did you read her replies?
-No!
But that jackass is
sending her dozens of emo...
-Emojis.
-Right, emojis!
-Smileys.
-Yes, smileys.
What do you mean by "dozens"?
I mean...
Lots of emojis at once!
Is there a fixed number
of smileys to be sent?
Will you land in trouble if you send more?
All of this is very normal.
We also do it, don't we?
And Suchi is not a child.
She can handle this kind of attention.
She'll take care of it.
The smiley that you mentioned...
Was it a normal one or like...
The one with a red heart on the lips.
Was it that one?
No, not that one.
Then you're safe.
-I'm safe?
-Yeah.
Milind, what's happening?
Sir, a guy named Iqbal came to meet him.
They were talking
about some delivery
which will happen tomorrow.
And, sir...
they were also talking about
a guest list and a floor plan.
Some guy called Nissar
is coordinating this.
We haven't seen him until now
but he can come any time.
Get me Iqbal's and Nissar's details.
Find out who they are.
Already done, sir.
What? What happened?
Must be a power cut, sir.
Oh, shit!
Milind.
Go stand outside the hostel gate
and stay there.
Keep an eye on things.
Milind, what's the status?
I'm at the hostel's front gate.
There's a power cut.
No activity here.
-Stay alert!
-Sir.
Fuck!
-Sir!
-Yes?
Sir, a van just passed
by from the side lane.
What kind of van?
I ran behind it but
I couldn't see the number.
I'm damn sure Kareem was in it!
-Kareem?
-Yes, sir.
Sorry, sir.
Why did you think we were being watched?
A couple of days ago,
a tea stall suddenly popped up
and then disappeared.
Did you see the van
outside gate number five?
It's been there all this time.
There are cigarette butts
strewn all around it.
I might be overthinking it but...
I can't afford to take a risk.