Nissar.
Are you sure about the floor plan?
I got it from the builder directly.
-How did you get the guest list?
-That was easy.
It's a public event.
Did you see the guest list?
Full of assholes.
Those bastards won't know what hit them.
These bastards deserve this!
Won't your uncle ask you about his van?
I've told him it's out for servicing.
It'll be back in two or three days.
Only God knows what will
happen in two or three days.
We'll wait here till the evening.
Okay, bhai.
Are all your cell phones switched off?
Yes, bhai.
Their phones have been
off for quite some time.
The last known location was Bhendi Bazaar.
They must have gone underground.
Any footage from the CCTV cameras
at the signal?
Nothing, sir.
There aren't too many cameras
in Bhendi Bazaar.
JK.
Tell Force One to send a unit
to Bhendi Bazaar.
In civvies, no uniform.
Kareem.
Isn't it looking great?
-It's fine.
-Bhai!
The uniform is ready too.
Shall we load the van?
-Not now. Do it just before leaving.
-Okay.
Iqbal.
Are you out of your mind?
Policemen will be checking us at the gate.
Those men
were just carrying mutton, Iqbal.
Didn't you see how they were slaughtered?
We can't go there unarmed.
We'll hide it.
Don't utter a word about this to Kareem.
He'll chew my brains if he finds out.
Did he know that somebody's
keeping an eye on him?
It's possible, sir.
It was such a sudden blackout.
It was either pre-planned
or he's just plain lucky.
A man carries out a scooter blast
and God knows what he's up to now!
But all we know is that he's plain lucky!
What's the next step?
We'll need a search warrant
as soon as possible.
If we go through his room,
we might find something useful.
-And if we find nothing?
-Then we have only one option, sir.
Evacuate Bhendi Bazaar.
Did you complete your English assignment?
-Mom, please!
-What do you mean by "Mom, please"?
Have you done it or not?
Go sleep in your own bed!
Mom?
-Where's Papa?
-I don't know.
Has he gone to the office again?
Maybe.
Mom?
If Dad works so hard,
we should have more money.
We should be rich, no?
Shut up, idiot!
Excessive sleeping leads to a lower IQ.
Your IQ is low already.
At this rate, you'll have a negative IQ.
Get up! Get up!
Mom, do something!
Please, let me sleep. I'll kill him.
He's right.
Excessive sleeping reduces brain cells.
-Come on, get up.
-Mom, it's a Sunday.
So what? Get up and
complete your assignment.
Don't worry, it'll take me
only two minutes to finish it.
Which one's the smiley?
Show. I will show you.
Don't worry.
-I'm not going to read your texts.
-It's okay.
I had my doubts, but...
Please, have a look.
Sir, I always knew...
Tell him to check under the bed.
Check under the bed!
Quickly.
Tell him to check
the top of the bookshelf.
Check behind the books.
-We've found the laptop, sir!
-Bring it here.
Show me.
Finally, dude.
Do you think I'm a terrorist?
How does it matter?
It does matter.
Do you think I'm a bad man?
It doesn't make any difference to me
whether you're a good man or a bad one.
I'm a bad man.
I've done many horrible things.
I've sinned my entire life.
If I had a choice,
I would have changed everything.
Do you know what happens when
one reaches the ISIS camp?
They tear your passport
up and throw it away.
So that you rot there
for the rest of your life.
I had read so many things
about the Caliphate.
Rivers of milk and honey
flow in those lands.
The streets are paved with gold.
Only the will of Allah is obeyed.
There's no sadness.
There's only the light of God.
Those bastards made me do things.
Things I'm ashamed to even speak about.
And they claimed it was the will of Allah.
You...
You need to rest a bit.
You'll feel better when you rest.
What's the use of recovering physically?
What about the scars inside?
How will they heal?
You shouldn't be thinking
about what you've been through.
You need to strengthen yourself.
Don't worry about anything else.
God will take care for you.
Why will your God care for me?
I...
-Sorry.
-It's okay.
I don't have any complaints
against your God.
In fact,
if your God can help me,
please tell him to do it.
Because I really need help right now.
My mom thinks I'm still in the Gulf.
I don't mind if I die!
I want to see my mom just once.
When I come back,
I want to see the assignment done.
I just said I'll be back soon.
Don't think you can do whatever
you want when I'm not around.
Do your assignment.
No arguments.
I don't understand how people work,
run their house, look after the kids
and still manage
to make time for themselves!
And you're already doing all of this.
So, where are you taking me?
Treat for your new job, right?
You should be treating me.
But that's later.
Right now, we're going to celebrate.
Do you like Italian or...
I love Italian.
Then we're going to the perfect place.
It doesn't look like
you're going to work on an assignment.
Shut up! Mind your own business.
What's happening?
Can you access it or not?
Sir, I just got it. I need a minute.
Sir, will you keep standing here?
Why?
It might take some time, that's why.
-Okay.
So, this is my favorite place.
Yeah, sure.
Hello.
Sorry, I wasn't able to call you.
I drifted off to sleep
while I was sitting.
It's okay.
I am dying under all this paperwork.
My bosses have come down from Delhi.
Okay.
-You were saying?
-Saying what?
You texted that you wanted to speak.
Tell me.
I...
Nothing, we'll talk about it later.
Let's talk about it now. I'm free.
No. Nothing urgent.
Let's talk when I reach home.
-So, where are you now?
-Nearby.
I'd stepped out for some work.
I had some college work too.
So, I thought I'll sit somewhere
and finish it off.
Anyway, listen, I'll call you later.
I don't even know why I am lying to Sri?
What's the problem now?
Suchi was lying.
Suchi!
She was hiding something.
You're getting paranoid for nothing.
No, no. Talpade.
I'm telling you the truth.
If a liar smells a lie,
then he must be right.
Did I say something wrong?
Ajit, I need to track this number.
Give it to me.
I need the last location.
Tiwari, this is getting out of hand.
Is this personal?
No. Tell me.
-Why do you make me do such things?
-Look, Tiwari!
You've neither eaten anything
nor slept since yesterday.
-Did you get it?
-Calm down!
-And please relax!
-It's in Mumbai itself.
Juhu. Hotel Sea Castle.
Hey, listen.
I'm going out for an hour.
Call me if anything comes up.
Listen! Even I'm coming along.
-Just move it, fucker!
-Tiwari! Calm down.
This is not good for your blood pressure.
Shove it!
I am telling you, you're making a mistake.
Your mind is playing tricks on you,
and you're letting it.
I didn't ask you to come along!
You followed me like a faithful dog.
Now, just sit quietly!
Do you do this often?
I mean, sometimes.
But mostly by myself.
Sometimes I come down and do some work.
Sometimes...
I just lounge around.
-You are living it up!
-What's wrong with that?
No, no. I'm serious.
We spend our entire lives thinking about
family, children, and society.
And if we ever think about ourselves,
then we drag ourselves down.
-Have your drink.
-Thanks.
I don't even remember
the last time when I went out.
There was a time when I
used to explore new places
and travel around.
You know, I used to have a life.
It's not over yet.
Tiwari, stop.
Tiwari!
There's still time, stop this.
Tiwari, stop. Tiwari!
Get out of here.
-This is a family matter.
-But...
Shit!
They must be drinking coffee.
Shit! Tiwari.
Tiwari, don't do this!
-Let's talk.
-What?
Talk like we're discussing
something important.
Fucker, I've to talk to you
about something important.
About how you're hell-bent
on fucking up your marriage.
-Oh, yeah!
-No, no, bhai!
Good afternoon, sir.
Would you like to go for brunch?
No, no. Just a whiskey with soda and ice.
Sir, we also have an unlimited
drinks offer with brunch.
Get the brunch then...
What brunch? What's the price?
Sir, for veg it is Rs. 2,799 plus taxes.
And non-veg is Rs. 3,299 plus taxes.
-Yeah, get it.
-You guys just want to fuck a man over!
Get a whiskey and an
orange juice, that's it.
Sir, no brunch?
Look, man! We are poor people.
For the cost of a single brunch
we can eat lunch for a month.
Isn't it your...
Srikant!
-She's seen us.
-Oh, shit!
Do you want to invite him over?
What are you talking about...
Oh, look at that!
Oh, shit! You're screwed now!
It's nothing, chill.
Looking nice, Suchi.
Why are you here?
We had some work.
We got hungry
and decided to grab a bite here.
What are you doing here?
Didn't you have some work?
That's what I'm here for.
I'm meeting a friend.
We're discussing my new job.
It's a nice place
to discuss things.
Hi, Suchi!
What a surprise?
Would you
like to meet Arvind?
Why don't you come and say hi?
Isn't he the one who left his job
and joined the start-up?
Srikant, is that whiskey?
Do you regularly come here?
Where are the kids?
Don't worry. They're fine.
I can pick up or drop the kids
if you're too busy.
There's no need for that. Today is Sunday.
Right.
You continue your important discussion.
You must have important paperwork too.
Carry on.
-Cool.
-What happened?
-Fuck!
What happened?
Bye. Bye, Suchi.
Thank you.
You'll sleep better
with Mother Mary watching over you.
Oh, sorry! I...
If it's a problem, I'll remove it.
No, no, let it be.
As it is,
everybody hates me.
At least there's somebody
who cares about me.
Thank you.
Let her stay over here.
When this Mary is not around,
Mother Mary will look after me.
Please rest now.
-Yes, Pasha. What's happening?
-Nothing yet.
We're wasting time.
We need to evacuate this entire place.
No, no. I'll let you know.
-Find anything?
-This encryption is very powerful.
It'll take some time.
-Srikant!
-Yes, sir.
We have to raise an alert soon
and evacuate the area.
-We don't have time!
-I understand, sir.
Give us some more time, sir.
We're almost there. We are working on it!
Take a right from there.
Guys, I'm in! I'm in!
Come, Talpade!
There's been a lot of activity
on his blog,
email and YouTube.
There's also this video
that he watched, sir.
Whenever they begin to forget,
it becomes our duty
to show them their place in society.
That's MP Deshpande.
The time code tells us
Kareem saw this video
an hour after he used the drop box.
It's possible that he got this video
in the drop box.
We can't keep waiting for the government.
Who's this Deshpande?
He runs an NGO
called "Cow Protection Force."
Where does he stay?
Near Bhendi Bazaar.
There's a birthday party
at Deshpande's house today.
In an hour.
The guest list and floor plan
are of this party!
Let's go!
Pasha!
They're going to attack
MP Deshpande's house.
We need to stop them
before they reach there.
Copy.
Alert all units.
-The target is MP Deshpande.
-Yes, sir.
Are you absolutely sure?
Yes, sir. They have the guest list
and floor plan.
They're in a van.
And if my guess is right,
there's something
very dangerous in that van.
The party is going to start now.
The attack can happen at any moment.
Srikant, you better be right about this.
Step on it.
-What's the update?
-Suspects are in this area.
We're tracking them.
If your intel is right,
they'll come through this road.
The rest of the units
are stationed at other intersections.
Let's see.
Iqbal!
Easy, easy! Stay cool.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
-Where did these guys come from?
-Fuck! How did they know?
I'm telling you, Kareem,
someone's out to fuck us!
Go, go, go!
-They will shoot us!
-Drive straight.
Stop! Stop!
Back! Back!
Back! Quick!
Back! He will shoot us. Back! Back!
Go straight! Straight!
Go, go, go!
Go!
-Kareem, I told you not to do it.
-Just, shut up!
You told us nothing would go wrong.
Take a left!
Left, left, left!
Shit! Drive back!
They will shoot us.
I'm taking care of it. Just shut up!
Back! Back!
What's happening?
They're chasing us.
Shut up!
I don't know how this happened.
Take a left!
They're going to kill us.
-Take left!
-Nothing will happen.
Drive straight!
I know they're going to kill us!
Shut up!
-Take a right!
Oh, shit!
I'll get these bastards...
-Hey, what're you doing?
-Let those motherfuckers come!
Come here, motherfucker!
Hey, Nissar! Have you lost you mind?
Nissar!
-Come, you motherfuckers!
-Nissar!
Fuck!
And we get justice.
I love you, Jonali.
Hey, who's there?
Sir, the target is in sight. May I shoot?
Take the shot!
He's dead.
Open it.
JK, sir.
Yes, tell me.
Come here, sir. You need to see this.
-What is it?
-See for yourself.
It's beef, sir.
Beef!
So this was their plan?
To feed beef to Deshpande.
This is just...
Shit!
Why the hell did they have guns?
Sir, only one of them had a gun.
Shit!
If word gets out,
TASC will be shut down permanently.
Sir, it's my fault.
-I take responsibility.
-What?
What difference will it make?
Okay, guys. Listen.
It was a terrorist attack.
We had intel that they were
going to attack Deshpande.
We warned them and gave them
a chance to surrender.
But they fired at us.
All three died in the encounter.
That's the story.
Sir! That's...
Do you have any other solution?
We've made a mistake.
Now is the time for damage control.
Your accepting responsibility
is not going to help.
Am I clear?
Yes, sir!
I'm coming!
Sorry, I forgot the keys.
-It's four in the morning!
-Sorry.
What was the need to drink so much?
Come on, Suchi. Please!
Have you been drinking since afternoon?
Suchi, be quiet, please!
Go, sleep!
Sleep, sleep!
Don't you want to say anything?
What?
About the fact that I went out for coffee?
No!
About the fact that you hid it from me.
You lied to me.
Sri, you, of all people,
shouldn't preach about not lying, okay?
No, no. Don't change the subject.
We are talking about you now.
What about me?
I'd gone to meet a colleague
and discuss a new job opportunity.
What is it with this new job?
That you want to give up everything
to run after it.
If you had ever tried to understand me,
then you wouldn't be
asking me this question today.
-I am asking you now!
-Sri!
I am tired!
I've been leading
my life for fifteen years
for you and the kids.
If I'm trying to do something new,
then what is the problem with that?
Arvind has left college
and joined a good company.
And he's asked me to come along with him.
That's what we were discussing.
Arvind has joined a new company.
So now the company is good.
Arvind has left his college job...
So now the college is bad.
Who the hell is this Arvind?
-Sri, come on...
-No, no.
It was such a beautiful place
to discuss a job.
-Seaside, romantic brunch, right?
-What?
How did you find out
where I was at that moment?
-Were you tracking me?
-Bullshit!
Like you track those criminals?
Nonsense! You're talking bullshit!
You're impossible!
I just don't want to talk to you!
You always say,
"We don't talk, we don't talk."
So what are we doing now?
-I am talking to you right now!
-Lower your voice, Srikant!
There's a point in talking
only if there's mutual respect.
What have I ever done to listen to this?
Oh, right!
I haven't taken you out for coffee
to a five-star hotel.
I haven't taken you for exotic holidays.
I have never given you expensive gifts.
If it were possible, I would have done it!
Have I ever asked you for anything?
Never have I asked you
for something we couldn't afford.
Don't make me sound
like a bloody gold-digger!
I'm a loser.
Everyone keeps reminding me.
My mother, my brother...
Keep reminding me.
Your father thinks
I'm a loser.
You think
My kids, too, think I'm a loser.
Sri,
every time the same thing?
Why does everything ultimately have to be
about you and your important job?
Enough is enough!
I'm sick and tired of this self-pity!
Tired of it?
Then why are you still with me?
Why don't you leave me?
Because I used to think
that whatever happens
your family is important to you too!
But I don't know any more.
Oh, and by the way,
I've said yes to the job.
Atthu, go inside, please. Yes.
Papa!
Dhriti, Atharv, let's go. Come on.
We have just received some huge news.
A terrorist attack was planned
on MP Deshpande's house.
But our vigilant forces
stopped it in time.
The terrorists were not from Pakistan.
They were three students
from Victoria College, Mumbai.
Arms and ammunition were recovered...
-No, hold on! Listen to me.
-I just...
Let me get this straight here.
-You think that these three terrorists...
-Terrorists!
Anurag, they're students.
-We don't have proof.
-Soldiers are dying every day.
You should question the government
if they have the proof!
-Proof. You want proof?
-Yes!
I will give you the evidence.
The evidence is that this guy
whose name is Kareem
who you think is innocent.
He refused to stand up
for the national anthem.
-Isn't this proof...
-Are you serious?
If he didn't stand up
for the national anthem,
you declare him a terrorist?
Anurag, come on! How can you say
that these innocent students...
Easy there.
Cool down a bit now.
Look, it was a collective failure.
Everybody is at fault.
And if everyone messed up,
then don't blame just yourself.
If Kareem was not a terrorist,
then why did he use the drop box?
And why that drop box?
Why just that one?
Maybe someone set him up.
I don't understand.
The biggest fuck-up is...
We know nothing about
that fucking scooter-bomber.
Good.
Your luck is good.
But your Allah won't be there every time.
But I'll be there.
Watching, like a CCTV camera. 24/7.
Diwali, Dusshera, Holi, Navratri,
if anything happens,
I'll make you dance to my tunes.
Now, get lost.