As-salaam alaikum, Sajid.
Wa alaykumu as-salam.
Altaf Bhai!
You got out.
You should be thanking us.
What for?
For saving you from the police.
But why?
-What did I do to--
-Faizan Bhai sends his regards.
He has big plans for you.
He doesn't want you caught
for petty IED blasts.
That's why he asked
me to bail you out.
-They had no evidence against me.
-Why take a chance?
That's why we put Kareem as bait.
-To get their eyes off of you.
-Kareem?
Kareem Bhat?
We knew those software idiots
would spill the beans about the drop box.
So, we sent them on the wrong trail.
What happened to him?
He was martyred.
It was tragic.
But there was no other way.
We led him to the drop box.
Whatever happened after that
was on him.
What does Faizan Bhai
want from me?
Only he knows that.
But he did say that...
after this, people will consider
the 26/11 attacks, child's play.
Get some rest.
And don't go back to the hostel.
Look for a new place to stay.
I'll meet you again.
Allah hafiz.
-What's his FiO2?
-Sir, sixty.
-Make it thirty please.
-Yes, sir.
-Call Dr. Patel immediately.
And you, inform the ATS, please.
We had information
that a drop box was being used
for terrorist activities.
Kareem used that drop box.
And you found out about this drop box
through the three IT employees...
you had arrested at their office.
Is that right?
Yes, sir.
They individually confirmed this.
Did you think that this
drop box could be used
by a person not involved
in terrorist activities?
Well...
It didn't occur to me then.
What do you think now?
Now... I think that...
somebody deliberately...
made Kareem...
use that drop box.
I think he was framed.
Framed?
Was there any evidence
against Kareem
besides the fact that
he used that drop box?
This is...
Standard Operating Procedure, sir.
We often need to take action
based on little evidence.
The suspect was kept under surveillance.
What did you find?
Actually,
we heard Kareem talking
to two of his associates.
-Iqbal and Nissar.
-Yes, sir.
They were planning to
attack MP Deshpande.
It's written here that
you heard them discussing
about a van, a guest list
and a floor plan.
Yes, sir.
We thought they were...
going to launch an attack.
The only difference is
you didn't know it was
this sort of an attack.
-Right, sir.
-Mr. Sharma's report mentions that
Kareem was never officially arrested.
But he was always
under surveillance
because of his actions.
Throwing ink on a politician,
writing anti-government blogs...
Is that right, Mr. Srikant?
Yes, sir.
But our actions are never based
on a person's political views.
Mr. Sharma, what is your assessment?
Sir, my assessment remains the same.
Srikant is very impulsive.
He gets carried away.
And sometimes, he doesn't follow rules.
He makes decisions without
bothering about the process.
In some cases,
his approach has benefited us.
Yet, we can't keep
overlooking his mistakes.
But in this case, sir...
the evidence against
Kareem and his associates
was sufficient enough to act upon.
So, what we gather, Mr. Srikant
is that you had a suspect
who had
anti-government views.
He used a terrorist drop box
and planned an attack
on an MP with his associates.
In such little time, it was impossible
for your team to figure out
what the attack was.
-Yes, sir.
-We believe that
you had a valid
reason to target Kareem.
And as far as...
their shooting is concerned.
It looks like a Force One call
and not TASC's.
Force One commander
Pasha and his team
got carried away and shot them.
So, Mr. Srikant
the decision to
shoot was Force One's.
Is that right?
This was my operation.
Every decision taken...
was mine.
Whatever happened...
If someone should be held responsible...
then...
I should be held responsible.
It will hurt a bit.
But you'll get better soon.
Oh! Your friend...
regained consciousness today.
How is he?
He regained consciousness
but then fell unconscious again.
The doctor says he'll recover soon.
Inshallah!
I had lost all hope.
This wound has healed.
It won't hurt much now.
The doctor says
you'll be discharged soon.
Let me...
-As-salaam alaikum
-Wa alaykumu as-salam.
Come in.
Have you heard of Basharat Ali?
Kashmir!
He's waiting for you in Srinagar.
What happened?
It's been ages since I went to Srinagar.
The city reminds me of my little brother.
He was fourteen...
when these bastards shot him.
He was returning from school.
He saw a procession.
People were raising slogans.
He joined them.
It was a peaceful procession
from Lal Chowk to Jama Masjid.
No stone-pelting, no furor, nothing.
We have faced many atrocities.
But we'll avenge them all.
And Allah has chosen you
for this mission.
-What is this?
-A ticket to Srinagar.
You'll need to leave soon.
-Who else is involved in this mission...
-Mission Zulfiqar.
Nobody knows anything.
Don't take this
the wrong way, Altaf Bhai.
But I know nothing
about this mission.
And I work on my own terms.
That's why, before I do anything
I want to speak to Faizan Bhai.
Each of us have been given a task.
We get orders and we do
what has been asked of us.
I was told to meet you and I did that.
That's all they asked of me.
Basharat's number is fed into this phone.
Speak to him.
If Sharma finds out
we're in the hospital
he'll suspend us.
It's an ongoing investigation.
We can do our job till then.
As soon as Asif regains consciousness
we'll start grilling him.
Nobody knows anything
about Mission Zulfiqar.
Except him.
Tiwari, we're not in a
position to give orders.
Sharma has issued a memo
and screwed everyone.
Hello, Doctor.
Hi.
What's the update?
He had regained
consciousness a while ago.
I think he's stable now.
But it will take time
for him to talk.
Is he still under danger?
No, he'll live.
And one more thing.
The one who was shot in the arm...
Moosa.
-His name is Moosa Rahman.
-Yes, him.
He's fine now.
He's in a bit of pain
but we can discharge
him very soon.
Okay.
Thanks.
You wait here.
I'll be back.
Rest as much as you want to.
The doctor said
you'll be fine soon.
Once you are discharged...
you won't be getting this royal treatment.
Tell me something important
or get ready for some
intensive care by the police.
Think!
Think fast!
I'll be back.
Atharv.
Hello! Atharv!
Put that mouth organ down.
Mom!
I need the laptop.
Are you going to take long?
Yes. Use your notebook.
Come on, Mom!
This is so annoying!
What?
What did you say?
What are you doing?
Fixing the house.
Oh, God!
Is everyone going crazy in this house?
This is so annoying!
Atharv.
Atharv!
Stop it.
May I come in, sir?
No, it's alright, sir.
You just had to agree with them.
They already said
that the three deaths were
Force One's fault.
They were looking to clear you!
Sir, I was responsible for the operation
-so the consequences--
-I know.
And yes, there are consequences.
You're being transferred to Srinagar.
Temporarily.
The lead analyst there
is on maternity leave.
She'll be back in a few months
and so will you.
You're lucky you haven't been suspended.
If it had been anyone else
he'd be packing his bags by now.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you for your support.
Don't thank me.
Thank Kulkarni.
He spoke to the officers
and set things up for you.
What's the bloody hurry?
You! You there!
I was about to park.
Take your car out.
Sir, I parked already.
-You can park is elsewhere.
-You don't seem to get it.
Take your car out!
Your blood pressure will soar, sir.
What did you just say?
Get up! You bastard!
-How dare you!
-Dad!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
We were just playing.
That's my son.
Say hello.
Go on!
-Say hello!
-Hello!
We were just playing.
Get out of here.
Don't tell Mom.
What?
I'm talking about what you saw.
-Hello?
-What?
You have to say, "Okay, Dad."
I'm craving pizza.
You ate pizza this Saturday!
I feel like having it again.
-Okay, I'll get you some tomorrow.
-I want it now.
Why did he get pizza?
I never get some when I ask for it!
-Do you want to eat pizza?
-Yes.
No problem.
Dad, an ice cream too.
The shop's on the way.
Sure, son, why not!
Hold on a second.
You're agreeing to
all his demands!
-What do you have against me?
-Nothing, my dear.
Do you want an ice cream too?
You can also have one.
-Hello, Sri.
-Hello, sir.
Sir...
can I disturb you for a minute?
Tell me.
Sir, I think I've
made a huge mistake.
Sri, you know I trust
your judgement.
I'm a little surprised that...
you made such a mistake.
Sir, I'm upset about the fact
that not only did we kill them...
we also destroyed their reputation.
Sir, they were not terrorists.
Their families deserve to know this.
Because now...
the world will taunt them all their lives.
Sir, I think I should tell the truth.
I'm ready to
face the consequences.
Don't do it, Sri.
Sir, we...
Actually, I...
murdered them.
Listen, Sri. Calm down.
If you tell the world that you
murdered three innocent boys,
it will be a disaster.
The media, human rights groups...
They will be all over us.
This will totally undermine
our fight against terrorism.
Please see the big picture.
I don't know who is wrong, sir.
There seems to be no difference
between them and us.
There's a very big difference.
And the difference is that
they need to win only once.
But we have to win every time.
We're at war, Sri.
Kareem was not a terrorist.
Please.
What are you doing, Tiwari?
Take it easy, buddy.
Don't you want a drink?
Years ago, my father threw
me out of the house.
You know why?
He thought I was killing my
Muslim brothers in the name of duty.
He said that if I side with the infidels
Allah will send me to hell.
You know what I told him?
I said, "Dad, go fuck yourself."
I'm not killing my brothers.
I'm killing terrorists.
They murder innocents.
And today...
I have murdered innocents.
-We're all murderers.
-Yes.
And now...
I'm left with neither work,
nor respect.
Will you two stop being
melodramatic, please?
You screwed up.
We all screwed up!
We're all killers!
But it was a mistake.
Nobody killed them on purpose.
It doesn't matter.
We killed them.
And now we're defaming them.
Everybody's calling them terrorists.
We need to tell their parents...
that their children were not terrorists.
We fucked up.
But it is a question
of national security!
-So the truth can take a flying fuck?
-No!
There's the truth.
And then, there's the country.
Please don't make any hasty decisions.
You mean suicide?
I'm a Force One commando.
-Don't worry about me.
-That's not what I meant.
When did I say so?
This is getting too depressing!
What are you doing?
You both are not asleep yet?
No.
Of course he followed you here.
Don't you have school tomorrow?
Why aren't you asleep yet?
Don't you have college tomorrow?
Tomorrow...
No, I quit my job at the college.
I got a new job.
-What? When?
-You didn't even tell us!
I'm telling you now!
-Only after I asked you.
You treat me like a child!
Suchi, you should
have told me at least.
And what is this new job about?
Relax! I'll tell you everything tomorrow.
Now go to sleep!
Okay, Suchi.
Let's have a chat tomorrow.
Hey! Run along!
I'll be there in five minutes
to check on you.
-I'll whack you if you're not in bed.
-I love you too, Suchi.
Moosa?
What happened?
Are you in pain?
I'll ask the doctor to
give you more painkillers.
What happened to you?
I don't want to get better.
You can't stay forever in the hospital.
If I recover...
they will throw me inside the jail.
They will kill me, Mary.
Don't think about such things.
God is with you.
I don't know about God.
But thank God you are with me.
I'm telling you, everything will be okay.
Have faith in God.
It's my mother's birthday tomorrow.
Our birthdays are on the same day.
We used to celebrate every year.
Mom would cook for us.
Chicken rice, beef...
Prawn curry is my favorite.
Dad used to visit the north.
He had learnt how to cook paratha.
All of us would sit in a circle
and eat together.
Dad would tell us stories
about places he had visited.
Rajasthan.
Punjab.
Gujarat.
I am sure they must be missing you.
Your sister must be in college, right?
She's dead.
They killed her.
Dad too.
Only Mom is alive.
She must be all alone.
And I won't be able to wish her!
Your birthday is in 15 minutes.
Listen.
Don't tell anyone about this.
Or I'll be in deep trouble.
Here you go.
Happy birthday!
Call your mother and wish her.
Quick!
And...
please talk softly.
Mom!
Mom, it's me!
Happy birthday, Mom!
Allah hafiz, Mom.
Will you be back before
my holidays begin?
Definitely.
Don't lie to me, Dad.
I said I'll be back by then.
JK, please tell me the truth.
He's telling you the truth.
He's going for a training
workshop to Srinagar.
You don't have to
worry about anything.
Dad, please don't go!
I'll call you every day.
Okay?
And don't trouble your mom.
Okay? Promise?
You two are fighting, aren't you?
It's obvious, I'm not a kid.
Really?
You're a grown-up, aren't you?
Sri is going to Srinagar!
"Sri! Srinagar!"
Get it?
You've also begun lying to me?
Nobody can lie to you
and your husband!
Actually...
there's an enquiry going on against him.
So it's kind of a punishment.
But don't worry.
Sri is our boss' favorite.
He won't let him stay there for long.
I hope it's not a mission or something.
Oh, God...
There is no mission, Suchi!
Don't worry.
Everything's fine.
How much longer, Sri?
Don't be glued to your phone.
-Take care of him--
-Help him with his homework.
Put him to sleep on time.
I know all that, okay?
Now will you answer my question, please?
-What?
-Is everything fine between you and Mom?
-You two cool?
-What do you mean?
Shut up!
Go get a glass of water.
Go!
Just focus on playing
the flute and the harmonica.
Got it? You need to master them.
We're spending a lot of money.
Dad, remember how
you thrashed that man?
Didn't I tell you to keep your mouth shut?
Yes, but even I want
to learn how to fight!
Why do you want to learn that?
You haven't even learned to touch
your elders' feet for blessings!
When was the last time
you touched my feet?
Do it.
Go on.
May you always be happy.
Suchi, please!
Bye.
You're not doing this to
get back at me, are you?
No. I am just...
following the
department's orders.
I know you won't get the time but...
call me at least once a
day and tell me you're okay.
Okay, bye.
I'd have taken a taxi.
Why did you come?
Don't dick around with me.
The cold war's between you and Suchi.
Not between us.
-Move it!
-"Move it!"
Mom!
Is everything okay
between you and Dad?
Yes. Why?
I just felt...
-What?
-I don't know.
I am sad.
What is it, darling?
Don't worry, Dad will be back soon.
Okay?
I hope so.
Mom...
I don't feel like going to school.
So don't go.
You can grow up to be a housemaid.
I'll tell our maid to train you.
I'll also give you an internship at home.
Very funny!
-I screwed up again.
-What?
You mean, once again?
-Sorry, I meant...
-No.
I took it too far this time.
Listen, man.
Don't worry about Suchi.
She'll calm down.
I've known you two for fifteen years.
Nothing will change.
One more thing.
Don't stroll around
all alone in Srinagar.
Always carry your gun.
When in doubt...
shoot first.
Who's your CO there?
Guess.
Come on, tell me.
Saloni.
Oh, fuck!
-You think it's funny?
-Shit!
Why do such things
happen only with you?
This is fucking ridiculous!
Saloni!
And that too in the middle of this mess!
As-salaam alaikum, General.
I have good news.
Wa alaykumu as-salam.
Our mujahid will be
discharged from the hospital
in a couple of days.
I've asked the sleeper cell to
be on standby for the operation.
Good.
We need to get Zulfiqar back on
track as soon as possible
We cannot waste any more time!
Is our second fighter in place?
Yes, sir.
He got his orders
and has left for Kashmir.
Remember...
this time, there should be no mistakes.
Sir.
Khuda hafiz.
Hello, sir.
Sorry, I just saw your message.
-Are you there yet?
-Just landed, sir.
I've sent you to
Srinagar for a reason.
I'm not that stupid, sir.
I've been working with
you for years now.
I was awaiting your orders.
We've got information from RAW
that a key asset of Mission Zulfiqar
has arrived in Kashmir.
I want you to dig deeper into this.
Be careful, it's Kashmir.
Things might blow out of proportion.
Thank you, sir.
I'll keep that in mind.
Okay, sir.
They're here to receive me.
Okay. Take care.
Thank you, sir.
-How are things here nowadays?
-Can't you see?
It feels like a free bird has been caged.
These fuckers call Kashmir
the "crown of India."
But they treat us like shit.
If they had as much concern
for the Kashmiri people
as they have for Kashmir,
things would be different.
That's the dilemma.
But everything is going to change now.
Inshallah!
How are things here nowadays?
All good!
We call the shots here.
I heard the number of tourists
have increased.
I can see the tourists...
in uniform.
When do I meet Basharat?
-I don't know.
-So what do I do?
Just lie low and wait.
They will let you know later.
"If there is ever heaven on earth...
it is here, it is here."
-What's wrong?
-I want to see my brother.
Asif?
But you don't have
access to that room.
I need to see him, Mary.
I need to see my brother.
But how will you go in there?
What are you doing?
Mary...
I have to see him.
Moosa...
My supervisors will question me.
I'll lose my job.
Mary...
I won't put you in trouble.
Trust me.
I'll be right back.
Did you squeal to the infidels?
No, Asif Bhai.
I didn't.
What are you doing here?
Nothing personal, Asif Bhai.
Potassium.
I injected it into your bloodstream.
Close your eyes.
You'll die in peace.
I don't want you to squeal
to the infidels...
about Zulfiqar.
Allah hafiz, brother.