He'll be here for the next few days.
They call him Al Qatil.
He's just like the ISIS. Brutal.
He's the best.
Killing infidels is his only goal.
He's been making chemical
bombs for ISIS.
I don't think...
ISIS will ever let go
of a capable person like him.
Never.
That's why we need to
get him out of here.
And then, with the help of your men...
he can cross into India.
That can be arranged.
Daesh is going to lose the war.
They cannot win,
no matter what they do.
They can fight it out
for another year, at the most.
We cannot let them waste his talent.
Instead of him being shot or caught
we could put him to good use.
As-salaam alaikum.
What have the terrorists
reduced this nation to!
Even hell must be better.
And you take orders
from such people?
I only listen to His orders.
Do you?
Or of those who pay you
in American dollars?
Faizan Bhai!
-As-salaam alaikum
-Wa alaykumu as-salam.
Meet this gentleman.
This is my guardian and
a dear friend, Major Sameer.
He works for the ISI
and has come from Pakistan
just to meet you.
As-salaam alaikum, Sameer Bhai.
Wa alaykumu as-salam.
I've heard a lot about you.
-Al Qatil, right?
-Sameer Bhai...
I don't label my work.
Isn't that Istanbul's Shia Masjid?
-In 2016, around--
-270 people died.
It was the biggest chemical attack
in ten years.
You used the nerve gas which
ISIS stole from Syria, right?
That too...
with other things.
I customized the nerve agent
to maximize the damage.
If the blast had been bigger
buildings would
have been destroyed...
with bodies scattered around.
It would have been a spectacle on TV.
There should've
been more destruction.
Pardon me, Faizan Bhai.
But there was destruction.
270 dead bodies.
I don't work because
I want publicity on TV.
I wanted to kill the most
number of infidels.
Faizan Bhai!
Please excuse us.
What?
I have a mission for you.
A very special one.
Mission Zulfiqar.
Saloni Bhatt!
-After so many years!
-Yup!
Nagaland.
Feels like... it was ages ago.
I never thought we'd meet again.
Neither did I.
Now you're my CO.
-Does that bother you?
-What?
Why would it bother me?
It's so good to see you.
You're still the same.
But you've gotten old.
So...
-how's your husb--
-My who?
Your...
husband... Husband.
You don't even know his name.
Come on!
I don't chant his name all the time.
And we haven't been in touch.
So you are telling me that
I didn't keep in touch?
No. All I was saying is...
It's so good to see you
after all this time.
Come on, tell me.
What's his name?
What's the name of the fortunate soul
who got to marry you, Your Highness?
I'm not telling you shit!
Follow me!
Of course!
That's what I've always done.
So this is it.
The headquarters is in Jammu.
This is a temporary office.
-You can take that desk.
-Okay.
And listen, Srikant.
You don't need to do anything.
Just try and stay out of the way!
Don't create a mess
like you did in Mumbai, please.
Sorry.
Maybe that was out of line.
It was.
Okay, settle down.
Thank you.
Saloni.
I wanted to ask you something.
Have you heard about Mission Zulfiqar?
Zulfiqar?
No.
There's a young man...
who has just arrived in Kashmir.
No one knows how he looks
or where he's staying.
But we do know that
he's an important asset
for this mission.
Oh.
Is that why you are here?
So this is not a
punishment posting?
No, it is a punishment posting.
But they want me
on this as well.
Has Kulkarni sent you?
Okay, let me ask military
intelligence if they know anything.
-I'll get back to you.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
-Can we have lunch together?
Not a chance.
Doctor, is it possible
-that he tried to kill himself?
-I don't think so.
The cause of his death
is cardiac arrest.
But...
it looks a bit fishy.
-What do you mean?
-I mean...
he did have
internal injuries.
But he was recovering quite well.
His GCS score was eleven.
-And you mean eleven was good?
-Yes.
When he came in,
his score was five.
So, eleven was good.
-Show me the sheet.
-Yeah.
According to the log sheet,
he was quite stable.
Did you guys observe anything
unusual in his cardio activity?
No, sir. The patient
died due to arrhythmia.
But we're unable to
diagnose what caused it.
Did you notice anything
strange yesterday?
No, sir. All vitals were good.
And you?
What's your name?
-Mary.
-Did you notice anything?
No, sir.
Dr. Patel, all those who had
access to the secure wing
cannot leave the city while
the investigation is on.
Sure.
Think again, Talpade.
Are you sure nothing's fishy?
I don't know how or when they did it.
Someone would have seen something, right?
But everything is clean here.
That's why I have my doubts.
Our biggest lead on Zulfiqar...
comes out of a coma and dies.
And nobody knows how!
Forward his medical report to me.
I'll do that.
Since Asif's dead,
Sharma is planning to
reduce the security here.
Has Sharma fucking lost it?
-Listen, tell Pasha--
-Pasha has been suspended.
You're not on the case anymore.
I am doing what I can.
And Asif was not our friend.
He was a wanted terrorist.
One of the Zulfiqar bastards has died.
This is good for us, Tiwari.
I don't know, man.
-What do you mean?
-Talpade, I'm telling you
this just doesn't seem right.
Alright. Until a permanent
solution is found
I'll put our juniors
around the hospital.
-Is that good enough?
-Talpade, do one thing.
Make arrangements to move Moosa to jail.
-Okay.
-He'll be safer there.
I'll do it.
ATS has withdrawn
almost all security.
But Moosa is still here.
This place can't be left unguarded.
How many ATS guys do we have now?
Only two.
But we can't count on them.
You guys stay here and be alert.
If need be, take turns.
As long as that fucking Moosa is here
we're responsible for his safety.
I am going to get
Moosa's judicial custody.
I want updates every half an hour.
Got it? I'll be back.
-Hi, Suchi.
-Hi.
Welcome!
I thought you called me to your office.
We'll get an office
when we have the funds.
Until then, this café is our office.
-Your entire team is here?
-It's okay!
Consider this your own office, okay?
Come.
Nikhil? Suchitra.
-Oh, hi. Welcome.
-Hi.
-I'll see you guys later.
-Oh, sure.
Guys? She's Suchitra
and she's the VP Marketing
for our company.
-Say hi.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Come, sit.
Why did you tell
everyone I'm a VP?
Because you are.
Everybody's a VP in
this company, so chill.
Okay, listen.
I was working on
the presentation
and I've noted
down a few points.
"Noted down" as in?
On paper?
Dhriti's always fighting
for the laptop, that's why.
Do you need a laptop?
Take mine.
But...
What would you like to have, ma'am?
-Can I order in some time?
-Sure.
Yeah. Here we go.
You're sure, right?
Yeah, it's cool.
I'll order another one.
-Thank you for the laptop.
-Welcome.
Now if you don't mind,
I have a lot of work to do.
Are you sure he's hiding there?
Intel's good, sir.
-Any movement?
-Negative, sir.
Copy. Wait for me till I get there.
-ETA seven minutes.
-Sir.
Are you sure this is
connected to Zulfiqar?
Major Vikram thinks so.
Once we catch them,
we'll know for sure.
You guys stay here.
I'll be back in a bit.
Firdaus.
Checking the parameter.
Unit One, ready to engage.
-Anything?
-No, sir.
Nothing since we came here.
Let's go.
First floor clear, sir.
Second floor clear, sir.
He's gone.
Check all the rooms.
Cigarette?
I have quit.
So you've changed after all.
A lot has changed.
You just know some
old version of me.
Really?
Tell me more about
this new version.
Why?
Why now?
Listen, Saloni...
I'm sorry, sorry for everything.
Won't you apologize as well?
Why should I?
-It was your fault.
-Oh, really?
And you're not to be blamed?
Yes. It was all your fault.
So this is what you have
been telling yourself?
You were equally responsible.
Actually more!
You actually believe
-that I was equally responsible?
-Absolutely!
You are unbelievable!
And I'm such a fool
to have felt guilty all this time!
Such a wastage of guilt!
What?
If we had married
we would've killed each other.
And we'd have continued fighting
in the afterlife.
"It was your fault!"
"No, it was yours!"
Exactly!
Nobody there.
But the good news is
that this was definitely a safe house.
And if my guess is right,
Basharat was here too.
Now it won't take long to trace him.
Basharat knows everything
that happens in Kashmir.
He was operating out of POK for years.
He's involved in every infiltration
that takes place across the border.
He's got a network of local support.
And now, he's active on
this side of the border.
If your asset is planning
anything in Kashmir
he'll definitely meet Basharat.
I'm pretty confident about that.
-Mom!
Watch it!
Both of you, shut up!
I am the one driving!
Your little Lilliput leg can't
even reach the accelerator!
So stop teaching me!
She called you a Lilliputian.
-That was for you, dumbass.
-Shut up!
Let me drive peacefully, please!
I don't know why
I stopped driving.
Listen, after the music class,
please wait there for me.
I will pick you up, okay?
-Can we go somewhere else, please?
-Yes, Mom!
-No!
-Please!
Do you know how much
your classes cost?
Yeah, we know!
Suchi, since when did
you become so boring?
-I swear!
-What?
Atharv, what did you just say?
-And why are you laughing?
-Mom, please!
-Shall we go to the mall?
-Yes!
People will think you starve at home.
You said we could
order anything, right?
And now you're lecturing us?
Yeah, but this way too much!
Go easy!
Look at this.
Very pretty, right?
No?
Too bright.
Try this on, please.
I don't wear such clothes.
Mom!
Trust me, I know my shit.
What kind of language--
-Mom, please!
-How can you talk like that?
Not allowed.
Wow! Sexy!
Yeah? Too much, right?
You've not grown old yet.
So, chill.
-Go, answer it.
-You do it!
You always do this!
Hello.
What's happening, you little brat?
Dad, I've decided that I'll learn
to play the ukulele.
-But why?
-What do you mean?
I've already learned all
the other instruments.
Okay, tell me how was school?
Dad, guess what!
We went out today.
Mom took us to the mall.
It was so much fun.
But then Mom and Dhriti
started shopping.
That was the end of the fun part.
Please! Mom did not
let me buy anything.
But she bought six
new tops for herself.
Wow! You guys are having fun.
Yeah, Mom gave us a treat
for her new job.
Really?
-What's she doing?
-I don't know.
She's always glued to her laptop.
What the...
You got a MacBook!
Are you seriously kidding me?
Dad, Mom bought a brand-new Apple.
Apple?
Do you even know how to use this?
-Wow!
-This is so unfair!
-I use that piece of junk...
-Hello?
-Mom! Just let me see it.
-Why?
Dhriti!
Fuck!
Oh, fuck!
Give me two glasses of tea.
Why is it not hot?
I just made it.
-Yes?
-Talpade, where's Pasha?
He's with me. Why?
Take him along and
go to the hospital.
What's the matter?
Do you know about Al Qatil?
ISIS.
The executioner of Raqqa.
He's number six on the FBI list.
So, yes, I know him. Go on.
This guy, Moosa...
Moosa is Al Qatil.
That fucker!
-What are you saying!
-He fucking fooled us all!
We were too busy focusing on Asif!
Moosa turned out to be Al Qatil!
Call ATS and ask them
to increase security.
And get moving, immediately!
We need to get to the hospital.
Let's go!
Sir, we need security in
the hospital immediately!
Because Srikant thinks
that Moosa is Al Qatil?
I think he's right.
What if he's wrong?
Sir, all I'm asking for
is an increase in security.
Only till we move Moosa to jail.
Please, sir.
Fine. I'll speak to the ATS chief
and assign a unit to the hospital.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
The number you are trying to call--
There's no network, is there?
Okay, I'm going to the café.
Do you need something?
Jayesh?
Okay, I'm also going for a smoke.
You want to come along?
I'm good.
Come in.
-Sir, you wanted to see me?
-Yes, Mary. Come, sit.
Mary...
I thought I should talk to you,
before speaking to security.
What happened, sir?
Asif's case was not
assigned to you, right?
Then what were you doing
in his room last night?
Sir...
Actually... I didn't...
Your access card was the
last to be swiped...
right before he died.
Roll down your window.
Okay, go ahead.
Let them through.
Check all your stuff.
I don't want any mistakes.
Bilal Bhai, can I ask you something?
Will the four of us be enough
for this assignment?
Get this straight
never teach Daddy how to fuck!
Why are you getting mad at me?
Are we really here to fetch Al Qatil?
Will you stop talking?
Just drive the fucking car!
-Are you all ready?
-Yes, bhai!
Keep the car ready. Got it?
We're here.
How many?
Two in the control room,
and the rest, upstairs.
Let's go.
Go upstairs.
Zoya.
Yes, Milind?
Can you get me a
coffee too, please?
I knew you would ask.
I already have one.
Jayesh, you're here?
Yes, I had to make a call.
Have you pumped enough
smoke into your lungs?
It's a hospital.
Smoking's not allowed.
Okay. Well, you'll live longer.
I'll see you inside.
Jayesh, is everything okay?
-Yes, sir. What happened?
-Stay alert.
Tell the others to be alert as well.
I've requested extra security from ATS.
They're on their way.
And secure all the exits.
-But what happened, sir?
-There's no confirmation
but Srikant thinks something's up.
Pasha and I are almost there.
Warn the guards too, and...
just be safe.
Al Qatil.
How are you, Bilal?
Fuck!
Shit!
Milind, red alert.
We're under attack.
We need backup.
Do you copy?
Fuck!
-I am coming there!
-Shit! Shit!
Shit!
We're under attack!
Zoya!
-Moosa's escaping.
-Fuck!
Milind, check for backup.
Give me the bag.
Hurry up.
Drive! Let's go!
Fuck!
The black car!
Catch the black car!
Go! Go!
-Fuck!
-They won't be able to get too far.
They will get caught.
-Where's Jayesh?
-Nowhere to be found.
He's not even answering his phone.
-Go in and look for him.
-Yes.
Let's check the number of casualties.
Shit! What a mess!
Yes?
What?
What do you mean?
If not in the van, where are they?
Pasha!
They are still inside the hospital.
What?
Pasha!
I think we lost him.
Fuck!
Moosa!
We didn't get Moosa, did we?
When I step out...
will you scream for help?
Are you sure?
Please...
don't hurt me.
How can I hurt you?
You're my Mary.
How can I...