In a brazen attack on Fortune Hospital
in Mumbai, last night,
terrorists went on a shooting spree
and killed multiple people,
that include hospital staff
patients and...
Security agencies are yet to release
the exact number
of casualties.
A lot of casualties
have been reported.
It's quite shocking actually.
According to our sources at least
18 people have died
including the four assailants
at the Fortune Hospital massacre.
What is the ATS doing?
What is the NIA doing?
What are we doing
right now to ensure
that such things and such incidents
do not happen in my city again?
I request our honorable leader,
the Prime Minister of India
to order an immediate, decisive
and fitting surgical strike
upon our enemies again.
And make it clear, once and
for all that new India
will not take it lying down.
Hello.
Is this Mohammad's shop?
Yes, tell me.
May I speak to Meherunnisa?
Meherunnisa?
Who's calling?
I...
I am a relative.
Okay.
The landlord asked
her to vacate a year ago
because she couldn't pay rent.
I think... she left after that.
Do you know where she went?
No, I haven't heard
from her ever since.
Any information at all?
Please, sir.
Well, she always said
that her son would get
her out of the village.
Maybe that's what happened.
Maybe she's in the Gulf, with her son.
As-salaam alaikum, brother!
How's everything?
Have you eaten yet?
What do I have to do next?
Is Basharat going to meet me?
I have no idea
about that, brother.
-So are you here for a stroll?
-I am here to check on you.
We wanted to ensure that you're fine.
"We"?
-Who is "we"?
-Don't ask questions.
Just do what you're told.
That's the order.
Whose order?
I don't know who the fuck you are!
Or what the fuck
I'm doing in Kashmir!
Someone gives me
new instructions every day!
Nobody knows what
the fuck is going on!
Get out of here!
Hang on.
What are you doing?
Get the fuck out of here!
And whoever's giving you orders,
tell him to speak to me directly.
And if it's Faizan Bhai issuing the orders
tell him, I want to speak to him.
I want to listen to his voice.
And I need all the
details of this mission.
What to do and when to do it.
Everything!
Saloni, I've worked
with many people...
but never met anyone like Pasha.
His duty was his only priority!
First, those three innocents
were killed, and now Pasha!
Come on, Srikant.
You can't blame
yourself for everything.
I can't just sit here and watch!
Hello, sir.
Yes, Srikant.
-How are things there, sir?
-Don't ask.
TASC is on the verge
of being shut down.
Sir, I think we should
be on high alert.
Moosa has been sent
for a special purpose.
And he's also a chemical weapons expert.
I think they're
planning something big.
I've issued a red alert
across all cities in India.
Sir, I have information that
a few more are involved.
-There's a whole team in Kashmir--
-Srikant, let us handle this.
If I need you, I'll let you know.
You need to stay
away from the field.
Take care, Srikant.
Talpade, what the fuck
is happening there?
Goddammit!
It's just one problem after another.
TASC is going to face an inquiry.
-Any news on the hospital attack?
-Nothing.
Seems like it was a new sleeper cell.
It wasn't even on our radar.
-Did you meet Pasha's family?
-I met his mother.
His father refused to see Pasha's corpse.
His mother wants him
buried in his hometown.
Talpade...
what about Moosa's mother?
What?
That bastard was talking
about meeting his mother.
Do you think he was telling us the truth?
I don't think that bastard
even has a mother!
I don't know why
I think he was being
truthful about this.
I don't know.
I can't understand what's going on!
Find out.
-Find out.
-Okay.
Hello.
Hi. What happened?
I got her blood test done.
But nothing showed up.
I got it done again.
I don't know why I'm
getting worried now.
The fever won't go away.
Isn't your wife there?
Is anybody there?
Nobody's here right now.
I am all by myself, for a few days.
-Do you need any help?
-No, it's okay. It's fine.
I'll manage.
I just fed her some noodles.
Arvind!
Your daughter's not well
and you fed her noodles?
Are you mad?
-Hi.
-How come you're...
I mean, come in.
Hi, Rhea!
I am Suchi.
Are you hungry?
Yes?
Would you like to have Rasam Rice?
Please! You'll get a lot of chips as well!
Okay? I'll make it in a jiffy.
Arvind, where's the coriander?
Here.
-Should I cut it for you?
-No, that's fine.
Where are the curry leaves?
-Curry leaves... here.
-Thanks.
And where's the garlic?
Here.
It's stale!
The maid chopped it yesterday!
Then, give it to your maid.
Here is your chip...
topped with some Rasam Rice.
Come on, open your mouth.
Very good!
When Dhriti was younger,
she was just like this.
And now she acts like she's my mum.
Why did I not think
about the chips?
I mean, it's super tasty!
And thanks for coming.
Thank you.
By the way, do you feel like working?
Yeah, sure. With beer?
We shouldn't emphasize the AI part.
I mean, AI is good
but eventually,
it's artificial intelligence. So...
So, yeah, it can never
replace human intelligence.
-Yes.
-Got it.
I'll finish it off later.
Are you going to finish this?
-I'm not a beer person.
-May I?
Thank you.
So...
Rhea's mother...
I mean, where is she...
It's a long story.
If I tell you,
it will spoil our mood.
Yes, Priyanshu.
Yeah, we're all set.
Yeah, we'll be there.
Of course.
Yeah, see you. Bye.
That was our VC.
We have a solid spot.
The investor's quite excited to meet us.
-That's great.
-It's at Lonavala.
So be ready, we're going.
But weren't you and
Nikhil supposed to go?
Yeah, but Nikhil wants you there.
What will I do there?
I don't have any experience.
It's always good to
have a girl on the team.
Listen, I'm not going to go there
as a glamour girl!
That's not what I meant.
It will be good for you.
I'm telling you, trust me.
-Are you sure?
-Hundred percent.
So, be ready.
I'll pick you up.
-Okay?
-Okay.
There's news from Kashmir
that your boy Sajid
has a lot of complaints.
You know how moody these boys can be.
No!
All I know is
Mission Zulfiqar has begun.
And for it to succeed
everybody needs to
follow the orders.
Tell that boy...
that nobody knows
everything about the mission.
So he should stop complaining
and focus on the work given to him.
-Or else, we have other ways--
-I'll talk to him.
The problem is, Sajid doesn't
know who our other fighter is.
What do you mean?
Sajid and Moosa became good friends
at my training camp.
I know how to convince Sajid.
Then do it!
We cannot afford to waste any more time.
After this, I shouldn't get
a single call from Kashmir.
I'll take your leave now.
I'll see you again when we
finish this mission.
-Khuda hafiz.
As-salaam alaikum,
Basharat Bhai.
Why haven't you met him yet?
We can deploy two units.
-We can position Unit Bravo.
-Okay.
And lead Unit Alpha ourselves,
and wait on the bridge.
-Yes?
-Srikant, there's an update for you.
We've just got intel
that Basharat will attend
a wedding in Baramulla.
-We won't get a better opportunity.
-Good.
But we can't enter the village.
-Why?
-We'll wait outside
and keep an eye on Basharat.
As soon as he leaves the
wedding, we'll get him.
Why can't we arrest
him during the wedding?
Sir, Baramulla is often
referred to as "mini-Pakistan."
Every house, every shop
has "Go India, go back,"
written on its walls.
The army is not welcome there.
Before mounting an operation
we need to get a clearance from the top.
If things go wrong, it will be
all over the news.
I don't get it.
Why is he attending a wedding?
Because Basharat is no fool.
He knows that the army
monitors his every move.
So, why would the lion
step out of the jungle
and head towards the city?
Sir, maybe he's sure we
won't get him in Baramulla.
It's his hometown.
Or maybe he's got orders...
to attend the wedding.
Would he risk his life for an order?
What if he's coming
to meet the asset?
It's a possibility, Saloni.
And even if the asset
does not show up
we'll know everything
once we get Basharat.
We have to wait here.
We can't go ahead.
Sri, come see this!
That's Basharat.
-Can you zoom in, please?
-Yes, ma'am.
I can't believe Munni
is getting married today.
It seems like only yesterday...
when she was playing with her brothers.
May God bless both of them.
Can you lower it a bit, please?
Sorry, sir.
If we do that, we could be detected.
I know her brothers are
watching over her from heaven.
Come, Basharat Bhai.
This is the room, as you wanted.
Basharat Bhai...
Thank you so much.
You have blessed the
wedding with your presence.
Please don't embarrass me, Tariq Bhai.
Munni is like my daughter.
How could I not be here?
No. Your presence
is enough for us.
Don't worry. Please, keep it.
Basharat Bhai!
-As-salaam alaikum.
-Wa alaykumu as-salam.
How are you?
I am good, by the grace of Allah!
-How are you?
-Alhamdulillah!
Please do not go till the
marriage is solemnized.
I'm not going anywhere.
-I'll stay for the feast.
-Inshallah.
Please make yourself comfortable.
Who is Tariq?
How is he related to Basharat?
Tariq's two sons were
militants who got martyred.
Excuse me, could you please
stop calling them "martyrs"?
If a terrorist dies
they call him a martyr
to get ten more recruits!
Sir, I was just using
the term they use.
Oh, really?
Do you feel the same way?
Sir, do we need to prove
our loyalty every day?
Is that a problem?
Okay, guys! Chill!
Chill, please!
As-salaam alaikum.
I am Sajid.
Did you know pigeons
used to be our postmen?
A pigeon used to fly across
the border with our message.
And another used to fly back.
Three months ago,
the BSF arrested a pigeon.
Some Kahwah?
Look...
I need to know
whether I'll get to
speak to Faizan Bhai or not?
It's been so many days!
Nobody has told me a thing.
I don't like to work like this.
I want to know
the whole mission...
and speak to Faizan Bhai.
Why are you so restless?
The Sajid that Faizan spoke about,
was not like this.
It's been only two days
since you came to Kashmir.
And you're already full of anger.
Kashmir that does that to you.
I want to finish my
work and leave quickly.
Brother, the groom
wants to speak to you.
Give him the phone.
Okay.
Sir, we're tracing a satellite call.
Guys!
-As-salaam alaikum, brother.
-Wa alaykumu as-salam.
How are you?
Everything's good.
Then why are you
not agreeing to the marriage?
I didn't do so.
I just want to
get to know the bride better.
If I'm going to sacrifice
my life for a girl...
I should be allowed
to make inquiries.
One makes inquiries only
when there's lack of trust.
Your elder brother
has chosen the bride.
Elder brother?
Your elder brother, Chettan.
Chettan?
Is he attending the wedding?
Yes, I assure you,
he knows you
better than you know yourself.
It's good that he
chose the bride.
Is there anything else I can do for you?
No, your assurance is enough.
Have patience,
you'll get the details soon.
I'll be waiting.
-Khuda hafiz.
That's definitely code.
Can you run a voice
analysis on the two?
Yes, ma'am.
I was told that this is the most
critical mission of our fight.
That's why I have
come back to Kashmir
without caring about my safety...
to ensure that this
mission succeeds.
Remember...
you have been chosen
for this sacred task.
You are Allah's most special.
Don't mess it up.
The groom's voice doesn't match.
But the other one matches
with Faizan Ahmed's voice.
Fuck! He's on the CIA's most wanted list.
Faizan was speaking to our asset.
Who's Chettan?
Any matches?
No, ma'am.
Chettan.
Could it be "Chettan" like
big brother in Malayalam?
Malayalam?
Malayalis call their
big brother as Chettan.
Moosa.
Moosa is Chettan.
Vikram, I think
we should move in.
You can't, Srikant.
I've already told you this,
the army cannot enter.
But I can, unofficially.
Sir, it's too risky.
Fuck the risk.
Srikant, as your commanding officer,
I forbid you.
Don't take too much time, Srikant.
And keep your head down.
Okay.
Sir, I'll wait here.
If I go further, they'll recognize me.
Okay, sir?
Good luck.
-Try to blend in, Srikant.
-Nobody will recognize me.
I'm wearing a Kashmiri dress.
My cheeks are rosy, like apples.
It's not funny, Srikant.
Please be careful.
As-salaam alaikum.
How do you say
"congratulations" in Kashmiri?
Sri, please don't.
Tell me quickly.
-Mubaarak.
-Give me a slightly longer phrase.
As-salaam alaikum.
Tuichu hat laikh mubaarak.
Wish me good luck.
As-salaam alaikum, Tariq Bhai.
-Congratulations to you and your family!
-Congratulations!
That's Sajid.
He took up a three-year course
but has been at it for six years now!
I think I got him.
How do you know?
I never forget a person's face.
Who are you talking to?
My father. He's up there.
He knows something's up,
I'm going after him.
Srikant, please don't!
Firdaus, he's coming towards you.
Catch the motherfucker.
Copy. I'll stop him.
Get me visuals, quick!
There he is!
Srikant, get back to base now.
I'll catch him at any cost!
No, Srikant. It's not safe there.
Don't be a hero.
Get back to base now!
Shut up, Saloni!
We have our fucking
asses on the line here!
He never listens, Vikram!
Done running, motherfucker?
I have the target,
send the backup.
Srikant, get out of there.
Abort and return to
base immediately.
I repeat. Abort.
Shut up and send the backup.
Srikant, get the fuck
out of there, right now!
We can't come in. I mean it!
Srikant! Sri... Srikant!
Sit down.
Listen, motherfucker!
This is not a joke!
Sit down!
He has led Srikant back
to the wedding.
-We have to get him out.
-I'm going in right now.
Vikram, you can't go in.
Let me go.
-It's not safe.
-I got it.
Fuck!
I'll blow your brains out!
Sit!
Brothers!
This man is from the army!
Indian Army!
He's come here to kill me.
He crashed the wedding.
These motherfuckers...
forcibly enter our
homes and brutalize us.
And if we protest,
they call us terrorists.
Another word, and I'll blow
your brains out, motherfucker!
I'll say a word!
A word which is on everybody's lips!
-Freedom!
Listen to me, please!
Don't be fooled.
He's a fugitive.
He has nothing to do
with your struggle.
If anything happens to him
things will get out of hand.
Everybody will suffer.
He crashed the wedding to spy on us!
He wanted to kill one of our guests.
Sir, he's not a guest.
He's a wanted criminal and a terrorist.
-He's killed many innocents--
-You consider all of us terrorists!
Go back to India!
Freedom!
Sir, you are misunderstanding me.
That is not the issue.
That man is from Mumbai.
He's the prime suspect in a
recent scooter blast that took place there
and we were after him.
Please listen to me, sir.
You know me.
I may be in the army...
but I work for the
welfare of Kashmiris.
I'm a Kashmiri.
Please, tell them to step back.
Otherwise, I'll be compelled
to call in my men.
For the sake of Kashmir, I request you.
If anything happens to this man
the army will barge in.
Even I won't
be able to help you then.
This valley has already
seen too much bloodshed.
Why do you want to taint
this joyous occasion as well?
Cigarette?
You don't smoke...
you don't drink.
Do you fool around with girls?
Not that either?
Stop playing that song.
What?
I don't like Gujarati songs.
Listen, asshole.
This is my truck!
I was the one who gave you a lift.
So I decide which song plays, got it?
You're not giving me a free lift.
What?
What is it?
The road's shut.
Take the other route.
You literally call the
shots in Srinagar.
There's a bloody curfew
and we're sipping hot tea
at the town square.
It's oppression, in the name of security.
You really think so?
We can do whatever we want
under AFSPA, and we do.
The result?
They launch an attack
and we enforce a curfew for weeks.
We shut down the internet
mobile services,
businesses, and schools.
We're oppressing them.
And it's the children
who have to pay the price.
Here, the people are
entirely at our mercy.
It's a crime to take
away a person's freedom.
And then, there are so
many players in the game.
Pakistan civil government,
the army, the ISI
our central government,
state government,
local politicians
and the Hurriyat.
They are all playing
their own games...
but it's the Kashmiri people
caught in the crossfire.
Sometimes it's difficult to figure out
who's right and who's wrong.
I mean, look at it from
their perspective.
In their eyes,
we are no different than the militants.
If only we had a regular job.
Simple and straight.
Wake up, go to work,
get your salary and go to sleep.
No need to rack your brains.
Just avoid any extra stress!
The problem is that our
work changes lives...
and the future of the country.
You know what
Kulkarni used to say?
They need to win only once...
but we need to win every time.
And, in the right way.
How do you know that maulvi?
You spoke to him
as if he's an old friend.
You can call it a friendship.
A convenient friendship.
We share the objective
of stopping the bloodshed in Kashmir.
But more often than not, we fail.
By the way,
-Major Vikram is very pissed at you.
-Why?
He thinks Basharat
escaped because of you.
They were tracking him
for a long time now.
I'm very sorry about that.
But it was imperative to catch Sajid.
We missed that
fucker by a whisker.
Don't worry, we'll find him.
Those bastards are very slippery.
Once they slither out,
it's very difficult to find them.
But now, we know who's
involved in Zulfiqar.
There's Faizan, then Moosa and Sajid.
Faizan is the worst!
He tells the other two to...
What happened?
We don't know where
Moosa and Sajid are.
But we do know where Faizan is.
He's hiding somewhere in Balochistan.
Exactly.
And he is on the CIA's most wanted list.
He's hiding in Pakistan.
How will we find him?
I know a guy who can help us.
You're not on the run, are you?
No, I mean...
You... kind of...
You have that look.
These days, it's all over the news.
I hope your mugshot
doesn't appear in the papers.
That's it.
You need to get down here.
I won't be going to the city.
I'll take a turn here.
Shouldn't have given him a lift.