Yeah, come in!
Mr. Lennington.
Srikant Tiwari of NIA is on the line
for you from India.
-Yeah, put him through.
-Okay, thank you.
Getting a patch from Islamabad.
Sir, connecting you to
Bruce Lennington in Islamabad.
-Hi, Bruce.
-Hey, Srikant.
Been a while!
How have you been?
I've been fine. How are you?
All good. What's happening?
What's up?
Okay, Bruce.
I have someone...
you've been desperately
looking for.
-Go on. I'm all ears.
-Faizan Ahmed.
-Tell me.
-I have his satellite number
and the location where he's hiding.
You're sure it's Faizan?
Absolutely.
Where is he now?
Somewhere in Zhob province,
in Balochistan.
-You have his exact location?
-Not yet.
But we'll get it.
But I need a favor from you in return.
What favor?
I want to have a chat
with him in person.
That...
I don't know how we're
going to achieve that.
I mean, assuming we do nab him
I'm not going to be able
to bring him to India.
Well...
If the mountain doesn't
come to Muḥammad...
Alright. What's the plan?
Two words.
Dzhokhar Dudayev.
And you think that will work?
Dzhokhar Dudayev was
a Chechen rebel.
The KGB used a similar plan to get him.
You think this plan will work?
With a bit of luck.
Just a second.
Yeah, Zoya?
Sir, the tech team has
processed the voice sample
and they've sent us an
audio fingerprint back.
What do you think?
Sir, it might work,
but there's a problem.
The sample is too short.
A longer sample would've worked better.
This is it, Zoya.
We don't have time.
-Send it!
-Okay, sir.
Sending it to you right away.
And, sir...
-Good luck.
-Thank you, Zoya.
Okay, these are the six safe houses
around the coordinates we received.
He could be hiding in any one of these.
Tracking all these
houses as we speak.
Beaming visuals onto the screens.
We've got tactical units
in striking distance
at all these locations. You copy?
Are you sure that these are
the only possible places
-where he could be?
-I hope so.
These are the only locations we know
-that General Ansari uses.
-Okay.
How are things going on
at your end?
Well, using the voice sample
from the conversation
of Sajid with Faizan
we've managed to put
together his voice profile.
I think we can manage with that.
Play it.
As-salaam alaikum, brother.
Hello, I can't hear you--
No. It's too clear.
Add some more noise.
As-salaam alaikum, brother.
Hello, I can't hear you, brother.
The network's bad.
Very good. Play this one.
-Bruce, we're ready.
-Copy.
Connecting, sir.
All teams on standby
for target location.
TU1 is active and ready to launch.
Try again.
-Negative, sir.
-Connecting again, sir.
Hello?
As-salaam alaikum, brother.
Wa alaykumu as-salam, Sajid.
All well?
How did you find this number?
Hello, I can't hear you, brother.
-Play it.
-Hello!
Hello, I can't hear you, brother.
Wait, let me go to the terrace.
We don't get network in the house.
Focus, guys!
Come on.
-Bruce, did you see him?
-Where is he?
Waiting for target confirmation, sir.
Hello, brother!
-Hello. Can you hear me now?
-Play it.
-Hello.
-Hello?
-I can't hear you.
-Sajid?
-Do we have anything else?
-Nothing else, sir.
Fuck it! Play this on loop.
I can't hear you, brother!
-Hello, brother?
-Hello.
-I can't hear you.
-Hello, Sajid!
The network's bad.
There he is! Zoom in!
-Hello.
-I can't hear you.
-Hello, Sajid?
-Hello, I can't hear you, brother.
-Where are you talking from, hell?
-Target locked, sir.
Srikant.
-We got him.
-Yes!
Bloody idiot!
What is this "Faizan" issue?
He was hiding in our country
and we didn't know?
Bin Laden has already brought
us enough embarrassment.
We cannot go through that again.
The embassy has received a
call from the White House.
It's no secret that General Ansari
is responsible for this.
Apparently, the ISI is involved as well.
General Khursheed...
this is a very serious matter.
I agree, sir.
We are checking the travel records
of all our men and agents.
Whoever is responsible for
this will be exposed soon.
Hurry up with the investigations.
The Americans have threatened us
that they will stop giving us aid.
Speak to the Secretary of State.
-Yes, sir.
-That's all. Thank you.
General Khursheed.
Please wait.
-What's going on, Khursheed?
-I'm sorry, sir.
Ansari's men kept Faizan in hiding.
And what were you doing?
Why didn't you keep
an eye on Ansari?
We did, sir.
We trace him every second
he's outside Balochistan.
But on his own turf, we can't do anything.
We need to clean up this mess.
What if we need to get rid of Ansari?
That won't be easy.
He fought a war for Pakistan.
He's received
the Nishan-e-Haider award.
He knows the top brass
in the army and the ISI.
Find out about his contacts in the ISI.
We need to tread very carefully.
Wow, Mom! Very cool!
You've never dressed up
like this for work.
Okay, listen.
I'm going for
an important conference to Lonavala.
I will take some time to come back.
Okay?
You're a grown-up.
Look after the house and your brother.
Make sure he doesn't play
video games all day.
Those are Math tutorials.
Not everything on the
tablet is a video game!
I have asked Aunt Neelam to cook for you.
Eat whatever she cooks.
Do not fuss or waste the food.
And don't mess up the house.
Okay?
-If you want something to munch on--
-Mom!
Got it.
Forgot something else.
-Dhriti, get the door.
-Atharv.
Come on!
Hi!
Atharv, right?
I'm Arvind.
Mom?
Mom!
There's somebody at the door.
-Hi!
-Hi, Suchi.
-Come in.
-Hey, young lady!
You must be Dhriti, right?
Would you like to
have tea or coffee?
Filter coffee, if possible.
Sure.
Hello!
Don't you have to go to school?
You're getting late.
Get up, come on! Go!
Get up!
-Bye.
-Go.
Dhriti, lunch box.
-Who is he?
-I told you.
He's my colleague.
It looks like you're going
for a picnic, not a conference.
-Don't put too much sugar.
-Shit! You scared me!
-How's Rhea?
-She's feeling better.
My mom found out she's ill.
So, she took Rhea with her.
Thank God for grandmas!
-Listen.
-Here you go.
Nikhil is coming from Delhi.
So he'll meet us at the venue.
There's a start-up boot camp.
We'll be meeting our VCs over there.
Boot camp?
The techies don't like
the word "conference."
So they call it "boot camp."
Sounds cooler.
Nice?
Authentic filter coffee!
Sir, the Americans won't budge.
They don't care about
Zulfiqar or its threat to us.
Sir, please! I want to interrogate Faizan.
We neither have time,
nor Moosa and Sajid.
Faizan trained both of them.
If anybody knows about their
location and plan, it is Faizan.
This is an extraordinary
request, Srikant.
But this is an extraordinary
situation, sir!
You cannot go to
Balochistan officially.
That's alright, sir.
I can go unofficially.
What if you go unofficially...
and something happens to you?
You won't be able to get me out of there.
Sir, I've made some mistakes
which killed innocent people.
Sir, this is my only
chance to redeem myself.
My life or any other life
it isn't bigger than Zulfiqar.
Sir, my gut feeling says
something terrible will happen...
and no one can
imagine its extent.
Qazi is a bastard!
It's shameful
that a coward like him is the
Prime Minister of Pakistan.
I am sure he must have
led the CIA to Faizan.
That son of a bitch
dances to the tune of the whites.
And his butler, Khursheed!
Both the bastards--
Sir, I suggest
we commence phase two.
And what about Faizan?
Do you think he'll spill the beans?
Sir, Faizan barely knows
anything about Zulfiqar.
But he could lead them to us.
And you know our Prime Minister.
The moment he finds out,
he'll try to stop us at any cost.
You're right.
Maybe it's time.
Are we ready?
We can start phase two in
the next 48 hours.
Sameer...
we are nearing the end of our mission.
With Allah's grace,
this mission will be a success.
Inshallah!
I'll ensure it succeeds, sir.
The jet belongs to
this guy from Delhi.
He's one of the many businessmen doing
infrastructure work in Afghanistan.
This plane will touchdown
in Kandahar for a while.
RAW's asset, Mustafa,
will meet you there.
Balochistan is a two-hour
drive from there.
He'll take you there.
Srikant, you know that this
is completely off the record.
If you're caught,
you're on your own.
We cannot extract you.
I know the risks.
Are you sure about this?
There are other ways to
get information from Faizan.
We don't have time for that.
I should've done this
a long time ago, Saloni.
Good luck, Srikant.
Hi.
Welcome to the boot camp, sir.
-Hello, sir.
-Hi.
-Hello, ma'am.
-Your name, sir?
-Arvind and Suchitra.
Okay.
Ma'am, Arvind and Suchitra.
-Your card, sir.
-Thank you.
-Yours, ma'am.
-And your keys.
-Thanks.
-All the best, sir.
-Thank you.
-All the best, ma'am.
-Let's freshen up.
-Yeah.
So, Nikhil wants to do
the opening remarks.
Glad you came.
Because with all these men around,
-you'll create a--
-Arvind!
Listen...
-Are you done?
-Yeah.
-Thank you, thank you so much.
-Sorry.
Never mind.
You know what? I feel
you should speak too.
Because Nikhil tends to get
too technical sometimes.
You're more natural.
You can do it charmingly.
Charming?
I'm flattered, thank you.
What I mean...
is that you can
manipulate words.
Wow!
What a backhanded compliment!
-Thank you!
-You're welcome.
Take this.
So the story is that
your name is Fahd Ahmed.
Fahd Ahmed?
You have a spices business in Karachi.
We are business partners.
And we are travelling to
Quetta for work.
-Are you from Mumbai?
-Yes.
Great!
It's an incredible city!
I have seen it a lot in the movies.
But never got a chance to visit it.
It seems that my dream
of visiting India...
will always remain a dream.
How long have you been in Balochistan?
-Almost 17 years now.
-17 years! My God!
I am from Patiala.
Jasmeet Singh.
Jasmeet Singh?
I changed my name and came
here during the rebellion.
I thought of returning after two years.
But I postponed it every year
in the last 17 years.
Now, I am Mustafa from Quetta.
Don't you miss your city, your family?
I stay with my wife and children.
I lost my parents a few years ago.
But I wasn't able to go home.
Very few can make such
sacrifices for the nation.
Back home,
people just talk about patriotism.
Nationalists!
We have settled here now,
it's a nice place.
I have no complaints.
Now, this is our home.
But fear lurks, even at home.
If my cover is blown,
they'll take me away
and slaughter me like a dog.
Don't think of such things.
-What about your family?
-Of course. Here, have a look.
These two are the little Avengers,
with Thanos in the middle.
Mashallah! God bless!
Perception management
is an equally big challenge
in the field of mental health.
We've factored in the cost
of educating the support system
friends and family,
on how to deal with people
with mental health issues.
We plan to take out
social media campaigns
and ads on television, outreach
programmes and events in colleges.
Reaching out to young
influencers is a key priority.
Any questions?
Please feel free if you
have any questions
or if you need any
more clarifications.
I must assure you one thing.
There are not many models of such
kind in the market right now.
We're doing it out of passion
and of course,
financial viability.
So, any questions?
Arvind, can I add a few points?
-Yes, sure.
-Sure?
Hi, everyone. I'm Suchitra Iyer.
And I'd just like to add a few
points to what Nikhil said.
Normally, when others have
a small problem
like a swollen finger
or a toothache...
or a cough or cold,
what do we suggest them?
To go see a doctor.
If someone says
"I'm feeling too low.
I'm feeling too depressed," or
"I'm not in the mood."
What do we suggest them?
"Come on, let's grab a drink."
And the worst thing is
"Get some action tonight
and you'll be fine."
The problem is
we don't give as much
importance to mental health
as we give to physical health.
If our body has a problem,
we look for solutions.
But if anybody
needs mental help
which I strongly believe
that we all do at
some point of time.
Then, we don't know what to do.
And we won't do anything
for the fear of being laughed at.
This is where we
would like to come in.
We want to make sure that we not
only have easy access to help.
But we have to fight this
taboo of seeking help.
For the last 12 years,
I was living in my comfort zone.
I had a safe,
happy, and easy job.
Overnight, I decided that I'd
quit this job and I did.
I joined this company
where nothing is easy.
There are no benefits...
and there is no money.
Well, not yet, of course.
Believe you me, we do not have an office.
We have worked out of cafes
all over, except Starbucks.
Quite frankly, we can't afford it yet.
But seriously...
each one of us is
attached to this company.
And the reason for that...
is the idea behind it.
Which is very beautiful.
-Thank you.
-Great job, guys. We nailed it.
-Cheers to that.
-Cheers.
Guys, you know what?
I see Priyanshu there.
I'll be right back.
-All the best.
-Thanks.
-He's super excited.
-Yeah, he looks it also.
Listen.
I was a bit scared when
you said you wanted to speak.
I didn't know what you would say.
But when you started,
you were flawless.
So, congratulations!
I can't believe I actually did it.
-You liked it?
-I loved it.
-Atharv, switch off the TV.
-Why?
You watched it for an hour.
That's enough.
We have to be at Aunt Neelam's for dinner.
Come on, get up.
Let's go.
Don't try to be Mom.
-Hello, Mom.
-Did you guys have dinner?
No, we were about to leave.
You're leaving now?
Aunt Neelam must be waiting.
Go right away.
Yes, Mom, we are going.
By the way...
I will be late.
If you want, you two can sleep
at Aunt Neelam's.
No. We'll sleep here.
Okay, listen.
Latch the main door properly.
Okay? Don't forget about it.
Mom, are you going to take longer?
Yes, it does seem like it.
I will take time.
But I promise I'll be back
as soon as possible. Alright?
Okay. Don't worry, we're fine.
Okay, bye.
Leave the talking to me.
Just pretend to be asleep.
Papers?
Here.
What were you doing
in Afghanistan?
We have a spices business.
What's wrong with him? Hello.
He's been up all night.
He's my business partner...
from Karachi.
I think they're suspicious.
We need to search you.
-Are you married?
-What?
Have you been married?
Yes, twice.
My God! Twice!
Here, buy some gifts for your wives.
Take it. My time is more
important than money.
I'd like it if you sped things up.
Let them go.
Thank you.
-Khuda hafiz.
What were you doing?
He was a soldier,
not an Indian policeman.
You bribed him!
What if he had arrested us?
Bribery works everywhere, Jasmeet.
You saw the other soldier who went in?
He was speaking on the phone
without dialing a number.
-He was trying to threaten us.
-I see.
Indian policemen do
take bribes sometimes...
but even they are not this stupid.
Guess what!
-We got it.
-Yes!
We did it guys!
We did it!
-Okay!
-Where's the fucking champagne?
-Waiter!
-What?
Here. It's time to celebrate.
We have to celebrate.
-To Shrink Me!
-Cheers!
Cheers to you.
One more. Champagne!
-Happy birthday.
-Thanks!
-Thank you.
What's up!
Wow! You finally made it!
I thought you'd never come.
Let's crash for a bit and
leave early in the morning.
I want to reach before the kids wake up.
Hey, D!
Here.
Check this out.
Try it.
You don't know what
you're missing out on.
One should try everything in life.
Try it once.
Later, you'll be asking me for it.
Try it.
-Try it.
-I said no!
Fine. Your loss.
Just go home.
I don't even know why I called you!
You're such a loser!
Just go!
Go!
Dhriti!
Are you crying?
I won't tell Mom
that you went out!
Atharv, please go away.
I'm coming, okay?
Please, Dhriti.
Don't cry.
Please!
I'M FEELING BAD FOR
TAKING UP THE WHOLE BED
I CAN'T SLEEP
ME NEITHER
The CIA has kept Faizan in a
safe house in this city.
He's being monitored closely
by five men.
It's a secret location.
What about the guys
I had mentioned about?
They're on the way,
they must be arriving soon.
We'll need to wait a bit though.
We'll wait here.
Our team should be here by morning.
What happened, darling?
What's wrong?
He was born a monkey, right?
That's true.
He had a long tail as well.
We had it removed through
a complicated surgery.
Mom, you must have a few
pictures from our childhood.
Of course.
I'll show them to you.
Stop it!
Hi, Suchi.
-Hi.
-Is everything alright?
How are the children?
How are you?
The kids are fine.
You tell me. How are you?
And what's going on?
All is well.
The usual files and paperwork.
When are you coming back?
I want to come back soon.
But...
Let's see.
Is everything okay at home?
Yes, everything is fine here.
Don't worry about us.
Your work is important.
Focus on it.
Finish it and come back.
Sri...
as soon as possible.
They are here.
I need to go now.
Okay?
Thank you.
Hello!
What's happening?
-Untie him!
-What's happening?
There's no time to talk.
Get out of here before
someone finds out.
Let's go.
Faizan, let's go!
Thank you for saving my life.
-Are you from the Pakistan Army?
-We are from the ISI.
The Prime Minister himself
planned this operation.
The Prime Minister?
Listen to me carefully, Faizan.
We had no clue that
you were in Pakistan.
Or that you got caught.
It was very embarrassing
for the Prime Minister.
Pakistan already has
a bad reputation.
And when the world finds out
that we were harboring
a terrorist...
we'll have to face more ridicule.
All the nations in the
world will blacklist us.
I was only following
the sacred word of--
Stop that nonsense!
Save that for your recruits!
Got it?
You don't do it for God.
You do it for the American dollars.
-But I--
-Shut up! Don't you understand?
The Prime Minister got a call
from the Indian Prime Minister
threatening us with war.
Have you sent two of your boys
to India for a mission?
-Mission...
-Zulfiqar.
Mission Zulfiqar.
You have two options, Faizan.
Tell those two guys to
immediately abort the mission
and give us their location.
A car is waiting for you
at the end of this tunnel.
It will take you straight to the airport.
Here's your Saudi passport
and a ticket to Riyadh.
It's a parting gift
from the Prime Minister.
We know that you
funnel all your money
into a secret account in Saudi.
Say goodbye to Pakistan
and lead a peaceful life.
Or, stay six feet under the ground
in Pakistan,
buried in an unmarked grave.
We don't want Pakistan's name
dragged through the mud
because of you.
What do you want to do?
Can I go to Sudan?
I don't like the
climate in Saudi.
Is the climate in Sudan good?
Who are these people?
They'll be taking you to the airport.
Motherfucker!
Bastard! You betrayed me!
I'll screw each one of you!
Bastard!
I hope you got what
you wanted from him.
Got something.
But thank you, Bruce.
-Thank you for your help.
-Anytime, Srikant.
Sir, both Moosa and Sajid
have been trained by Faizan.
A few years ago
Lashkar-e-Taiba
got their hands on
a stockpile of nerve gas in POK.
This was later seized by the ISI.
Then, Major Sameer and Ansari
planned a secret mission.
Mission Zulfiqar.
Over a few years,
they slowly smuggled it
in small quantities
across the border, into Kashmir.
The nerve gas has been
stockpiled in a hideout in Kashmir.
The original plan was that
Moosa and Asif would enter India,
Asif would get all the nerve gas
from Kashmir into Delhi,
and Moosa would make
a bomb in Delhi.
But after Asif was caught,
Faizan chose Sajid for this task.
Sajid is sharper and
much more dangerous.
If my guess is right
then Sajid is currently
getting the nerve gas to Delhi.
Moosa is hiding somewhere.
And these two will meet in Delhi.
Nerve gas attack in Delhi.
-What a disaster!
-Yes, sir.
This time they didn't go for
terrorist attacks like 26/11
or the parliament attack
which were eventually blamed on
independent terrorist groups.
Nerve gas attack
means an act of war.
And this is not possible
without the government support.
Which means the Indian government
will have to go to
war with Pakistan.
This will give General Ansari
an opportunity
to carry out a coup.
And soon, they'll get control
over the Pakistan government.
Sir, Major Sameer has
all the information.
I think we should involve
the government of Pakistan.
We have to work together.
If this mission is successful
then this will be disastrous
for both the countries.
-Good job, Srikant.
-Yeah, good job, Srikant.
Thank you, sir.
Thanks for waiting, sir.
The honorable PM will join
this call in a moment.
Thank you.
-Hello, Mr. Kulkarni.
-Sir.
I have been briefed thoroughly
about the seriousness
of the situation.
I have only one question, Mr. Kulkarni.
And I want a straight and clear answer.
Do they really have
a stockpile of nerve gas?
Yes, sir.
Mr. Kulkarni, we cannot afford a war.
But if a nerve gas attack
is carried out on us
we'll have to retaliate.
We will have to unwillignly
go to war with Pakistan.
I need a solution to this problem.
Let me know what I can do to help.
Sir, you'll need to speak to
the Prime Minister of Pakistan.
You'll need to convince him
to stop his men...
and give us the information...
that we need.
How sure are you about
this information?
One of our agents is in
Balochistan right now...
and I have full faith in him.