-Are you lost?
-Rashid, wait.
Sajid, you're still alive?
I thought you were
killed at the wedding.
Allah wants you to win, Sajid.
Is this what I think it is?
-Yes.
-Chettan!
I should have known.
We brought these canisters
one by one, across the border.
It took us three years.
We were waiting for you.
I'll need a vehicle.
It will be arranged.
When do you need it?
How many canisters
are you taking?
All of them.
Okay, okay.
Thank you.
No, no!
No, no, no!
I need an update every hour.
Set up checkpoints
at all the entries and exits of the city.
Speed up!
You're telling me Kareem's
girlfriend got a text from him...
accidentally?
A text from a dead man's phone!
We're done for!
-Did you tell anybody?
-No, sir.
Nobody should find out about this. Got it?
What do we do now, sir?
What do we do?
Who was that the policeman
who posed as a tea-seller?
Shinde?
Yes.
Get him on the phone.
As-salaam alaikum, General Ansari.
Wa alaykumu as-salam, sir.
I hope I haven't disturbed
you by arriving unannounced.
But... why are you here?
It was a very urgent matter.
I couldn't afford to wait.
Please sit.
Let me get to the point, General Ansari.
The Indian PM called me
about a mission
that was being executed
right under our noses...
and we have no clue about it.
I don't quite understand.
Zulfiqar.
Who's that?
General Ansari
I haven't come all the way here
to waste your time or mine.
Given the circumstances,
we cannot afford to go to war with India.
It will shatter our economy.
And it will take us decades to rebuild it.
Sir.
I maybe an army officer.
But I'm first and foremost, a Pakistani.
I would never want...
the Pakistani citizens to suffer.
Trust me.
I don't know anything about Zulfiqar.
The hearing on your corruption case
is next month, right?
There are many who wish
that the judge does not
rule in your favor.
I just wanted to remind you that.
Thank you, sir.
But there are many who
want the ruling in my favor.
And if that doesn't happen...
they can cause a lot of
trouble for your government.
I'm aware of your influence in
this province and in the military.
If you ensure that
Zulfiqar is prevented
the corruption case against
you will be closed forever.
No matter what I do...
the ones carrying out Zulfiqar
won't stop.
No general in Balochistan
will oppose you.
Your wish is their command.
There's only one
person I'm worried about.
Major Sameer from the ISI.
But we'll take care of him.
Isn't your cabinet looking
for a new Chief of Army Staff?
I have no problem
accepting that offer.
Srikant!
You were supposed to tell
me when you got back.
Talk softly.
Fuck!
-Sorry.
-What happened?
Any leads?
We're combing through
Delhi for Moosa.
What about your
door-to-door search?
Nothing. Mostly false alarms.
We don't have any leads.
And we're running out of time.
Relax, Srikant.
We'll figure it out.
I just hope that...
they pressure General Ansari.
Good shot, Major.
Major Sameer,
please come with us.
Who the hell are you?
-Don't you know who I am?
-Of course.
Let me guess.
1/11 Infantry.
Why did you leave the PM unsecured?
-Cuff him.
-How dare you!
Do you know what you're doing?
Mask him.
I'll make sure you're
punished for this.
Let go of me, you bastards!
You cannot just barge
into somebody's house
and start asking questions.
You should've filed a notice first.
Ma'am, I am an undercover officer.
We don't file notices.
We came to know
through our network...
that Kareem sent her a message
-when...
-He was murdered.
That, we don't know.
All we know that
he sent you a message.
You might want to tell us about it.
-It'd be good for you.
-Is that a threat?
Are you threatening her?
Ma'am, you're
misunderstanding me.
The gang Kareem worked for,
cannot be trusted.
They--
Kareem was never a part of a gang.
You murdered him!
Now you're covering
up by blaming him.
When you returned his belongings
his phone was missing.
Where is it?
Where is his phone?
How would I know?
It must be with the
people he was working for.
Please!
Whatever you want to say,
please say it in court.
We are suing all of you.
ATS, Mumbai Police.
Ma'am! That's...
Don't do that.
We're just doing our duty.
We're just trying to help you.
You see…
if you co-operate,
we have a chance...
to find out why he died.
I didn't get any text from him.
Not when he was alive.
What do you mean?
Did you get a text after he died?
-Did he?
-Jonali, no need to answer him. Okay?
One minute, ma'am.
What was the message?
It was only one word.
What was it?
-Ink.
-Ink?
Correct.
Ink.
Is that a code word you used?
What does it mean?
I wish I knew.
You know it.
That's why he sent it to you.
Think.
What could it possibly mean?
-Think.
-She just said she doesn't know.
Will her answer change if
you keep pestering her?
She'll tell you when
she figures it out.
Fine?
Thank you.
Let's go.
When you figure out what
it means, let us know.
Come. Let's have some tea.
How's your therapy progressing, Jonali?
The counselor said...
I can stop taking anxiety
pills after three weeks.
Don't be scared.
They'll use everything against us.
Power, money, politics.
But you have to be strong. Okay?
But I'm sure Kareem was trying
to tell me something.
What do you mean?
Look at this.
-What could it mean?
-I don't know.
Kareem had once
thrown ink at a politician.
That's all that I can
gather from "ink."
But what could it possibly mean?
Don't worry, we'll find out.
Hello, sir. Good evening.
-The usual one, sir?
-Yes.
Send him another drink.
-Sure, sir.
-On my behalf.
I didn't order this.
It's a decent hotel.
Do you come here often?
Listen...
Let's exchange numbers.
We can plan something again.
Why? Once is enough!
What if I want to meet you again?
If we're destined to...
we'll certainly meet again.
Hi, sweetie.
Yes, I am on my way.
Of course, I was at work.
We have to do those extra
shifts these days.
There's a lot of work.
Is the little one asleep?
Oh, well...
I wanted to come play with him.
Never mind.
I'm coming.
I've sent you all the
videos on WhatsApp.
Fine.
Delete them from your phone.
I hope we are even now.
Yes.
And not a word about
this to anybody.
-Got it?
-Yes.
Leave.
Good job.
Thank you, bhai.
WhatsApp it to me.
Sure.
Is the team ready?
Yes. Everything is ready...
at Sanjay Colony.
Don't do anything…
until I give the word.
Got it.
Go home.
-Khuda hafiz.
We need to save this country!
We need to protect our religion!
Sir, why are you spreading hatred?
-Who said that?
-Hey, move aside.
What did you say?
Sir, don't you think
you're spreading hatred?
The truth is always bitter, son.
To stay in this country--
Kareem had written
"Ink" in the message.
Maybe he was trying to
tell me something about this incident.
This was the first time
Kareem raised his voice
against the system.
He started writing his
blog after this incident.
How is that related to this text?
Maybe he was doing something
similar this time.
You mean another ink attack?
Ink attack or maybe
something else like that.
I refuse to believe that
he could ever kill anybody.
He was not a terrorist.
Let's assume you're right about this.
But how do we prove it?
The police returned all his belongings...
except for his bodycam.
I am sure his
bodycam was with him.
Because that's the whole point
of pulling off a stunt like this.
You mean Kareem wanted
you to look for the camera?
What else could it possibly mean?
You said it yourself.
Kareem couldn't tell me everything.
He knew the police would
check all his stuff.
Maybe that's why he sent me
something only I could understand.
Makes sense.
I think we should
look for the camera.
After all the things
I did for my country...
this my reward?
This is not for what you
did for your country.
It's for what you were
going to do to your country.
Tell me.
Where is the nerve gas?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
Listen to me carefully.
We know everything.
I'll give you one more chance
to save yourself.
It doesn't matter if a million lives
like mine
are sacrificed for my Pakistan.
If you think you'll
succeed, you're wrong.
Here, look at this.
You used to follow his orders, right?
General Ansari has joined
the PM and deserted you.
If you continue to be stubborn...
you will die.
And that too for an infidel
who doesn't care about anybody
but himself.
Sameer, there's still time.
Give us what we want.
We'll close the matter.
Sir.
Srikant, I got a call from
Khursheed in Islamabad.
We have the location
coordinates of the nerve gas.
Sajid will be transporting them.
We need to move in now.
Okay, sir.
We have inputs from Intelligence.
Our target will move the
stock from this location.
The target is
a highly motivated individual.
He has extensive training in IEDs.
As far as I know
he has complete support
of Basharat and the locals.
Our communication units
will launch drones
to get their exact locations.
If they'd still be in the village
we'll attack them there.
If they leave the village
then I'll be stationed
with Unit Alpha here.
Unit Bravo will be here on standby
and Unit Charlie will be here.
Once they take the route on the mountain
there's no other way out.
We'll have to surround them on both sides.
Nobody fires at the
truck without my orders.
-Am I clear?
-Yes, sir.
-Yes, sir!
Good.
Catch it!
Go, get it.
Hurry up!
Throw it!
What are you looking for?
Did you lose something?
Nothing. Run along.
Listen.
Do you play here every day?
Did you find something here?
Anything at all?
Something secret?
Yes, something secret.
No, I didn't find anything.
Okay, go play.
You're doing Allah's work, sir.
These infidels won't find a place even
in hell for treating you like this.
God will punish them.
Can I be of any help to you?
Basharat?
Yes, brother.
Tell the groom right away
that he shouldn't go collect the turban.
Brother...
-has the wedding been called off?
-No.
The wedding will take place
on the decided date.
Now listen carefully.
Tell the groom right away to go to Delhi
and meet his elder brother.
Meet his Chettan.
He has chosen another girl for him.
He'll explain everything.
Thank you.
Farooq!
-We have to stop Sajid.
-Now?
Get all the boys.
Carry the weapons with you.
Basheer, Farooq, Ashraf, let's go!
Quick!
The number you're
trying to call is currently--
Damn!
Faster!
That's him! I can see him!
They are following us.
Drive faster.
He doesn't know it's me.
Sajid, stop!
Is that Basharat?
What does he want?
Sajid!
Stop.
Sajid, stop the vehicle!
Why did you stop us?
What's going on?
We have orders that the groom
must not leave the village.
What nonsense!
The mission has
been compromised.
I was told that the mission
should be finished at any cost.
-So, what happened suddenly?
-I don't know.
We have direct orders
from Major Sameer.
You can shove the orders
up a donkey's ass.
I am taking the truck--
Shoot.
In fact, shoot me in the back.
Because that's what cowards do.
I've been entrusted
with this mission...
and I shall complete it.
Sajid...
now is not the time for your nonsense.
Major Sameer has asked you to
go to Delhi and meet Chettan.
Chettan?
Damn you mother...
Target engaged.
Orders, please.
-Engage on target.
-Fire!
They're firing!
Do not shoot at the truck!
Attention all units.
This is Alpha.
The target is on the move.
He's heading towards you.
Engage to capture.
I repeat, engage to capture. Over.
-Copy.
-Alert! The target is coming!
Motherfucker!
Send out a red alert.
Call as many fire brigades
and ambulances as you can.
Alpha to Bravo.
-The target is approaching you.
-Copy.
Alert!
Do not shoot the truck!
Why have they put nails over there?
Get rid of them!
The truck might crash!
Damn it, the truck will crash!
Get rid of the nails!
Hurry up!
Yes, sir.
Fuck!
We need the masks now!
Get the masks!
-Masks!
-Get the masks!
Get down!
No leakage detected.
All canisters are intact.
Thank God!
If their plan worked...
it would have been a disaster.
I just wish that
bastard was captured!
Yes, but at least
Mission Zulfiqar is over.
Thank you.
Since the time you've been here,
you've been messing your health up.
You always have a drink
or a cigarette in your hand.
How else can one tackle stress?
There are other ways.
You can't keep smoking just
because your wife's not here.
Come on.
What's gotten into you?
Fuck, yeah!
I'm going to miss you.
-Me too--
-Don't force yourself.
You don't have to say it
just because I did.
Now go.
-Bye.
Listen...
I couldn't meet your husband.
What?
How can you?
I am not married.
I hope it's not because of me.
You really think too much
of yourself, Srikant!
Now go.
-Go!
-Okay.
So Ms. Saloni is still Ms. Saloni?
There's something going on.
On and off.
Who is he?
Bye.
-Major Vikram?
-Bye!
Moosa!
It's been ages!
Yes, it's been a long time.
Come in.
Faizan trusted me.
He entrusted me with this mission.
I let him down.
I don't know how...
I'll be able to face him.
Faizan was captured.
What happened?
-Is he a martyr now?
-He's currently in American custody.
And Major Sameer was arrested
by the Pakistani Army.
And General Ansari turned
out to be a traitor.
Zulfiqar is over.
Everything's over!
Zulfiqar is not over yet.
It's not over.
There is a Plan B.