WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
I informed Inspector Majid
when she went inside.
She never came out.
Only the fair-skinned man came out.
- How did he look like?
- He was tall and fair, with short hair.
I can help with his sketch.
Is this him?
Yes, that looks like him.
Where's Sartaj?
He didn't answer my call.
You're lucky.
Every religion says the same thing.
Everything is predestined.
The day I was born in Luxor, Egypt...
and you were born... in Mumbai?
It was decided that we'd meet here one day
and I would do this.
Endure the pain for two hours
and then… it will all go away.
What are you guys doing here?
Preparing for the 16th.
What's going to happen on the 16th?
Why did Gaitonde kill himself?
Some people are weak.
How did you betray him?
He betrayed us.
Aadam and Hawwa had two sons,
Haabil and Qaabil.
Allah asked them for a sacrifice.
Both of them
offered their sacrifices to him,
but Allah only accepted Haabil's.
Qaabil didn't like this
and he killed Haabil.
But Allah served Haabil justice.
Haabil, the world's first martyr.
And the first criminal...
that went to hell was Qaabil.
This story is in the Bible too.
Haabil is Abel and Qaabil is Cain.
We need to make sacrifices in our lives.
They have a message for us.
Why do we need to make sacrifices?
Why?
I don't know!
Allah is fed up with us.
He got sick of us when he made us.
We have to bear the pain for him
to start again
from the beginning.
That's the debt we owe him.
We have the place surrounded.
You can't escape.
You better surrender.
We have the place surrounded.
You can't escape.
You better surrender.
The cops are here. I'm leaving.
Sartaj.
I knew from Dilbagh Singh's face
that Parulkar would kill me.
Their plan was to kill me
inside the prison.
With time, we get used to everything.
After being beat continuously
for 22 days, I got used to it.
Everyday I'd wake up, take a bath,
get beaten and go to sleep.
Just when I began to expect
that nothing would change...
I met Mathu.
My old friend...
Mathu.
from the Mandrax and gold-smuggling days.
Easy money turns men into fools.
Sir, tea.
For you too.
I couldn't handle it.
If you'd stayed with me,
we could've destroyed them together.
But you're here.
I'm the king of Gopalmath.
I'm here by my own will.
They're all scared shitless of me.
Do you think I'm worthless?
Tell me if anyone gives you problems,
and I'll take care of them.
Isa's men... They're bastards.
Isa fled the country
and left them hanging here.
It doesn't matter.
I'll teach them a lesson.
Gaitonde.
They've planned to kill you in the prison.
They won't let you get out alive.
And you're talking about saving me?
The next one's a home run, okay?
Here it comes.
Back then, I thought Parulkar
was torturing me on Isa's orders.
But I didn't know that my dear friends,
Parulkar, Bhonsle and Trivedi
were behind this
and that they were following
my third father's orders.
Has he given up?
He will very soon.
Don't end up killing him.
Even if I chop him into pieces...
and throw them into the sea,
he won't be dead.
Bastard!
Like the Terminator...
- Fucker!
- That's how the Mahabharata begins.
What?
A king's semen falls into the sea.
- Oh!
- A fish swallows it.
A woman eats that fish and gets pregnant.
She gives birth to India.
A nation was born from the drops of semen.
You remind me of my father.
Was he a scholar?
No, but he told stories like you.
You guys...
Be careful. Your life is in danger.
There's not much time left.
They'll kill me in two or three days.
Why do you say that, boss?
I know what's coming.
I'll kill them all
if anything happens to you.
Get Kharvas for me.
- The white-colored one?
- I want to taste it one last time.
Boss, please don't say that.
Nothing will happen to you,
I'll get you out of here.
Stop saying all this.
- I was kidding. Listen.
- Yes?
I need a knife
to take care of a few guys here.
- He's a good man.
- Okay.
Scream, motherfucker!
You don't believe in God.
What's your name?
Jamila.
Is this your first time?
What did you say?
What language is that?
Farsi.
Where are you from?
Tell me, I'm not a cop.
Afghanistan.
We don't have much time. Just 20 minutes.
I don't have the strength in me to...
You don't have to do anything.
I was in such bad shape
that I didn't even
have the strength to fuck.
But I felt better when I thought about
taking revenge on Isa's men.
Isa's dog. Are you dead?
Come on.
- Wanna suck it?
- Do you have the balls to get sucked?
You want it, right?
I swear, slitting their throats
was more fun than fucking.
You'll get out of here when you're dead.
Parulkar, do you get it now?
Even in prison, I'm a god.
Mr. Singh?
Fucking bastards.
It's so dark in here.
Fuck, I can't see anything.
That's the bucket.
They think this will kill me. Assholes.
Gaitonde. Take a look.
This is the isolation cell.
The ceiling is low.
Shit and piss in the bucket.
Keep this flashlight.
Hide it in the bucket
if anyone comes to check.
Take it.
Be careful.
- Okay?
- Yes, sir.
I'll lie down here. Bastards!
Does it still hurt?
A little bit.
Will it ever be normal again?
What's normal?
Do you know what disabled people
call the abled?
What?
Anything can happen at any time.
Everything's temporary.
Everything.
Sartaj?
Please visit soon.
How are you?
The fever's gone.
We're interrogating Bhonsle tomorrow.
Did he agree?
He can't avoid it,
especially now, after Anjali's death.
Any lead on Malcolm?
But his fingerprints match with those
found at Trivedi's house.
It's almost certain that Anjali was...
He can't get away.
All the exit points are on alert.
I wonder why would anyone
kill a RAW agent.
It's a huge risk.
Sartaj, we'll find out.
Your NGO was transporting
Gaitonde's weapons to India
in those water tankers.
- What do you have to say about this?
- Nothing.
We're collecting evidence
from offshore accounts.
Go ahead.
What do you know about Trivedi?
Nothing.
Bunty delivered those weapons to Malcolm.
Who allowed him to use
a private freight line?
Tell us or we'll have to file
a police report.
Try doing that.
Don't hold yourself back, sir.
Do it for yourself,
if not for the country. It'll do you good.
So, you don't know Trivedi?
I do not.
Trivedi emailed you this picture.
Try to remember.
We know there are more emails.
Do your worst.
You people will not understand.
What are you talking about, sir?
Aren't you ashamed of betraying
your country...
Shut up!
- You can't see it.
- What can't we see?
You can't see
that this country's in danger.
You can't.
Maybe you aren't aware
that we're the most peace-loving country
in history.
We've never been the first to attack...
and this time is the same.
But if we're attacked...
we must be ready.
What attack?
The country's in danger.
We can't just sit and wait.
What danger?
You're such a smart group of guys,
figure it out yourselves.
Dilbagh Singh introduced me
to my third father.
I called you to repay his debt.
Everything will be destroyed in 25 days.
Why are you... Bastard.
You son of a bitch.
Let go.
Dirty bastard!
Give me some water, Parulkar.
Water, please.
Mr. Singh.
Please get me some water,
I'm dying of thirst.
Will you really kill me, fuckers?
Water, piss...
just give me anything to drink, Mr. Singh.
Parulkar was a bastard.
I could barely speak, or I'd have told him
to shoot me and end it all.
I survived for about 25 days
without food or water.
I had no strength left.
Every day seemed like my last.
Three days ago, your news was published
in all the papers.
By now, they're probably in the garbage.
The cows will eat them up.
Stop it. Your dad would've been so happy.
I dreamt of him the day before yesterday.
He wouldn't have.
What?
He wouldn't have been happy.
Why do you say that?
He surely had something
to do with Gaitonde,
for him to send us the cricket bat.
I told you,
his conscience was always clear.
Then why did Gaitonde call me?
Why would a famous gangster
remember an ordinary officer
after 25 years?
Because everyone remembers a good man.
Your father wasn't ordinary.
I didn't mean that.
Then what did you mean?
That he sold his integrity for this bat?
Then what's the truth, Mom?
The truth is that
when your father was at work,
he often gave Gaitonde his food.
Hold on.
Did he work at the prison
where Gaitonde was being held?
There's no record of it.
Yes. It was an unofficial posting
for two months
under Parulkar.
They'd beat him black and blue
in the prison.
Gave him no food or water.
He was kept in the isolation cell
for 15 days at a time.
Everyone thought he'd die.
Your dad couldn't bear to see this.
So he'd tell me to make extra rotis.
Ganesh.
Eat this.
Your father saw Gaitonde
as just another human being
and so he helped him.
A while later,
Gaitonde called and thanked us
and said, "Ask for anything you want."
But he took nothing.
One day, he casually mentioned
that you wanted to be a cricketer.
So Gaitonde sent us this bat.
Someone wants to talk to you.
Ganesh, hurry up. Someone will come.
Come on, be strong.
Close your eyes...
and chant...
"I am Lord Brahma."
"I am the Alpha and Omega."
Close your eyes and chant,
"I am Lord Brahma."
"I am the alpha and omega."
Gaitonde,
it's Trivedi.
I know your condition.
Guruji wants to have a word with you.
Gaitonde, you'll live.
You may feel that you're going to die,
but you will not.
We all carry the burden of our fathers.
In the west, the son envies the father.
Freud called this the Oedipus Complex.
Deep inside,
every son wants to kill his father.
But we believe in Yayati.
In contrast to the West...
the father envies the son.
The father wants to sacrifice the son.
And eventually, he must do it.
This is the blessing and the curse
of being a father.
Gaitonde's third father.
Who are you?
A friend, a brother, an enemy...
a father, a son or a lover,
whatever you want me to be.
What do you want?
I want you to believe that you'll live.
Bullshit. They'll kill me.
Relax.
Think about the first time you felt fear.
Look at the wall in front of you.
I killed her.
I killed my mother... with my own hands.
I've sinned.
I'm not going to survive.
I'm going to rot and die here.
You're both the mandala
and the door to it.
You'll survive.
You must survive.
Understand the mandala
and you'll be free of the curse.
It represents the universe.
A powerful device.
Like every word is a mantra,
every symbol is a key.
From ancient to modern times,
you will find symbols all around us.
They should only be placed
at the doorway...
or in the passage.
Gaitonde.
You rat.
Come out.
Come on.
Come.
I won't die.
What?
I'm... not going to die.
I came out to find
Isa's men waiting for me.
Mathu and I
against 40 of them.
RAKSHAK PARTY
It was certain that I'd die,
but that voice kept my hope alive.
It said, "You'll live, Gaitonde."
But I needed a miracle...
and it happened.
Men dressed in black
came and took me away.
I was half-conscious,
but I was dying to meet the one
who saved my life and changed my fate.
That man was my third father.
A mastermind.
He played a game with me in the prison
and now, he's playing
the 25-day game with Mumbai.
He told me to leave Mumbai.
Twenty-five days is all you have
to save Mumbai.
Gaitonde told the cop
about the 25-day matter.
The country's in danger.
Everyone will die, except Trivedi.
Mr. Sartaj, my information is never wrong.
Holy shit.
Subtitle translation by Harini